Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Luffy and the others are trying to
get to the rooftop of the dome to reach Kaido.
Charge!
We will take care of the rest!
Wait.
Kin'emon.
Dog! Cat!
You-gara guys!
We'll take over!
Hey, Zoro!
Oh, Luffy! Where are you going?
Up where Kaido is.
I'll come with you.
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Dammit!
I won't let you go, you fools!
I won't let you in this area!
We'll never be able to get up there!
Security's very tight!
We still got a bunch of enemies around us!
But for some reason,
I don't feel like we're gonna lose.
--You're right!
--Yeah, me neither!
It's strange. Why do we feel this way?
It's obvious, isn't it?!
Because the straw hat man is with us!
Let's go, Captain!
Yeah! Let's do it one more time! Ready?!
Everyone! I'll leave the rest to you!
Back us up!
I'm gonna go...
...take down Kaido!
"A Risky Invitation!
A Plot to Eliminate Queen!"
Luffy-san has the ability to draw people in.
Indeed,
the atmosphere changed
when Straw Hat appeared.
I was afraid of what would happen
when Kaido and Big Mom...
...declared their alliance.
This confusion that the
Straw Hats have created...
...is not a bad thing to me.
It's not just the Straw Hats...
Those are definitely Udon prisoners.
Even Hyogoro's here!
What happened at the Excavation
Labor Camp in Udon?
Was Babanuki threatened?
This is Chief Warden Babanuki from Udon!
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain Kid,
and the other hoodlums
are all quietly behind bars.
I just called you to say
everything's okay here...
That doesn't add up.
I'm not gonna blame you now.
You've always been brainless.
You always say one word too many!
Have you ever heard the word "kindness"?
We must settle this situation already.
Now you sound like a leader!
Damn Straw Hat! That shithead!
Onigashima is in chaos...
Hawkins.
Don't you think this is a good chance?
If an enemy comes, I'll just slice them.
I don't know what you mean by "chance."
I didn't know you were so
loyal to Kaido... sama.
You're only here because Apoo fooled you.
Kid, you, and Apoo formed an alliance...
But Apoo betrayed you two!
You unwillingly joined the
Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Now's the best time to betray them...
Are you encouraging me to betray them?
Don't take me for a fool.
One percent.
What have you been trying to predict?
The probability that this certain man survives
until tomorrow.
Just one percent... I feel sorry for him.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Come in, Tobi Roppo!
How annoying! What do you want, King?!
Guys... As you know,
the situation has changed.
On the day of the annual Fire Festival,
out of all our enemies,
we let the Akazaya samurai invade.
This is the worst blunder
in Onigashima's history.
We must cease the internal strife...
...that Kaido-san encouraged.
Internal strife?
It has to do with Young Master Yamato.
The one who brings
the missing Young Master Yamato home...
...earns the right to challenge one of us,
the Lead Performers, for our position.
Though I was looking forward to it,
we must postpone it for now.
What?! Really?!
Of course.
Look around you, Big Sis.
Oh, Pay-Pay! Just who I was looking for!
Yamato got away climbing the wall,
so I need you to carry me on your back...
--No way!
--You must!
Shut up, you shitty brats.
Who did you call a brat?!
I'm not a brat anymore,
don't call me that!
Kaido's on the rooftop.
The enemies are gonna climb to the top of the castle
from the inside.
Each of you must intercept them
in any way available to you.
We have 30,000 troops.
As for them, they only have 5,000 troops.
But you'd better not underestimate them.
Good luck.
Clank.
Hey, Drake!
This mess reveals an opportunity.
Come along with me.
It's a bit too tough for me to go by myself.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go kill the one who I wanna kill!
To where Queen is.
Even if an officer gets killed
in this confusion,
it'll be considered a casualty of war.
Don't get me involved in your rivalry.
Do you wanna diminish our forces?
He's useless anyway.
I'm not sure about this...
Just follow me.
I like the way this is going.
Straw Hat-san and the others!
We'll clear the way for
you to get to the castle!
Yeah! So don't waste your energy!
Charge!
Send Straw Hat-san and the
others into the castle!
Don't let them get into gear!
They're damn prisoners and yakuza!
It's extremely chaotic.
We must kick that big
one out of the way, too!
I can't believe such a human exists.
FIVE
Don't be scared! We've got to do it!
Attack his feet!
Oh, that was close.
Guys.
Jimbei-san!
What?! Did you say there is a traitor...
...among the officers?!
Is it true, Who's-Who?
Yeah.
Come to think of it,
Babanuki was acting strange.
Have you figured out who it is?
Well...
Who do you think it is?
What the hell?!
Don't tell me you guys...
...are trying to supplant your superior?!
That's highly likely...
Haw... Haw... Haw... Haw...
You too, Hawkins?!
Pay the price for your betrayal
and agonize in pain!
Mama! I don't wanna die!
You're a bad actor!
How could you be fooled by shit like that?
Don't call good acting shit!
Didn't I act quite well?
Well, let's just leave it at that.
What's going on?!
The probability that you
survive until tomorrow...
...is one percent.
My reading of your fortune...
I was kind enough to tell you that.
X. Drake.
We're the ones
who want to know what's going on!
We Animal Kingdom Pirates aren't
so careless that we don't
notice someone betraying us.
Why did you suspect me?!
Ask yourself that question!
You let Trafalgar Law escape in the Flower Capital,
didn't you?
If you're plotting to let me escape...
I'm in.
There was a guard...
I thought it had to be you.
What's your objective?
I see...
The one you wanted to kill is...
It's you, you piece of shit!
We should be ashamed
that we had a rat as our officer.
What are you up to?
Did you infiltrate us by yourself
or with other people?
Who are you?!
You'd better come clean.
I guess this is it...
It's impossible to make an excuse.
Unfortunately, I...
...won't tell you anything
even if it means death!
We're not gonna kill you...
My torture will torment you mentally.
Can't wait, huh? Drake...
FIVE
The straw hat man's friends are all strong!
Damn monster...
Straw Hat-san!
Just watch us! We once fought...
...against one just as large as that!
Pierna Fleurs!
Here we go!
Thanks!
The weather forecast is rain!
Rain Tempo!
I'm cranking it!
Fire!
I'm frozen!
I can't move.
Not a chain!
You're amazing, Sanji!
I'm really going to throw you.
I'll be fine! I'm a rubber man!
Be careful.
Gear Three!
Bone Balloon!
I'm on it.
Three-Sword Style...
...Secret Arts!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Bazooka!
That monster is just like Oars.
Back then, it took all of us
to finally bring down something that massive!
But things have changed!
Luffy!
Gear Four!
Bounce-Man!
Oh, he did it again!
That form... He's like
the God of Fire himself!
What should I do?
Even if I run from them,
I'll be surrounded
by a legion of the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
I guess there's no hope...
Amazing!
Are you gonna talk or not?!
All right.
So you don't want torture?
What a bummer...
This is...
...a thank you gift...
...from me!
Duck!
Now what? How should I get away?
There's no way to go back to the Navy?!
No! Let's not think about that now!
There's still hope!
Gum-Gum...
Get out of my way!
Juki!
X...
Kong...
--...Gun!
--...Calibur!
He's so impressive!
That's...
Drake from the Tobi Roppo!
Why did he attack the Giant?!
There's still...
...hope.
Damn!
Luffy-san is amazing!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I'm fighting alone for a reason!
Please!
Let me fight alongside you guys!
The traitor won't be forgiven!
The samurai warriors get involved
in the attack by Kaido's army
aiming at Drake who vowed
to fight alongside Luffy.
Nami stands up to save her cornered friends.
Her opponent is Ulti, one of the Tobi Roppo!
She challenges the strong
enemy at the risk of her life.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A New Rivalry! Nami and Ulti!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!