mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
After a fierce fight,
Dogstorm and Cat Viper finally took down Jack.
That's enough, you fools!
A head-on clash between
the Akazaya members and Kaido now begins!
I know you'll eventually
get tired from running and die!
Can't wait to see how many you can dodge!
"An Inherited Technique!
Unleashing Oden's Secret Swordplay!"
Kaido!
Get out of my way!
What's going on?! No!
It's cold! I feel cold!
No! Somebody, help...
What's going on?!
This chaotic battle will end
when the samurai's hope is gone.
You can locate him, right?
Bao Huang.
You can count on me.
Why are you running?!
I told you I'm Kozuki Oden!
I don't know what you're talking about!
So fishy! Incomprehensible!
Are you okay?! Are you hurt?!
Oh?
Momonosuke-kun, are you okay?!
Momonosuke-kun!
It seems like he is really worried about me.
Momonosuke-sama, don't be fooled.
Momonosuke-kun!
I've always been waiting to see you!
Let me protect you!
It does not look to me like he is lying...
Who is that man?
Why does he care about me so much?
You're there, right, Momonosuke-kun?!
I'm glad that you're okay!
I'm Kozuki Oden, so I know...
...what my son Momonosuke-kun smells like!
What?! Do I smell that bad?
I like your smell.
You smell very good...
Are you hurt, Momonosuke-sama?!
No, I am okay!
That's good!
Come jump into my arms!
What's the matter?!
Are you going through a rebellious phase?!
On the snowy...
...night
The two...
...who missed each other
But they didn't get a chance
To see each other for so long
Finally seeing each other
Under the moonlight
That excitement!
Kin-sama!
Kin-san!
I'll avenge Oden-sama!
Take this!
You really wanna die that badly?
Kin-san!
What?!
You fools are so annoying!
How boring...
I guess that's all you've got after all.
Not even remotely close
to Oden's swordplay...
Don't underestimate...
...the samurai!
You're...
Don't underestimate the samurai!
I am definitely going to...
...avenge Oden-sama today!
No way.
There are only the remnants
of Oden's group here.
What am I doing?
If it'll help Oden-san...
I'm happy to die!
I want to bring down Kaido!
Oden-sama!
Even though I made it this far,
I have not accomplished anything yet...
Guys, listen carefully!
I'm gonna teach you how to use...
...Oden Two-Sword Style!
I'll initiate you into my secret arts!
I get to inherit Oden Two-Sword Style?!
I started following him
without his permission...
I did not expect I would inherit
Oden-sama's secret arts as a samurai of the Land of Wano...
It is a great honor!
I am happy to inherit Oden-sama's will!
Hey!
What is wrong, you guys?
Can't you see?!
Why do you think
you alone have the right to inherit?!
"Why"?
Because I am definitely his best disciple!
Kin-san, that's nonsense! If the order of
joining his clan matters, we joined the same time.
No, respect matters more than the order!
I respect Oden-sama the most!
So I'm the one who'll inherit it!
No one else!
No, if that's the case, it's gonna be me!
You use shuriken.
So leave the two-sword style to me!
You-gara have a different
kind of sword style!
Since he has such a big heart,
I should be the one to inherit his secret arts!
Why bother passing it down
to a small-hearted man?
--I'll inherit it!
--What?!
That is enough!
I love Oden-sama...
...more than anyone!
You coward! Don't try to pull that!
I love Oden-sama more than anyone!
--No, I do!
--Me, too!
--It's me!
--I love him!
--No, it must be me!
--No, me!
--So it's me!
--Me!
--No, it's me!
I am the one!
You are right, sir!
Hey, guys! I'm gonna teach you
how to use Oden Two-Sword Style!
No thank you.
We have our own style...
Why?!
Hey!
It is true that
our strengths are nothing like Oden-sama's.
But...
Kin-san, you're getting fired up
in your head as always...
You're trying to go off by yourself again,
aren't you?
Kin-san always does that.
Guys...
But it's been a while...
...since we fought together like this.
I remember the days we ate
Oden-sama's oden together.
I wanna eat fish cake with burdock...
Eggs are better!
No, shirataki noodles are the best.
There's no argument!
You're my little brother,
but you're clueless...
Ganmodoki is the best!
No way.
Chicken wings are everything!
As always, no one backed down...
But we are comrades
who sat around a pot together!
Maybe I put too much pressure on myself.
All right, let's fight again!
You guys are not Oden after all.
You were acting like great samurai
under Oden's wing,
and even now, after Oden's death,
you're still like kids playing samurai.
What can you do?
Why don't you fight us
and find out if we are really just playing samurai?!
All right... Bring it on!
Let's go!
Crimson Cat Dance!
Kappa Style!
River of Sea!
What?!
Canine...
...Scourge!
Fallen Snow Scythes!
Slicing Rounds!
Why?!
Their attacks are nothing
like Oden's swordplay.
How can they cut me?!
Kaido!
Come on now!
Come on! Now!
Ninpo: Scrolling Jutsu!
My scroll will roll up anything!
I'll give it back to you!
Blast Breath!
Restoration!
We did it...
Raizo, you were almost too late!
But that made Kaido drop his guard.
You think you can kill me?
You guys are merely his
spineless retainers...
...who only chase your lord Oden's shadow!
That is right.
We have always been spineless.
I'm gonna teach you
how to use Oden Two-Sword Style!
No thank you.
We have our own style...
Why?! It's Oden Two-Sword Style!
Why don't you wanna inherit it?!
Of course, we wanted to inherit it.
Everyone insisted they
were his first disciple.
We had a serious fight
to decide who was his best disciple.
We all loved him too much,
so it looked like a fight to the death.
We admired him so much...
Then why were we running, leaving him behind?
We were nothing but hoodlums
before he led us!
We knew how big his heart was.
By believing in him,
we could become stronger and stronger.
But we could not save even him!
We could not save the Land of Wano!
We have always been thinking!
If only we were stronger!
If we were strong enough to save Oden-sama!
If we are going to die anyway,
let us at least die as Oden-sama's samurai!
Oden!
Two-Sword Style!
What are you doing?!
What rubbish!
Listen, guys! Ryuo is...
Listen to me!
We polished our sword skills
to save the Land of Wano today!
Kaido!
Blast Breath!
Flame-Rend!
Don't underestimate...
...the samurai!
People will talk about how heroically you died
for generations...
I don't mind being forgotten!
My spirit...
...will live on!
Oden Two-Sword Style!
Paradise Totsuka!
Our beloved Luffy-senpai
who aims at becoming the King of the Pirates!
He creates havoc all over the Land of Wano
to take down Kaido
who dominated the country!
I, Bartolomeo, will tell you all about
his numerous adventures in that territory!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Special Episode: Barto's Secret Room"
Luffy-senpai's gonna become
the King of the Pirates!