Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
I have two questions for you.
What will happen if you take damage...
...that has nowhere to go?
Why did my own arm get chopped?!
All the damage must...
Kid...
...doesn't have...
...a left arm!
Spin & Sonic!
What's wrong?
You suddenly came alive.
Kid!
My body feels light.
Go, Partner!
"A Shadowy Figure Pulls the Strings!
Onigashima in Flames"
Sanji!
Stay focused! Behind you!
You brat!
Ouch.
What?!
Queen-sama's sword got broken!
It definitely hit his neck, right?
How could he break the sword
with his neck?
The Color of Arms?!
Whatever it is, that's impossible!
You didn't use Haki, did you?
Germa's scientific technology
is amazing, huh?!
What's this?!
Your body is fascinating!
I remember Judge said once!
Give humans exoskeletons!
An extraordinary healing ability!
Physical strength!
A heart of ice that won't feel anything!
I'm sorry!
I shouldn't serve
anything unpalatable to you...
Are you trying to leave a scar
on a woman's face?!
Hey, stay with me!
They knocked a woman unconscious...
What are they?!
It can't be helped
because they're strong and obedient.
When they die, we can just restock.
It takes five years to make
a 20-year-old soldier.
This is the depot
where we keep a stock of the soldiers.
No, I...
...don't wanna be
a cold-blooded monster like them!
You're a monster!
Welcome to this monster world!
Black Coffee Beam!
Wait a minute!
What's happening to my body?!
Give me some time to think!
Think back! What did I do?!
What are you doing?
That's very powerful, Nami-san!
Soba Mask!
Nami-sa...
Sangoro!
Is it because
I transformed into Soba Mask?
No way!
Am I gonna become heartless at this rate?!
Sanji...
...is acting strange...
There is one of the Straw Hats!
He's cornered by Queen-san!
He's mumbling something.
This is our chance! Shoot and kill him!
Black-Leg Sanji! You're finished!
Yay! We got him!
Ya-hoo!
That hurt!
What?!
His exoskeleton is so tough!
Put on the combat suit!
Show me more
of Germa's scientific technology!
I have nothing to do with them!
Don't lump me in with those shitholes!
CAVE CHAMBER
Drake!
If you're persistent,
you won't be popular!
You're probably a spy for the Navy.
But it doesn't matter now...
What matters is whether
you want to take down Kaido or not!
When this battle is over,
whoever the winners are,
they'll be badly bruised!
It won't be that hard to crush them then!
What a dirty trick... That's so you!
I'm just saying...
...we have a good chance of winning!
We have power!
We still have power!
You're not gonna believe
how powerful these Giants are!
Zanki!
ZANKI
Fuga!
FUGA
Inbi!
INBI
What do you think?
Do you wanna ally with us
and just snatch up the spoils at the end?!
Kaido's army and the rebel army...
Since we don't belong to either,
we have no reason to fight each other!
I'm amazed...
Do you think I'd trust a coward like you?
You're not trustworthy, either!
I'm telling you this because
I think it'd be beneficial to you!
You won't have...
...another chance like this!
STAIRCASE BETWEEN FIRST AND SECOND FLOOR
INSIDE THE CASTLE
Master-sama!
We rescued Komachiyo!
I'm glad that you're okay...
Komachiyo, thank you!
Thank you all, too!
Praise me more, Master-sama!
Komachiyo, you're great!
Hurry up! The fire's gonna get us!
Everyone, be careful!
A ghost!
A lower-human-body creature!
Somebody! Please help-bu!
What?
What?!
Somebody! Somebody-bu!
Stop, stop! What are you doing?!
Please help-bu!
I said stop!
Who are you-bu? I am Kin'emon-bu!
Calm down! Calm down!
Isn't he a ghost?
A human?
Is it a human?
I am looking for my ally-bu!
I am your ally, Kin'emon!
It's me, Usopp!
Let go of me-bu!
There is no time to lose-bu!
A lot of blood!
Are you okay?!
Usopp, he can't hear us!
His ears are on the other half!
Oh, yeah!
But we gotta tell him that it's us!
Who are you?! Reveal your identity-bu!
How is he talking?
With farts.
I heard that's his special skill.
--What?
--Farts?!
--What an amazing skill!
--What should we do? Um...
All right!
Is that the Reversed Crescent Moon?!
That means you are my ally-bu!
--Great!
--He got it!
Then I need your help-bu!
The thing is we fought Kaido earlier...
...and got defeated...
However...
...one of my companions
is still breathing faintly...
...so I need you to help her!
Let us take Hamlet!
I'll leave Tama to you!
I'm counting on you!
Gee! Everyone needs me!
Thank you-bu! I do not know who you are,
but you are my ally!
From the left tower on the castle's first floor,
you can enter a crawl space!
Count on me!
Gee, they're really high-maintenance!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
There she is!
Nico Robin!
They're so persistent...
They won't stop chasing us!
--Don't let her get away!
--Oh! They came from the front, too!
I'll get the credit!
Take her to Kaido-sama!
Should be alright
if we mess her up a little!
Catch her!
Robin-san!
Don't worry! We're here!
We're glad to have you guys!
Minks! How dependable!
We'll take care of them!
You can go ahead, Nico Robin!
Okay! Thanks!
Sorry to cause you trouble.
CP-0?
Nico Robin...
...must come with us...
It's not very elegant
to force a woman to do something.
No need to talk.
We'll just do what we gotta do.
A little bit more...
Endure a little bit more...
Kiku!
I just met our ally...
Anyway...
I could not believe that I was alive
even after my torso was cut off...
I guess when my body was cut in half
by Law-dono, it was not reattached properly...
It is a miracle!
Now if only...
If only Kiku could be...
saved... somehow...
Hey...
Hey!
Respond, Kanjuro!
Hey! Can you hear me?! Kanjuro!
No way!
Why am I hearing Orochi's voice?
I am sure I chopped off his head
with my own hands!
--Kanjuro!
--And Kanjuro is already...
Hey, Kanjuro!
Yes, Orochi-sama...
You're barely breathing, Kanjuro.
I... I must say that this is...
...the end of my performance...
Yeah, I take my hat off to you!
Your performance was amazing!
I appreciate your kind words
more than anything...
Kanjuro, can you hear them?
The cheers for you?
F-For me?
Kurozumi!
We've been waiting for you!
But I'm still frustrated...
Resentful!
That's right...
Our ancestors...
...are waiting...
...for a spectacular encore!
Draw it for me, Kanjuro!
The Kurozumi Clan's burning grudge!
Who is the winner?!
The deep-seated wrath of
the Kurozumi Clan...
...will parade through this castle,
and at last,
it will... it will walk into the abyss,
and the bottom where it dead-ends
will be our graveyard!
Soothe our spirits!
Kanjuro!
As you wish.
I am going to show you...
...Kurozumi Kanjuro's final performance!
KUROZUMI CLAN SUICIDE
The Kurozumi Clan suicide... Rapid finale!
Kazenbo!
We're gonna get burned!
A... A monster!
I have a report!
A mysterious giant specter appeared
on the second floor inside the castle!
The specter is moving through the walls
like some kind of ghost!
The castle is now on fire!
The time, time, time, time to show!
Germa's suuuiiit!
You shitty lizard...
I'm sick of hearing it!
We can't stay here anymore!
Let's escape, everyone!
This is no time for fighting!
You're right...
Before the flames cut off our retreat!
Kozuki's support force...
The emperor of the sea...
Pride comes...
...before a fall!
Blast Breath!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Law and Kid face Big Mom's fierce
persistence and are cornered!
When their strong will to break
the dominance of the old generation comes together,
the two men, who have the worst chemistry,
unleash their awakened Devil Fruit abilities!
On the next episode of One Piece! "A Countercharge!
Law and Kid's Return-Attack Combination"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!