Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy and Kaido clash
on the rooftop again.
The castle is still in chaos...
Somebody! Somebody-bu!
Stop, stop! What are you doing?!
Please help-bu!
I said stop!
Who are you-bu? I am Kin'emon-bu!
Calm down! Calm down!
Isn't he a ghost?
A human?
Is it a human?
And fierce battles continue.
Meanwhile, Orochi and Kanjuro...
The deep-seated wrath of
the Kurozumi Clan...
...will parade through this castle,
and at last,
it will... it will walk into the abyss,
and the bottom where it dead-ends
will be our graveyard!
KUROZUMI CLAN SUICIDE
The Kurozumi Clan suicide... Rapid finale!
Kazenbo!
"A Countercharge!
Law and Kid's Return-Attack Combination"
I'm Kozuki Oden!
I'll save the Land of Wano
and the Flower Capital!
I know Momonosuke-kun is going to
stop this island!
But I'll use my power
in case something goes wrong!
I'll get rid of tons of explosives
in the armory!
At least minimize the damage, if any!
Young Master Yamato!
Where are you going?!
The armory is at the lowest level
of the basement!
Can I get there in time?
Momonosuke-kun!
Slow the island down even a little bit!
It takes effort! Hang in there!
My guts! You can still do it, Momonosuke!
You can still do more!
I gotta create more and more Flame Clouds...
...to outnumber Kaido's Flame Clouds!
More, more!
I won't let Onigashima
reach the Flower Capital!
Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
What a lousy attack!
Punk...
...Gibson!
What a lousy technique!
Chambres!
We gotta wear her out even a little bit!
Injection Shot!
Hera!
Yes, Mama!
Destroy their shitty weapons!
Chambres!
I'm getting a little frustrated...
Mama! I can take them down on my own!
Hey! Don't try to hog all the fun!
Sorry.
Mama! I'm here for you, too!
Let's kill them together!
Hey, you can do more, right?
Don't play dumb!
Are you stupid enough to face an Emperor
of the Sea without any trump card?!
Trafalgar... Has your power awakened?
I'm not used to it yet...
I'd use it if I were faced with death,
but it wears me out inordinately,
so it might be
a critical misstep in a fight.
Same here.
But we can't make any progress like this!
Back me up with that ace up your sleeve!
I'll take those heads off you!
It's gonna hurt but be patient!
You shitty old bag!
How stupid you are to think
the bigger the better!
Prometheus!
Leave it to me, Mama!
You just made the target big for us.
What a dumb technique.
Punk Rotten!
The samurai who are trying to take back
the Land of Wano!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates
who are fighting back against them!
It's useless! Useless!
Everything is in the palm of my hand!
I know, Kaido!
About the giant armory
in the basement of the castle!
I know what's there!
The weapons that I had made!
And tons of ammo!
There's gonna be a massive,
massive, massive explosion!
Ignite them, Kanjuro!
Blow everything up!
To the abyss, to the abyss.
And at our graveyard of the Kurozumi Clan,
we'll have a great finale!
This is it! It's all over!
I'm tired of dealing with those morons!
Come here already, Fukurokuju!
Flower Shuriken!
That's nothing!
Earlobe Crackers!
I'm avenging our lord! Die! Nin!
Ninjas think of nothing but their task!
Let's get out of here! Escape!
Before Onigashima is engulfed in flames
and explodes!
A war between pirates
is none of our business!
This is strict punishment
for naughty brats like you!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
Did I get the first one?!
Kid!
Those two are keeping Big Mom tied down?
How strong!
I'll have your head!
Back me up with that ace up your sleeve!
K-Room!
Anesthesia!
I'll make it very painful!
I'll give you tremendous pain, too!
The penetration is harmless!
But K-Room...
...generates a shockwave from inside!
Shock Wille!
Mama! You're bleeding!
Damn you shitty brat!
I'll make you magnetic!
Assign!
Oh? I'm sticking to Mama!
What the hell? Did I become a magnet?
Whoa-whoa! That's not it yet!
--The towers' steel beams...
--...will collapse! Oh no!
What?!
Release it, Trafalgar!
Don't tell me what to do!
Punk Clash!
She was crushed under the steel beams!
She must be dead...
Not even Big Mom can...
That was my ace...
How's that, you old monster bag?!
With the awakened
Magnet-Magnet Fruit power,
you can turn things into magnets.
How long will it last?
Why should I give away secrets to you?
She got back on her feet!
We only made her mad...
Getting mad means
her back is against the wall.
It's your back that's against the wall!
I backed you up!
Why didn't you get her with one shot?!
Life...
...or...
...red-bean soup!
Oh, no! That's Soul Pocus!
Life or red-bean soup?!
We have red-bean soup, don't we?!
No, we spilled it all...
Damn beggars! Just be happy you're alive!
If we don't have soup,
she'll steal our lifespans!
Stand up, you guys!
I'll give you life!
I'm gonna use
a year's worth of my lifespan...
There's no other way
to make myself stronger.
Stronger than now...
I can't believe that old bag.
She's getting bigger...
Well, the bigger the better for us...
Gee...
It'll be quite a chore to send her flying
or slice her into pieces.
This means the Four Emperors are
stronger than we expected.
Gigantified?! Look how big she is now!
The castle is on fire.
The situation couldn't be more dangerous!
Yeah...
This Performance Floor...
...is like hell!
While they're keeping Big Mom busy,
and Momonosuke-kun
is slowing Onigashima down,
I...
...will do what I need to do!
There are many soldiers ahead!
I gotta go around from the Cave Chamber!
I need to get rid of the explosives
as soon as possible!
I haven't felt this much pain...
...in decades...
I recognize you both...
Trafalgar Law!
"Captain" Kid!
And Straw Hat Luffy...
You guys really came to take my place...
I can't believe
we can't even study history...
...without taking down
a monster like this!
As long as you live, don't hold back
from exerting all your strength!
Even if I die,
I'll dislodge her from that position!
Come take it!
My place as an Emperor of the Sea!
Sanji is tormented by an intense conflict
and nearly loses himself.
In the end, will he choose strength or heart?
The oath of determination
exchanged between the two arms, Sanji and Zoro,
gives new life to these close matches
to defeat the powerful enemies they are up against.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"For Luffy ? Sanji and Zoro's Oath"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!