iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
"Luffy's Peak
Attained! Gear Five"
I can hear the Drums of Liberation.
I'm hearing them
for the first time in 800 years...
DRUMS OF LIBERATION
The Drums of Liberation!
I'm positive!
He is here!
JOYBOY
Joyboy...
...has returned!
What happened...
...to me?
How come I can still stand up?
I lost the battle...
But this is getting fun!
Joyboy?!
Luffy is?!
JOYBOY
Is that what Zunesha said?!
This is getting fun!
PLEASURE HALL
INSIDE THE LEFT BRAIN TOWER
You're awake...
Pirate man!
Luffy?!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR
What?
Is that the straw hat man?
Straw Hat?!
Hey!
He's still alive-yoi!
Luffy's not dead?!
Big Bro's still alive?!
That's great!
MARY GEOISE
PANGAEA CASTLE
Sacrificing one of our best agents...
THE HALL OF POWER
...only to enrage Kaido
is like putting the cart before the horse.
But what if it's better
than the alternative?
It's better to eliminate a risk factor.
The World Government...
...has always tried to
get ahold of the Gum-Gum Fruit,
but it never came into our hands.
For 800 years!
It's as if...
...the fruit is evading us...
That's not entirely implausible.
Zoan Type Devil Fruits
have a will of their own.
Furthermore, that Devil Fruit
bears the name of a god.
Another name for the Gum-Gum Fruit is...
The Zoan, Human-Human Fruit,
Mythical Type, Model...
..."Nika."
They say that his body
had the exact properties of rubber.
He fought as he fancied,
and made people smile.
The Warrior of Liberation.
Also known as...
...Nika, the Sun God!
Awakening it is said to give
its user's rubber body even more strength...
...and freedom.
I heard that
it's the most ridiculous power...
...in the world.
The song Kozuki Oden loved?!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE
THE TREASURE REPOSITORY, ONIGASHIMA
Komurasaki!
H-Hiyori!
I really liked Oden, too!
Think twice!
I was exploited by Kaido!
Let's escape together.
So pull the nail out of me...
You've been repaying...
...the samurai's kindness
with hostility...
I conceived of the idea of changing his sentence
from boiling to shooting a minute ago!
And we'll execute not only Oden...
...but also all his family members!
Who do you think will listen to you now?
My father...
...kept his promise to you,
didn't he?
He believed that you and Kaido...
...would free the Land of Wano,
so he spent five years...
...playing the fool and dancing!
He didn't even make
a single excuse to his family!
My father kept his promise!
He believed that you'd keep your word
and set everyone free,
so he withstood the one-hour boiling!
Being cooked by the heating oil!
He always, always
had a smile on his face...
...but the whole nation was taken hostage,
and he was carrying the burden
all by himself.
I wonder how painful it must've been!
What's the matter, Hiyori?
Father, are you okay with
people swearing at you?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Why?
Because I have you guys!
Yeah?! Then I'll stay with you forever!
Yeah, Oden was a hell of a samurai!
I applaud him.
As the Shogun,
I can even give your father a reward!
My name is...
...Kozuki Hiyori!
Watch what you say, you insolent man!
Even when I starved and dressed in rags,
I've been living up to my father's name!
There wasn't even a single day
when you were the true Shogun!
You're foolish and pathetic!
The more foolish and pathetic you become,
the more people's deaths will have been in vain!
Hey! Stop! Don't do anything to me!
Seeking revenge is so outdated!
Even if you kill me,
you can't defeat Kaido!
Orochi-sama...
I failed...
Are you Kanjuro?!
I'm finished...
You're just in time!
I'll give you a new stage!
Burn her to death!
Charge!
The woman who endured for 20 years
fails to get her revenge!
What a tragicomedy!
You see?!
You relic of the Kozuki, Hiyori!
This is... This is how lucky...
...the strong are!
Orochi-sama...
Not this way! Don't come to me!
Kanjuro, you idiot!
Hiyori, you gotta help me!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
A dawn will surely come.
The Kozuki...
...is a clan that keeps their promises!
I can do everything I wanted to do!
I think I can fight a little bit more!
My heartbeat sounds funny!
This is my peak!
This is it!
Gear Five!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Someone's Color of the Supreme King?!
Where is it coming from?!
Hey! Guys!
What's that on the roof?
What?!
Kaido-san?!
Straw Hat?!
Is that Luffy?!
Muscle! Muscle!
Muscle!
Here we go!
Straw Hat...
You're alive!
Thank you.
What?
What?!
What?!!
Blast Breath!
Go get him!
Gear Five!
I'm sorry for what the idiot did earlier.
Over...
Thunder Bellow...
Iron Body!
What?!
CP-0?! Why is he here?!
I didn't want to win like that.
No problem.
Let's settle this!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodou nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
The new experience that defies logic!
The earth becomes bouncy
and all of his techniques are bizarre!
Is he a god or Luffy or something else?!
The comedic scene is enough
to make your eyes pop out of your head.
Attention, everyone! This is his peak!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ridiculous Power! Gear Five in Full Play"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!