With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
An Emperor of the Sea, Kaido.
Another Emperor of the Sea, Big Mom.
Both fell.
That marked a turning point in time.
Thus, the stunning awakening of
Luffy who became an Emperor of the Sea...
...shook the world.
Times are beginning to change
in a big and definite way.
Their adventure advances to the next stage.
"A New Emperor!
Buggy the Genius Jester!"
Hey!
You're not qualified to be a captain!
I... I'm... I'm sorry...
You put all the crewmembers at risk!
How can you be so stupid?!
Well, everyone was okay,
so maybe that's enough...
Don't go easy on him, Jimbei!
C-Color of the Supreme King?!
Stop it, Boss!
Don't get close to an angry Nami!
Oh, did you finish the repairs?
Yeah, it's perfect!
Did you see how tough the Sunny was?!
It fell from that height,
but only broke a yard!
What's that noise?
I guess you can still afford
to feel hungry!
Robin-chan!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Thanks!
Love, love, love, love...
Oh!
Our wanted posters.
Wanted posters?!
Let me see!
Robin-chan!
The senior captain of the Straw Hat Fleet
with 5,600 members,
the Emperor of the Sea Straw Hat Luffy,
and the nine senior officers...
How did their bounty rankings turn out?
Did it go up?
SHIP'S DOCTOR
CHOPPER THE COTTON CANDY LOVER (PET)
Ship's doctor, Chopper the Cotton Candy Lover.
"Pet" in brackets.
BOUNTY: 1,000 BERRIES (UP BY 900 BERRIES)
Bounty: 1,000 berries.
Up by 900 berries.
Hey! It went up but...
NAVIGATOR, CAT BURGLAR NAMI
Navigator, Cat Burglar Nami.
Bounty: 366 million berries.
BOUNTY: 366 MILLION BERRIES
Over 100 million?!
I wish I could have that money!
Yeah!
Musician, Soul King Brook.
MUSICIAN, SOUL KING BROOK
Bounty: 383 million berries.
BOUNTY: 383 MILLION BERRIES
Thank you!
What the...
SHIPWRIGHT, CYBORG FRANKY
Shipwright, Cyborg Franky.
Bounty: 394 million berries.
BOUNTY: 394 MILLION BERRIES
Screw them! Where am I?!
SNIPER, GOD USOPP
Sniper, God Usopp.
Bounty: 500 million berries.
BOUNTY: 500 MILLION BERRIES
That's enough!
I don't want it to go up anymore!
I'm not a pet!
Raise my bounty more!
Here.
Cheer up.
Chopper.
ARCHAEOLOGIST, DEMON CHILD NICO ROBIN
Archaeologist, Demon Child Nico Robin.
Bounty: 930 million berries.
BOUNTY: 930 MILLION BERRIES
Thanks, Robin!
My bounty has increased a lot!
COOK, BLACK-LEG SANJI
Cook, Black-Leg Sanji.
Bounty: 1 billion 32 million berries.
BOUNTY: 1 BILLION 32 MILLION BERRIES
Jimbei, here's yours.
What an honor.
They recognized me
as a member of the Straw Hats.
Of course, they did.
You made quite a stir.
What?!
HELMSMAN, "FIRST SON OF THE SEA" JIMBEI
Helmsman, "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
Bounty: 1 billion 100 million berries.
BOUNTY: 1 BILLION 100 MILLION BERRIES
SWORDSMAN, PIRATE HUNTER ZORO
Swordsman, Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Bounty: 1 billion 111 million berries.
BOUNTY: 1 BILLION 111 MILLION BERRIES
Why am I lower than him?!
1.1 BILLION     1.111 BILLION
1.032 BILLION
Are you okay, Sanji?
What's wrong?
Oh yeah, Jimbei...
You're also...
1 BILLION 111 MILLION
Don't worry, Jimbei.
About this fourth-placer.
Who did you call a "fourth-placer"?!
Don't mouth off to second-place!
--Shut up, Mosshead!
--Calm down!
I'm sorry...
Please let me out...
SENIOR CAPTAIN, EMPEROR OF THE SEA
STRAW HAT LUFFY
Senior captain and an Emperor of the Sea,
Straw Hat Luffy.
Bounty: 3 billion berries.
BOUNTY: 3 BILLION BERRIES
Stop it, you two!
I'm hungry...
EMPTEE BLUFFS ISLAND, NEW WORLD
--Did you see them?
--Yeah, I did!
--It was really them!
--Man!
That was the world's greatest swordsman?!
--I'm scared!
--Gee!
When the Seven Warlords were abolished
and we were surrounded by the Navy ships,
I thought we were finished...
Because of our great Chairman Buggy,
it turned out to be like this...
Wait a minute!
Take anything you want except for my life!
Hey, please!
I'll do anything!
I'll even lick your shoes! Please!
EMPEROR OF THE SEA
BUGGY THE GENIUS JESTER
FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Cross Guild was originally
gonna be founded by me and Hawkeye.
FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Why are you the boss? Hmm, Buggy?
Well, I can only say "I'm really sorry"!
Or, "Never mind"...
You're the first and last person who rose to
Emperor of the Sea just by saying sorry.
It sets a bad example
if we keep you alive.
The word "humiliation" isn't enough
to express how I feel.
Don't kill me...
That's impossible.
Stop, stop, stop! Stop!
Well, well...
Boss!
I'm so happy to serve you
after a long time!
FORMER BAROQUE WORKS AGENT
(CROCODILE'S SUBORDINATE)
You bastard!
Are you betraying me, Galdino?!
I don't remember becoming
your subordinate, Buggy!
What a douche!
Call me whatever you want!
Chairman is finished.
What should we do now?
I'll serve Crocodile!
It's a cold world we live in.
You pushed your luck too far!
--Hey! You! Stop it!
--Here! Here!
You've lost your privilege
as a Warlord of the Sea, Mihawk!
GLOOM ISLAND
What do you want, Crocodile?
This island is surrounded by the Navy
as we speak.
No wonder.
In the last Reverie, the Seven Warlords
forfeited all their rights,
and their connections
with the World Government were cut off.
That means you're just a pirate now.
Only in times like this
does the Navy move quickly.
You're partly to blame for what happened.
That was a long time ago...
It's troublesome,
but I have to relocate myself.
Come here, then.
That doesn't sound so bad, right?
If we team up together, we'll be
an organization the Navy can't ignore.
You were once known
as the Navy Hunter.
You and I are the same...
...in that we don't trust others.
What does he want?! I'm so scared!
Why am I constantly plagued by misfortune?
Hurry up!
--Hustle!
--What are you doing?!
--Captain Buggy!
--Captain!
Captain Buggy!
What's the matter?! Fight!
Are you scared of the Navy?!
These fools!
I'm getting ready to sneak away here!
Captain!
The warships surrounding the island
are getting attacked!
They're sinking one after another!
You mean the Navy?!
What?!
Who's helping us?!
It's Crocodile!
Outta my way.
Shoot, shoot!
Sables!
So the rumor that Crocodile
is Chairman Buggy's henchman was true!
He came to rescue us
at the risk of his life!
Because of our great Chairman Buggy!
I see... That's Crocodile!
He came to collect my huge debt to him!
What should I do?
I don't have money to pay him back!
He's scarier than the Navy!
I know you.
I thought you'd flee without paying me back.
He got that right!
Well...
Buggy's Delivery
may look like it's doing well,
but there's a lot of mouths to feed!
And my biggest earners, the giants,
all quit recently...
If you can't pay,
we can sell you into slavery.
Don't say such a horrible thing!
We broke out of Impel Down together!
Cro-chan!
I lent you money for that sake,
but if you can't pay,
you'll have to take full responsibility.
Responsibility?
I'm gonna found a new company,
so I need money now.
N-N-N-No...
Then...
...l-let me help with that business!
This former Warlord of the Sea...
...will serve under you!
Yeah?
I'll work off my debt!
The establishment of a company
must be flashy!
We have various human resources!
Advertising design.
Printing.
Transportation!
You can boss us around!
We'll work for free!
Now, is this the flyer you distributed?
You're standing out...
President.
N-No...
That's not what I intended to do!
If it's not deliberate, then what?!
I-It really wasn't my intention!
My staff respect me too much!
I was surprised, too!
Chairman!
I made a good one!
Hey, what the hell is that?!
I made Chairman look the coolest!
What?!
You haven't shown this
to anyone yet, right?
--We've already...
--...distributed it to the world!
What?!
Buggy is the mastermind of
the Impel Down prison break,
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
and formerly a crewmember of
the King of the Pirates.
He was once on equal footing
with the Emperor of the Sea, Red-Haired.
He's so well-liked that Crocodile
came to his aid at Emptee Bluffs Island.
The tie between Crocodile and Mihawk
was confirmed by wiretapping.
Many shady organizations have already
invested in "Navy soldier hunting."
In view of the trend towards insurgency
in the world,
Cross Guild is a significant threat to us.
What are the bounties of those three?
The former Warlord of the Sea,
Sir Crocodile!
His Logia-type Devil Fruit power
is still formidable.
And he also has a sharp intellect
and an ability to lead.
So his bounty is 1 billion 965 million berries!
Hawkeye Mihawk!
The former Warlord exceeds
the Emperor of the Sea Red-Haired at swordplay.
As the greatest swordsman in the world,
his bounty is...
...3 billion 590 million berries!
And Buggy the Genius Jester!
Not just his record that I mentioned,
but more importantly,
he has the other two under control...
So his bounty is
3 billion 189 million berries!
Just like Straw Hat Luffy,
we consider him to be a new emperor,
and grade him as a security risk
to the World Government!
And...
...you're an Emperor of the Sea?
You've made quite a name for yourself...
Clown...
I'm really sorry! So sorry!
I'll lick your shoes!
Shut up!
But on the other hand,
it's not a bad idea to have him
as our figurehead.
I, at least,
would rather live peacefully
than become an Emperor of the Sea.
You sure?
Let him take the heat,
and we can get rid of him
whenever we want.
You're right.
Guys!
To prepare for the looming new era,
we founded Cross Guild!
Let me introduce the executives!
First...
Sir Crocodile!
And...
Hawkeye Mihawk!
--Crocodile!
--Mihawk-sama!
We'll follow you!
Sir Crocodile!
All right, guys!
Let's do it in a flashy way!
Chairman Buggy is crying!
We're moved to tears, too!
What's gonna happen to my life?!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
Navy Captain Koby invades,
leading new Pacifistas.
Seizing on the confusion, the Emperor of the Sea
Blackbeard comes to raid.
Pirate Empress Hancock fights back.
Who will win this three-way struggle,
where darkness and beauty intermingle?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The War on the Island of Women!
A Case Involving Koby the Hero"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!