Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
That sword Shusui that you had was
the Land of Wano's stolen treasure!
When it was taken away,
the whole tragedy began!
What god?
You blasphemer!
Stop fighting!
What are a samurai and a monk fighting for
in the remote countryside like this?
Kawa... matsu...
Kawamatsu?! Is that you?!
"Hiyori's Confession!
A Reunion at Bandit's Bridge!"
K-Kaido-san!
--Please stop, Kaido-san!
--The island can't take it anymore!
Shut up! That's enough!
Sorry!
I got you!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
Thunder Bagua!
When will that battle end?!
We should really flee to the mainland!
Hey, guys!
How could you fools take cover
when your boss is fighting?
You damn cowards!
Queen-san?! When did you get here?!
You ran away, too?!
N-No way...
Anyway, have you heard from Udon?
No... We can't reach them via Smail yet...
All right!
I'll go there to check if everything's okay!
You just wanna get out of here, Queen-sama!
That's not fair!
No! I'm just gonna go check!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Give it to me!
--Oh, okay!
Clank!
Yo, this is Queen!
Queen!
This is Chief Warden Babanuki from Udon!
Oh, so now the Smails have been restored.
Yes! Just now!
I brought too many men here.
If you're short-handed, we can make our way there!
He's acting cool
but looking for an excuse to flee!
No, that's not necessary
for the time being.
Rejected!
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain Kid,
and the other hoodlums
are all quietly behind bars.
I see...
I just called you to say
everything's okay here...
I wish that weren't the case!
Queen-sama!
That's all from me.
Clank.
Was that okay, Master-sama?!
Uh-huh! Thank you!
Good boy!
Yes!
What sorcery!
She tamed her enemy with a millet dumpling!
Seems like it works on animals
and animal power-users!
Damn!
You bastards!
Do you think you can get away with this?!
I'll get you no matter what!
You are spunky even under restraint.
Tama! Let him eat your dumpling!
The one you gave to Horselina!
What?!
But I don't know if it'll work
like it did at that time...
Just try it!
O-Okay!
Dumpling? What are you talking about?
You'll see!
If you insist...
Kibi Dango!
Oh?! She really created
a dumpling from her cheek!
Here! T-Try it, it's delicious...
What did you say, you brat?!
What do you want?!
I'm scared!
You're fine.
Master-sama!
Don't hesitate to ask for anything!
W-What the?!
Yes! It worked!
Okay, shake hands!
Yes, ma'am!
Good, good. You're a good boy!
Otama-chan's ability...
If we make good use of it, I think it'll come in handy!
This is fun!
What an honor! Master-sama!
It all went well!
Thanks to you, Caribou!
Yeah, that's right!
Thanks to me!
I gobbled up their Boss Snail,
and cut their communications!
Now, the enemies outside think that
thousands of us prisoners are just sitting quietly in our cells!
On the day of the great battle,
I'm sure they'll be dumbfounded!
Please don't forget my contributions!
You owe me!
I know!
All right! Now we can contact
Kin'emon and the others!
Chopperemon-dono!
By all means, we will repay our debt to you
even if it costs us our lives!
Don't mention it...
That virus wasn't so hard to defeat.
And samurai tend to take repaying debts too seriously,
so forget it.
W-Well, this is great!
Even Luffytaro has fully...
Let's do it, guys!
Yeah!
--Luffytaro-san!
--You're the man!
--We can do it!
--I'll follow you!
...regained his health and charisma!
Merely because Momonosuke-sama brought him here,
he earned the people's trust!
It is no mistake!
He has not changed a bit...
Long time no see...
Boss Hyogoro!
Oh! Look at them!
Blood-writing Ohmasa!
OHMASA, UDON
Split-Hat Tsunagoro!
TSUNAGORO, HAKUMAI
OCHO, RINGO
Ocho the Bottle Gourd!
Snake-Eyes Yatappe!
YATAPPE, KIBI
Those are the bosses from different regions!
I did not know they were here!
I did not think that I could survive
to serve you again!
I am so glad that you are all alive!
We are not worthy to benefit
from your kindness!
It is like having to take
a crap after a bath!
That is right!
So true.
They're so weird!
Old man, you got high-and-mighty with them, too!
"Old man"?!
Oh, no!
--Tearing nails!
--Cutting off fingers!
Ripping off ears!
Take the consequences, you fool!
How many should we take?!
Boss, give us an order!
Stop it! That man saved my life!
We will lose no time in scraping together
any rebels that are still hiding across the country.
--Mm-hm. I am counting on you!
--Yes, sir!
You escaped death, young man...
Be careful hereafter.
Shut up, you idiots!
Wow! He's got some nerve to squarely face
the regional bosses!
I'll follow you for the rest
of my life, Luffytaro-san!
Yeah, follow me! I'll save this country!
KIBI
Oh, my!
I thought so! The man from Kuri
who made off with the blueprints in the end...
...was you!
I have been looking for these!
The blueprints of Kaido's mansion on Onigashima!
Oh, I put Franosuke-dono
through a lot of trouble.
But now we can plan what to do
in the enemy's territory!
You are the best!
Were you that attentive before?
Stop saying that, doggie!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Is that Raizo? How is everything?
Have you managed to rescue Luffytaro-dono?!
It is far better than that.
It's a long story, but we gathered a number of warriors.
Roughly...
Th-Thirty-five hundred?!
That is so many!
So you safely rescued Luffy-dono!
And you even found and freed Kawamatsu?!
Oh, Kawamatsu was caught by them, too?!
On top of that,
you occupied the labor camp?!
You did far more than saving Luffy-kun!
Let's go! To Onigashima!
Yeah!
We are expecting to have more warriors
to join us!
But there is one problem
you need to know!
There are a number of weapons factories
in the Land of Wano,
but almost all their products are
war machines meant for export!
Samurai like to use
swords and spears the most!
Currently, those are tough to get
since carrying weapons is banned by Orochi!
If we do not have enough weapons for all the rebels,
we will not stand a chance!
Okay. I understand.
That is quite serious.
Swords, huh?
We made some progress, too,
but I will fill you in later!
To gauge on our combat preparedness,
I am going to go to Amigasa Village,
and will work from there!
Raizo! Give me the details
of your group later!
--I got it!
--Clank.
Now, let's go!
Y-You are...
I cannot believe this...
Is it really you?!
Kawamatsu!
What?
No way...
Do not tell me... you are...
Kawamatsu!
I never imagined getting to see you
in a place like this!
More than anything else,
I am so happy that you are alive and well!
Hiyori-sama!
Oh, yeah. She said she was raised by a kappa
after her parents died...
I am sorry.
I got scared and ran away at that time...
Even if it was just a scrap,
you always gave me any food you found...
I am still half-fledged...
Kawamatsu...
I could not watch you wasting away
year after year.
I knew you could easily survive
by yourself...
I was thinking, "What am I going to do
if Kawamatsu dies because of me?"
Your Majesty!
This is...
Kawamatsu, I'm sorry!
If nothing is done, you'll die soon!
I got scared and I... ran away!
"Dear Kawamatsu,
Thank you for everything.
DEAR KAWAMATSU, THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
I'LL BE FINE. HIYORI
I'll be fine. Hiyori."
What?!
H-Hiyori-sama!
Hiyori-sama!
Your Majesty!
BATHHOUSE
Listen! I washed my hair by myself today!
I closed my eyes like this...
Your Majesty...
She is not here...
Hiyori-sama!
Hiyori-sama! Where did she go?!
Hiyori-sama...
Your Majesty... Where did you go?
Your Majesty...
Hiyori-sama!
I am sorry... I am really sorry...
How kind of you! So that is why you left!
Thanks to you, I put on a lot of weight!
K-Kawamatsu-sama...
Who is it?!
We're here to get revenge, Gyukimaru!
How dare you rip off tons of weapons from us!
We'll take them all back!
I bet you're paralyzed!
It's a magnum, enough to hunt savage animals!
--Hiyori-sama! Hide behind the tree!
--Okay!
--Hm? Are they his associates?!
--It doesn't matter! Just shoot them all to death!
Go to hell!
Kappa Style!
Two-Sword Style!
River of Retribution!
RIVER OF RETRIBUTION
Rhino Cycle!
RHINO CYCLE
Kawamatsu-sama!
Kawamatsu!
Are you okay, Hiyori-sama?
Kawamatsu-sama...
Hey, wait! Are you running away again?!
Damn you! Give me back my Shusui!
Kawamatsu-sama!
I am so glad!
He is alive!
Kawamatsu seizes weapons
for the warriors they allied with after conquering Udon!
Meanwhile, Hiyori tells Zoro
about the legendary sword used by Kozuki Oden,
only weapon that ever injured Kaido!
The past and the present flow together
to create the potential for new power!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Its Name is Enma! Oden's Great Swords!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!