Wealth, fame, power...
Gol D. Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has been verified,
it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
"Overwhelming Strength!
The Straw Hats Come Together!"
Stop me!
That's Mama!
No way.
I'm sure it is!
Whoa-whoa,
what happened to the ogre extermination-yoi?
Mama?!
Sasaki-sama, I can't believe you got tied up.
So dumb, right?
I never expected to be fooled by Kyoshiro,
my alleged best friend.
Now, what happened to this?
Well, Big Mom let loose in the dome...
And her attack made it out here?!
What monstrous power.
Well, thanks to that, I got released...
Anyway, I can't believe
Kyoshiro was one of Oden's retainers.
I'm not interested in the Land of Wano's history...
But he must pay a heavy price for betraying me.
Charge!
We're gonna stop them!
Exterminate the Minks!
We Minks have a strong will!
We'll take you-gara down!
Do your worst!
This will finish you off!
I can't take it anymore!
Thank you for fighting until this point.
We will take care of the rest!
Wait.
Kin'emon.
Dog! Cat!
Let us handle this.
Yeah.
You-gara guys!
We'll take over!
How fast!
Catch him!
Oh, I see the sky.
Okay, I think I can get up there from here.
Don't move!
Queen-sama!
Shut up. I'm on a break.
It's Straw Hat!
What?! Straw Hat?!
And he isn't alone?!
Hey, Zoro!
Oh, Luffy! Where are you going?
Up where Kaido is.
I'll come with you.
I won't let you guys go!
What's that giant creature down there?!
All right!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
I can get there!
Kaido's up there?
Yeah, Kin'emon and the others
are all fighting up there, too!
We're almost there!
Dammit!
I won't let you go, you fools!
I won't let you in this area!
We'll never be able to get up there!
Security's very tight!
Get out of my way!
Screw you!
Straw hat man!
The big one is back for more.
--Let's fight!
--Yeah!
Leave it to me!
Come on, Brachio Tank!
I'm Commander Chopper!
I'm Driver Usopp!
To reunite with the Black Rhino bike,
we went through so many hard battles...
...and we just arrived at this promised hill now!
Good job! Let's start combining!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Let's do it!
Combining formation!
Black Rhino, stand by!
Brachio Head, change!
Sorry! This robot is a single seater.
What?!
That's unacceptable!
Are they...
Usohachi-san! Chopperemon-san!
Are you okay?!
Thank you for sacrificing yourselves for us
at the Pleasure Hall!
Guys, put that aside for now...
For now!
And pay attention to the combination!
The combination!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
IRON PIRATE GENERAL FRANKY
What?! Is that a mechanical warrior?!
Great Djinn-sama!
Thank you, thank you!
Here I go!
Franky Cannon!
I knew you were gonna shoot it yourself!
Yourself!
Super!
Jaki has been taken down!
We're in trouble!
Let's just get away from here!
You're right!
Where's Momo?
I guess he got away...
That bird brain...
He almost punched a hole through my stomach!
This suit is annoyingly solid...
Damn Germa!
The enemies keep coming!
Even if Jaki has been taken down...
We still got Goki and Juki!
Here they come! Buck up, guys!
The enemies are right in front of us!
Straw hat man?!
Gear Two!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Straw Hat Luffy.
Bounty: 1.5 billion berries.
Whoa-whoa, he's coming all by himself!
Is he stupid?!
One-Sword Style!
360-Pound Phoenix!
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Bounty: 320 million berries.
Commander Chopper,
we got to do it, too!
Mm-hm!
It's close combat!
Special Attack Green Star!
Skull Blast Grass!
It's an exclusive version for this occasion!
God Usopp.
Bounty: 200 million berries.
You...
Chopper the Cotton Candy Lover.
Bounty: 100 berries.
Mil Fleurs, Gigantesco Mano!
Stomp!
You have to pay attention!
Clutch!
Demon Child Nico Robin.
Bounty: 130 million berries.
Three-pace Hum...
...Notch Slash.
You've been cut!
Soul King Brook.
Bounty: 83 million berries.
She's a hot chick!
No! I can't stand pests!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Don't mess with me!
Cat Burglar Nami.
Bounty: 66 million berries.
Nami-san! I'm coming to help!
Damn!
Poele A Frire Spectre!
Black-Leg Sanji.
Bounty: 330 million berries.
Everyone's quite strong!
As a newcomer, I have to keep up!
Cut the crap! You're a mere Fish-Man!
Oh, no. I shouldn't have overdone it like that.
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
Bounty: 438 million berries.
This is the "marauder's sword"!
Franken!
General Watch-Your-Step!
How's that?!
Cyborg Franky.
Bounty: 94 million berries.
You just took down some weaklings.
Don't flatter yourselves!
We still have a numerical advantage!
Oh, I'm sorry!
This situation kind of tickles my funny bone.
We still got a bunch of enemies around us!
But for some reason,
I don't feel like we're gonna lose.
--You're right!
--Yeah, me neither!
It's strange. Why do we feel this way?
It's obvious, isn't it?!
Because the straw hat man is with us!
I thought I could just get there by jumping.
Damn. It's not that easy.
I'll come with you.
Let's just get to the top!
What a pain.
Are they all capable of flying?
If we tear off their wings,
they're just caterpillars.
The way you put it
creeps me out as always!
So they're the Lead Performers
that everyone's talking about.
They look strong,
but our captain's stronger!
Yeah!
As a navigator, my duty is to help the captain
get where he wants to go!
Super count on me!
This General Franky'll clear the way for you!
Let's go, Captain!
Yeah! Let's do it one more time! Ready?!
Everyone! I'll leave the rest to you!
Back us up!
I'm gonna go...
...take down Kaido!
While Luffy and the others are making big strides,
restlessness starts prevailing among the Tobi Roppo.
A daring cur looking to get promoted
rises against the Lead Performer, Queen!
A blade to supplant his superior closes in on Queen,
who is preoccupied with the enemy raid!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Risky Invitation! A Plot to Eliminate Queen!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!