iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
"Yamato's Past!
The Man Who Came for an Emperor of the Sea!"
--He went that way!
--Hey, wait!
BANQUET HALL, THIRD FLOOR, INSIDE THE CASTLE
When a man makes up his mind,
don't try to hold him back!
He's walking out on us...
Hey, stop!
Wait a minute!
Even if you tell me to wait,
I'm sorry, but I can't do that!
Damn! What's this?!
Untie me!
Stop fighting like that...
Bad boy... Don't try to run.
Hey, gentleman...
You said you loved me.
BLACK MARIA - A MEMBER OF THE TOBI ROPPO
SPIDER-SPIDER FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
ROSAMYGALE GRAUVOGELI MODEL
Stay here forever. You'll be my pet.
Don't be silly! I...
I gotta go!
But...
Everywhere...
...I look...
Women, women, women!
Is this...
...heaven?
He's got to be out of his mind.
You're so cute. As a reward for that,
I'm gonna open heaven's door for you.
Oh, no!
This is something extra!
FOURTH FLOOR, INSIDE THE CASTLE
Stop, Straw Hat!
You'll get hurt if you
don't get out of the way!
CAT
Straw Hat went ahead.
It's gonna give Kaido-san trouble...
Could you stop...
...bullying my subordinates?
WHO'S-WHO - A MEMBER OF THE TOBI ROPPO
CAT-CAT FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
SAVER-TOOTHED TIGER MODEL
You're a former Warlord of the Sea,
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
How can you be so childish?
I'm the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Can't you use that worthier title instead?
Oh, my bad.
I've seen you at one point
when you were a Warlord...
What?
Sometimes people completely
change their positions.
So maybe I used to be on your side.
Jimbei.
Well, forget it.
Who are you?
Who knows? I wonder who I am.
If I take off your mask,
I might be able to recognize you.
That won't happen.
There you go.
FORBIDDEN STOREHOUSE, INSIDE THE DOME
Thank you.
W-Why are you laughing?
Oh, sorry.
This brings me back...
...the memory of the wounds
that I inflicted on him...
Inflicted wounds?
So you fought and beat him?
No...
I lost.
But it didn't matter if I had won or lost.
You see,
the meaning of life...
It was him, without a doubt,
who taught me that...
It was Ace.
The place they said children
were being held...
...must be that island, it seems.
We're finally here.
I'm gonna fight you...
Kaido!
Hey, let's go.
I thought the Onigashima gate guards
would be stronger.
What a letdown.
Hey, don't lower your guard.
Our enemy is that infamous Emperor of the Sea.
Yeah, I know.
What? No one's here?
There are intruders!
Kaido is the only one we need to see!
Ace!
Guys, go save the children while you can!
--Got it!
--Leave it to us!
He's persistent!
Who are you?! State your name!
You first!
I'm Ace!
I'm here to take Kaido's head!
I found them! Come here!
Don't be scared. We're here to save you all.
Come on, let's go.
You're strong.
Ace!
All the children are okay!
But our target, Kaido,
is nowhere to be found!
What?!
Father and the others went on an expedition.
Right now,
not a single officer is here!
Father?!
What?!
So she's Kaido's daughter?!
I'm Yamato!
I think we've had enough of this rampage!
If you have time to wonder who I am,
get out of here now,
and bring them back to their families!
We'll do so.
But is it okay for you to let us go?
I have no obligation to protect this island.
First of all, I hate seeing them
kidnapping such little children!
Did you hear what she said?
If Kaido isn't here, there's no point in us staying.
Let's go back!
All right, let's go back to the Land of Wano.
Your families are waiting for you!
What a relief!
I'm indebted to you for the rest of my life!
Don't mention it.
More importantly,
show your families that you're fine.
Thank you so much! Thank you!
You sure about it, Ace?
We'll go back to the mainland without you.
Yeah, look after them.
I'll catch up to you later.
I'm not convinced that such a strong person
isn't a captain or anything...
I'll settle this!
I was bored anyway...
I'll fight you!
Fire Fist!
Why... Why aren't you going out to the sea
if you're so strong?!
I want to, but I can't...
You'll never be able to
understand my feelings!
What?!
The reason I stay here
without going out to the sea...
It's all his fault.
My father...
Kaido!
It's all his fault...
I can't believe he's my father...
It's all your father's fault?
Are you making excuses?
You can't choose your parents, Yamato!
Gol D. Roger?
You mean Gold Roger?
Did you ask me if I know him?
Don't you realize why there is so much destruction
in the world caused by pirates?
It's all Roger's fault!
His fault?
I heard that right before his execution,
he bullshited about this great treasure thing...
...causing the idiot pirates who believed him
to run wild.
--He should've never been born in the first place!
--He was just a worthless bastard!
He's such a nuisance - living or dead!
Roger?
Don't mention the name that makes me sick, brat!
It's ruining my drink! Go away!
What are you looking at?!
What do you think you're doing?!
You little shit!
Hey, Ace?
I heard that you're out of control these days.
--Old man.
--Huh?
Do you think...
...that I deserved to be born?
That's something...
...you'll see as you live.
You can't...
...choose your parents, Yamato.
Shut up! You don't have to tell me that!
You sure?
As long as he's my father,
I don't have freedom!
The only thing I have...
I-It's heavy...
Why are you cuffing me?!
Because you're thinking about the wrong things.
You don't even have one good reason to leave this island!
If you're my son, become stronger for me!
Don't think about anything else!
No... Uncuff me!
Father!
I've been confined on this damn island
and put in handcuffs
which will explode if I step out.
I have no choice
but to stay here for my entire life.
Just because I was born
to that asshole named Kaido...
Even though handcuffs were unavoidable,
if you hate your father so much,
why are you letting them chain your heart?!
Did you become stronger
to protect your father?
Or to let off some steam
by fighting someone like me?
No! You became stronger for yourself!
Yamato!
What do you really wanna do?!
Think about it.
Don't you have the answer...
...deep, deep inside of your heart?
Inside of my heart...
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
I-I...
I...
What do you really wanna do?!
You don't even have one good reason
to leave this island!
I admit...
I was holding myself back.
I couldn't help dreaming...
But I couldn't do as I wished.
The explosive handcuffs...
Kaido's son...
An impossible dream...
"I'll be stuck on this damn island."
"I have no choice."
"It's all my father's fault."
That's what I was telling myself.
But I now realize.
I wanna sail out to the sea
and go on an adventure!
I wanna live freely like Oden!
To the sea...
Getting off this crappy island...
I wanna live freely!
That's it, Yamato!
--That's how it should be.
--What?
You know what to do now.
Yeah!
I can't believe I ended up like this
with someone who came to kill my father.
So you love your father.
No way!
Gee! You keep attacking my soft point.
Sorry, sorry.
Are you really sorry?
Hey, Ace.
Tell me.
About you and your adventure...
About the world...
About anything and everything.
All right.
But it's gonna take a while,
so get ready for it.
WISHFUL MOON
SNOW MOON
And he came home in tatters!
When we were young,
he really caused me a lot of trouble!
--Your brother's so interesting!
--Yeah, isn't he?!
Hey, how are things on the outside?!
Are there many young people rising to fame?!
Young ones? Let's see...
Everyone's talking about Caven-something.
Heh!
Well, I'm in a class of my own,
but I heard some dangerous guys
are running wild in each sea.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Kid in the South Blue and...
...Law in the north and Bege in the west.
But the toughest one
will come out to the sea in a few years...
It's my brother!
He'll be extremely powerful!
How many times
do you have to mention your brother?
--Who cares? Just listen!
--Ow, ow, ow!
--You... That hurts!
--Hey, stop!
What an awesome friend...
Yeah. The truth is I'm the one
who broke this dragon statue first.
But he said,
"This is a warning from me to Kaido
that I'll come back again!"
I see...
I did not know there was a pirate
who tried to save the Land of Wano...
That made my father angry,
but in the end, he never met Ace.
--Wait...
--Your father?
Didn't I say Kaido is my father?
Hey, don't be so scared!
Oh, but I hate him!
I told you I'm Oden, right?!
That confuses us even more!
You don't have to be scared.
I hate Kaido!
I dreamed of the sea and an adventure,
so I became Oden who lived freely!
We understand most of it, sir.
We appreciate your treatment!
Stop being so formal and come here!
Sir, if you insist...
Stop it!
But Yamato,
where is the man
who tried to save the Land of Wano now?!
Ace died two years ago.
Otama, you knew Ace?
Yes, we were so close!
I've been trying to become a kunoichi
believing in Ace,
but Big Bro Luffy insensitively said...
Ace died.
He said it to me out of the blue
and it made me so sad.
Oh, I'm sorry. That's what he's like.
But Otama, Luffy's been
through a lot of pain, too.
--When that happened...
--What?
We couldn't do anything
at that time, either...
Luffy lost Ace right in front of his eyes!
I see. He is no longer in this world.
Then, Yamato...
But...
...I was waiting for his brother.
With...
...Straw Hat Luffy who inherited Ace's will,
I can...
Damn you, Straw Hat!
Zoro and Marco work together
to face the Lead Performer's fierce attacks.
To the top of the pirate world with Luffy!
With that unwavering belief, Zoro charges.
Marco sees in his bravery
the image of the comrade he swore allegiance to.
Even if he'll never see him,
their bond will last forever!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Marco's Tears! The Bond of the Whitebeard Pirates!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!