Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Here I come!
In various parts of Onigashima,
heading towards the Flower Capital,
fierce battles are being fought.
That was a good one!
You got much stronger, Yamato!
Straw Hat won't come back!
Your efforts are futile!
Luffy will come back!
Kaido!
You can't drive me to despair anymore!
All I see is hope now!
Meanwhile, a giant dragon appears
in front of Luffy and the others at Tokage Port.
Are you Momo?
Indeed.
--That's the brat from earlier?!
--What's this all about?!
What?!
Let's go, Momo!
To take back the Land of Wano!
Yeah!
"For the Future!
Yamato and the Great Swordsmen's Pledge"
Okay!
Let's go!
Good, Momo!
Oh, it's so high!
High?
I-It is very high...
Do not look... Do not look down!
Oh, I'm flying!
What? Flying?
It is very high! I'm scared!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
W-W-What are you doing?!
Calm down, Momo!
Huh?
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn! We fell!
Kaido!
Narikabura Arrow!
Vajra Arrow!
You have to understand already...
...that you...
...can't become Oden!
You've always tried to kill me!
Yeah, I have.
This isn't a family quarrel.
If you wanna identify yourself as Oden,
you gotta be prepared for a war.
This isn't a game!
Yamato!
Admiring someone...
...is a sin?!
I...
...love Oden!
ONIGASHIMA, TWENTY YEARS AGO
Ogre Princess-sama!
Stop Ogre Princess-sama already!
Get out of my way!
I'm gonna protect the Land of Wano!
Open the borders of the Land of Wano!
How savage!
She's been like that for a week now!
Don't be scared!
Even though Kaido-san's blood is
running through her veins, she's just a child!
Stop her by force!
Oh yeah?
Stop me if you can!
Stop fighting already!
Yamato-sama!
No!
I'm...
...Oden!
What just happened?
She took them down without touching them.
Catch her!
I'm sorry, Kaido-san...
Ogre Princess-sama didn't stop rampaging,
so we had no choice but to restrain her...
Did you do this?
Yamato.
No! I'm Oden!
I...
...am Oden!
Answer my question.
Did you do this?
I don't know...
They collapsed on their own...
Hey, unchain me, Father!
I'm starving to death!
I see. It's the Color of the Supreme King.
You show promise.
Color of the Supreme King?
But if you wanna call yourself Oden,
then die.
--Yamato.
--What?
What?!
Why?! Why are you doing this to me?!
Give me a meal! Father!
Hey, what are you doing?!
I give you one month.
Why don't you cool your head in here?
Wait! How could you leave me
in this dark place?!
A-A month?
Even though Ogre Princess-sama
is tough, she'll die!
Besides, there are vicious samurai
from the Land of Wano in there...
Samurai-san from the Land of Wano?
Kaido-san! I think...
Great swordsmen of the Land of Wano!
Just like that idiot over there,
I give you one month.
Cool down and think.
If you change your mind,
shout through the air hole in the ceiling.
If you're gonna join my army,
I'll get you out of there.
How many days have you guys gone
without food?
Hey! Bring food!
But...
...just for one person.
A swordsman needs his sword, right?
Father!
I'm Kaido's child!
I know they have an ill-feeling towards me!
If you give them swords,
they'll kill me right away!
What are you talking about?
I thought you were Oden.
Think about the meaning of that name.
Please...
Hey.
About what Kaido-san said earlier...
Don't tell me the great swordsmen
of the Land of Wano are...
Yeah, that's right.
After the public execution
of Kozuki Oden the other day,
Daimyos from all the regions stood up.
The most savage ones among them...
That's who they are.
Although I'm Oden...
I'm also the son of Kaido,
who killed Oden.
I know the Samurai-san won't like me!
Father wants us
to fight each other to the death!
Over a meal!
No, before that...
They'll kill me!
What?
A bug?
Eat it.
What?
What? What?!
Go nuts.
Samurai don't get hungry...
He's right. We don't get hungry.
A-Are you sure?!
I...
I'm very...
...hungry!
If you all won't eat it, can I have it?!
Yes, you can.
You were born into a terrible family.
Thank you!
You samurai are so tough!
I can't believe you don't get hungry!
Thank yommm...
Sammmurai-san...
I'll nev'r forget mmm...
the taste of this mmmeal!
Thanks for the meal!
Hey!
Can I become a samurai
even though I get hungry?
I wanna be a strong and cool samurai!
Is he gonna kill me?!
Hands in the air.
Y-Yes, sir!
Keep your cool.
You're Kozuki Oden, right?
No! I'm Oden!
I...
...am Oden!
We were listening.
We love that man, too.
What?! Are you people his friends?!
Yeah, kind of.
Um... Um...
What's your name?!
Asking a defeated samurai his name?
Just call me So-and-So.
So-and-So...
You have a high aptitude!
Come to think of it,
Oden was strong since he was little, too!
When he was a child like you,
he got into a melee at a gambling parlor.
Oh yeah?!
Yeah. I'm sure
you'll become stronger, too.
But...
...you have to pay attention
when you're fighting.
Yes, sir!
All right! One more time!
Bring it on!
Hey.
I need to ask you
So-and-So people a favor...
I wanna read this journal...
ODEN'S TRAVELS
...but there are difficult kanji...
Oden's journey log?!
Where did you get it?!
I happened to find this
at the foot of Oden Castle...
I'm begging you, So-and-So people!
Teach me how to read them!
"The world is made up of four seas
and one long strip of sea.
And the world is round
like a rice cake ball.
Very strange!"
Please! Just for a year will do.
Let me borrow Oden!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime request!
With him,
I'm sure I can get to the Final Island!
Screw you!
Roger! Are you trying to
take my family member away from me?!
White-Kichi-chan! I wanna go!
Please allow me to go!
I wanna see the Final Island
that he talked about!
The second chapter
of my life as a pirate...
A new adventure began!
White-Kichi-chan is great,
but Roger has incalculable depth, too.
The Log Pose is pointing at the sky...
Is it broken?
It's not... Let's go.
Go where?
To the sky!
The world is big!
There is still so much more to it!
Even Buddha couldn't imagine
that there were people living in the sky!
How is it?
Mm-hm... It's perfect, Oden!
"I made it here. I will guide
this text to the ends of the earth."
I must see it, Roger.
The final chapter of the great adventure
that you're devoting your life to!
Here it is! The last Road Ponegliff!
Now we've got all the Road Ponegliffs...
Let's go, guys! To the Final Island!
Yeah!
The Final Island!
The Roger Pirates finally did it!
The pirate Roger traveled around the world
for the first time in history!
Now there is a conqueror of the sea!
He's the king of the sea!
The King of the Pirates!
The day we reached the Final Island,
we learned everything about the world.
What is the 100-Year Void?
What is the People of the D?
What are the Ancient Weapons?
The Land of Wano was once
connected with the rest of the world.
With the extraordinary treasure
that sat there before our eyes,
at that moment, Roger was...
...laughing.
"More than 20 years into the future,
young, strong pirates who will lead the next era
will come surging into the New World."
If I die...
the ones who'll bring Kaido down are...
"Roger named the Final Island...
...Laugh Tale."
Laugh Tale...
The One Piece!
Oh... It's been about 10 days?
I have no idea
since nothing changes in here.
Yamato... Is your father really going to
let his child die?
At this rate, we may not be able to see the battle
that Oden said would happen in 20 years.
When that happens, I'll fight...
...alongside the Land of Wano...
I'll go out to the sea...
...to become stronger and stronger...
That's reassuring.
Then...
...by not allowing you to die here,
we'll take part in the future war.
What?
Because 20 years is...
...a little too long for us to wait.
Samurai-san!
If you do that, my father will...
We don't want to rot away like this!
We've had no intention of
giving in to Kaido...
...from the beginning!
We'll leave the Land of Wano to you.
Kaido-sama!
They broke out of the Sacred Cave!
Don't let them leave here alive!
There are people who believe in me!
Who accept me!
Why do you want to
take away my freedom?!
And the freedom of the Land of Wano!
Life isn't a series of
simple questions and answers!
You little punk!
Thunder Bagua!
Luffy and a pink dragon blow up a storm!
Yamato confronts his cursed fate.
Momonosuke voluntarily transforms
into a giant dragon!
The tragic but brave resolutions of
those who resist the rule of force
have become a great swell
that will blow and shake Onigashima!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Soars! Revenge Against the King of the Beasts"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!