iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Luffy and Kaido's
full-power attacks collide.
Is there any chance you could beat me?!
As long as I live,
there are infinite chances!
By their torrents of Haki,
the clouds split open,
and it changes the course of the war.
Meanwhile, Momonosuke...
...tries to fly to stop Onigashima that is
heading towards the Flower Capital. However...
M-Momonosuke-kun!
Grab the sky!
Grab?!
Listen, Momonosuke-kun!
You're a dragon now!
You're a giant dragon
soaring through the sky!
I am... a dragon.
I create...
...clouds!
Dragons don't fly!
They create clouds and grab them...
...and run through the sky!
That's what dragons are!
I am flying!
The name of these clouds is...
...Flame Clouds!
"The Situation Has Grown Tense!
The End of Onigashima!"
I did it!
I'm going to keep going!
Mm-hm!
Let's fulfill our promise to Luffy!
We'll stop Onigashima together!
I'll save the Land of Wano!
You bit an Emperor of the Sea!
Is there anything left in the world
that can scare you?!
N...
No!
You can fly!
Yeah!
Go stop...
...Onigashima!
I'll defeat...
...Kaido...
...at any cost!
Let's go...
Let's go, Yamato!
Yeah! I'll come with you!
The moon is beautiful!
Hey, Momonosuke-kun.
When this battle is over,
we gotta have a moon-viewing party.
Falling rocks ahead! They're big!
What?!
Dodge to the left!
Dragons can't turn on a dime!
Good! You're getting used to
being a dragon!
Whoa!
Don't panic!
Just grab the cloud!
Yamato! Rocks are falling
one after another!
Yeah, this isn't just a rockfall!
Momonosuke-kun! Look!
This is an anomaly!
The island's collapsing!
What?!
Is that a problem?!
Don't tell me...
...Kaido's power...
...is weakening!
The Flame Clouds that Kaido created
are unstable,
and they can't support
the cracked bedrock!
Don't die until I kill you this time.
Straw Hat!
The island will continue to collapse!
The battle's gonna get more intense!
Yeah!
So Luffy has the upper hand?!
Yeah, he'll win!
Let's just do our job!
Thank you, Yamato!
I'm honored to protect you!
Momonosuke-kun...
It's hard to do our job now.
The island's collapse
and the falling rocks.
If they rain down on the town,
many people will get hurt!
We must hurry then!
I do not care what happens to me!
I'm not going to let such a dangerous thing
fly to the Flower Capital!
Don't do that! Momonosuke-kun!
I got bigger to stop this island!
No, Momonosuke-kun!
You can't stop it like that!
But we do not have time!
Look! The capital is so close now!
It will reach there
in less than five minutes!
Then, create the Flame Clouds!
With those giant-dragon-like clouds,
Kaido is moving Onigashima!
To push it back, you must create
more powerful Flame Clouds than his!
That is impossible! I cannot do it!
I just learned to fly!
Besides, I would not necessarily have
the same abilities as he does!
But you can create the Flame Clouds!
I'm sure you can do it!
So let's do it!
It's up to us now.
The situation is more serious
than we thought!
Even if it lands as Kaido planned,
there'll be so many casualties
in the capital!
In the worst-case scenario,
if by any chance Kaido runs out of strength,
the Flame Clouds will disappear
and Onigashima will hit the ground!
There are a tremendous amount of
weapons on Onigashima!
And explosives!
Onigashima is like a huge bomb!
It's too close now, there isn't enough time
for the people of the capital to evacuate!
If the island falls,
all our enemies and allies will die!
It's beautiful...
Everyone in the Flower Capital, too?!
What?! Then we must stop Luffy!
You fool!
He's standing on the edge
with everything on his shoulders!
Only he can take down Kaido!
We shouldn't tell him about the situation!
We're gonna get through this crisis
without anyone knowing!
Your silly lizard's laser beam can't hit me!
Three at once!
A series of beams!
Sky Walk!
Gravity means nothing to me!
That was quite a dance!
But not as good as me, a superstar!
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
I can sing and dance, I'm the best!
Power, speed!
And power!
I'm a triple-threat, that's my funk!
And my secret technique is activated!
Hair Attack!
An additional attack is confirmed!
Damn... I took a big hit...
I think some of my ribs got broken...
Not my ribs... Is it my back?!
Maybe my neck?!
The enemy is powerful, makes good prey!
Three-Sword Style!
1,080 Pound Phoenix!
360 Pound Phoenix!
One of your spikes for starters.
Damn you...
Damn you!
What?! Nerves pass through those spikes?
I feel pain.
Pain that can't be wiped away!
I won't allow even a shred of you
to remain on earth!
Is it a dinosaur's power?!
Yes.
That was just a little example.
Get down! King-sama is pissed off!
He's so uptight!
I'm cheerful and happy!
My ass took a serious blow!
Zoro!
What happened to you?!
King the Wildfire...
He's not called
a Lead Performer for nothing.
He's strong...
No surprises.
What's going on on the floor?
It's really a big decisive battle...
Need my help?
No, I don't!
Damn you, King!
Stop attacking randomly!
My ass got cut!
I wish it was your neck.
Pirate Hunter Zoro
damaged King-san's mask!
Yeah, that pisses him off...
No one knows his unmasked face!
What are you looking at?!
Focus on me!
Pay attention!
Vinsmoke Sanji!
"Vinsmoke" isn't necessary!
Dance with me more!
Flying Pan!
I'm a super machinegun!
It never stops! Funk!
It's heavy!
I'll never stop attacking!
Now, show me!
Germa 66's combat suit!
Sanji!
Judge's son!
Let me see it!
You showed the combat suit
when you were fighting against King!
What's that?
Sangoro!
You became invisible at that moment!
That's Judge's scientific acumen!
Now is the time to show the power of the suit
demonstrating your parent-child bond!
You loud-mouthed shitty lizard!
I'm feeling off again...
Wear the suit now, Vinsmoke!
I told you not to call me that!
You don't know my family situation!
I mean they're not even my family!
I won't wear that shit!
Please wear that suit!
I'm beggin' you!
Is that the guy?
Sorry, Franky!
Stay away from me!
All right! Hang in there!
Three-Sword Style!
Imperial...
...Archer!
Ultra Tiger...
...Hunt!
What?!
Wait...
I'm gonna fall!
Two-Sword Style!
Clear Lance!
That was close!
At least kill me by your sword!
I won't forgive you!
I won't forgive you, either!
A scientific disaster that can destroy Sanji!
The monster Queen's killing machine
crumbles his body
and the hellish childhood memory
wrenches his heart!
On the brink of defeat,
when the pain exceeds the limit,
the forbidden door that lies dormant
within him is opened!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji's Mutation ? The Two Arms in Crisis!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!