Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The battles against the Emperors of the Sea
get extremely fierce.
Gum-Gum...
Blast Breath!
...Red Hawk!
Shock Wille!
Punk Clash!
Come take it!
My place as an Emperor of the Sea!
The heat of battle
swirling in every corner.
There are many soldiers ahead!
I gotta go around from the Cave Chamber!
What do you think?
Do you wanna ally with us
and just snatch up the spoils at the end?!
I'm amazed...
Do you think I'd trust a coward like you?
You're not trustworthy, either!
I'm telling you this because
I think it'd be beneficial to you!
You won't have...
...another chance like this!
"For Luffy ?
Sanji and Zoro's Oath"
Hey, think about it, Drake!
This is good for you!
Who could've expected
it'd turn out this way?!
Straw Hat's doing so well!
We must make use of it.
Don't you think so?
You see?!
That formidable Kaido
has never been weakened like this!
This is our first and last big chance
to take him down!
Right after Kaido takes down Straw Hat,
I'll send these guys to fight him!
And then what?!
It won't last two seconds!
What if they get knocked down?!
That's easy!
The last ones standing in line
are me...
...and you!
He'll never have a chance...
I see...
Understood.
I knew you'd understand, Drake!
Now we'll be the real winners in this war!
Don't get me wrong, Apoo...
This is...
...my answer!
Wait, wait! Are you nuts?!
Why should I get sliced by you?!
Do not argue!
Screw you!
Scratch!
Boom!
What a fool...
If he had just nodded,
he wouldn't have had to die.
I already figured out
how your attack works!
It won't work on me.
Stop bluffing!
Your line of attack...
...is hard to see,
but it's surely there!
Activation requires the target's hearing.
And the scope is your eyes!
Don't give it all away!
That doesn't make any difference!
You're cornered
because I have three Numbers here!
Doesn't matter!
To do my duty by Straw Hat,
I need to take you down!
That's bullshit!
I hope you won't regret...
...that you blew your chance...
Huh?
Drake! Apoo! What are a Tobi Roppo member
and an informant doing here?!
That's what I wanna ask you!
Young Master, why are you here?
I thought you were
fighting against Kaido...
I gotta go to the armory...
Yamato...
Yamato?! He is Kaido's enemy!
That fool Drake is useless, so...
Let's switch!
Okay, I gotta go!
Drake, let me...
Wait, wait! Young Master Yamato!
I got some good news for you!
I don't know what it is,
but I don't have time!
I completely cut ties with Kaido!
Don't think of me as your ally!
Really?!
Then I'd like to talk to you even more!
Anyway, I don't have time
to chat with you guys anymore!
Let me go, Animal Kingdom Pirates!
Don't get in my way!
Wait, Yamato. I...
If you don't move...
I'll force my way through!
Hey, wait!
Don't think you can stop me!
Get out of my way already!
I broke away
from the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
I have nothing to do
with Kaido now, either!
What?! Really?!
I'm sorry, Drake! I gotta go!
All right! I gotta get going!
Onigashima and the Flower Capital
are in danger!
Hey!
Damn! Why's everyone so useless?!
They're all so boring!
I really don't wanna die like a dog
after being pushed around!
I have to get Yamato on my side somehow!
What's wrong, Fuga?
Where are you going, Fuga?!
What?!
What is it?!
Fuga!
See you!
Hey, Fuga...
What?!
Where are you going, Fuga?!
Stop!
What the hell is going on?!
Hey!
Let's stop them! Follow me, guys!
I won't let him get away!
Young Master Yamato!
I won't let you get away, Apoo!
They are... extremely strong!
Before more people fall victim,
give Nico Robin to us.
No way!
Wait!
Run, Baron Corpse!
Why?!
Protect Nico Robin!
We need you to leave them to us.
Minks!
Go, Baron Corpse!
Robin-san!
Let's go!
Brook!
We can't let their sacrifice go to waste!
They're beating the Minks
so one-sidedly...
I wonder who they are.
They're a Cipher Pol unit, CP-0,
who were at Dressrosa...
Cipher Pol?! It's an intelligence organization
working directly under the Government, right?!
Why are they here on Onigashima?!
I don't know...
One thing I know is
the situation can't get any worse.
What?!
Among CP-0,
the top-ranked unit in Cipher Pol,
the masked agents
are even more exceptional.
I see...
If we have to run,
we'll be running for our life...
I'm already dead though!
She's so cold!
It's bonebreaking work to shake them off.
That's a good one!
Robin-san, leave it to me!
Let's jump!
That time, too...
And that time...
I...
...am gonna become
just like those assholes of Germa...
You've got to be kidding!
What should I do?
Chuji!
Where did you go, Chuji?
I-I'm sorry I...
Please! Help me!
Judge said...
I'm just a geisha
brought from the Flower Capital!
By the power of science...
Shut up...
...he'd create a warrior
with a heart of ice that won't feel a thing!
Shut up!
I'm begging you! Please let me go!
Germa's blood in your veins
is actually making you excited, right?!
Shut up! I...
...am human!
What?
You okay, lady?
Stay away from me!
What?
Stay away...
Help!
Osome, what happened?!
You're bleeding! Who did this?!
Are you okay? Let me help you!
How could you do this
to a young girl like her!
Wait! There's been a misunderstanding!
Shut up!
You're from the army of
the Land of Wano, right?!
Yeah...
How dare you do this to your own?!
No! Listen to me!
I'm sure I...
I didn't do anything...
Didn't do anything...
...to her...
I think...
Stop lying!
Osome ran from you!
Get out of here! We're hiding in here!
I can't believe you'd assault
an innocent woman!
That can't be true! I...
You brute!
To hell with cowards!
Just go away already!
I...
That's impossible...
I would never assault a lady...
Hey!
Germa!
Where've you been?
I thought the Pleasure Hall was closed!
No! That's the last thing I would do!
How could I lay a hand on...
They knocked a woman unconscious...
You gave a woman of low birth
a taste of self-confidence.
You only bring shame to the Vinsmokes.
Royalty has its own reckoning of the world!
An idiot who has no respect for food.
A man who beats a woman.
The arrogance of royalty that compels you
to see your servants as less than human!
Everything about you guys goes against
what I stand for!
Am I gonna be like them?!
My body isn't tingling anymore...
Is the mutation over?
I was caught up in my thoughts
at that time...
But the moment I noticed her...
...she was flying and bleeding...
...and looking at me, scared!
What's the matter?!
Show me Germa's true power!
Without the suit, you're no match for me!
I...
Hey, Luffy...
Which one do you prefer?
This human me who isn't reliable
because I'd be helpless...
...when our enemy is a woman...
...or the cruel and heartless warrior of science
who can beat up a monster like this...
...and will bring anybody's head
when he's ordered!
Which version of me
can help the King of the Pirates?
Hey you, cook! Join my group!
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
You're a good cook,
so let's be pirates together!
Be sure to come back, Sanji!
Without you, I...
I don't know what'll happen...
Is that Germa's suit?!
I made up my mind.
I'm tired of waiting!
Let me enjoy it to the fullest!
Probably because I wore this,
the "science" that was in my body
from birth awakened.
Nothing can be done about it.
That's right! Accept it!
Show me Germa's science!
If so...
then no more!
Without you, I...
I can't become the King of the Pirates!!
I...
...won't become a Germa warrior!
What a waste!
Show me your transformation!
Goodbye, Germa!
Goodbye...
Women's bath!
I'm gonna finish...
...this fight!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Did I have a Transponder Snail?
Who's calling me at a time like this?!
Not now!
I snuck one into your belly band.
Just in case
you die in a gutter somewhere.
Stupid Cook!
Don't bother me!
It won't take long so listen.
We're gonna beat
the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Yeah, of course!
But after the battle,
if I lose my mind,
you must kill me.
Hey.
Okay, I got it.
I'll make sure to kill you myself!
I don't know what the deal is,
but I got something to look forward to!
In that case,
don't die until then!
Thanks.
Clank.
Where did you go?!
Is that a science thing, too?!
Judge's son!
Hey, don't add fuel to the fire!
It's already burning!
I'll show you hell!
Hell Memories!
The flames spreading through the castle
engulf both armies
and plunge them
into pandemonium full of agonizing cries!
Will the long-held resentment of the Kurozumi Clan,
which consumes everything in its path,
engulf Onigashima as well?
The Kurozumi Clan Suicide reaches its climax!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Onslaught of Kazenbo -
Orochi's Evil Clutches Close in"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!