(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
Purgatory Oni Giri!
Tempest Kick! White Thunder!
Gum-Gum...
Six King...
...Kong...
--...Pistol!
--...Gun!
"Survive! Deadly Combat
with the Strongest Form of Humanity!"
Shave!
Hand Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
Yellow Lotus!
...Kong Organ Gun!
Tempest Kick!
Slaughter!
White Thunder!
One-Sword Style Iai!
Death Lion Song!
They may be tough,
but they won't be able to get up now.
The Seraphim are
the pinnacle of scientific innovation!
Don't underestimate
the strongest form of humanity!
That's enough, you guys!
You're getting up too many times!
What are you, Kaido?!
Why don't our attacks work against them?!
How is that possible?
Oh yeah...
They remind me of King
who I fought in the Land of Wano.
There was a Lunarian in Kaido's pirate group?!
I don't know the name of his tribe but...
I see...
That man is probably the guinea pig...
...who escaped from Punk Hazard
with Kaido a long time ago...
Alber.
Who are you?!
Me? I'm a pirate.
I see why the Government
can't let you go.
You're a Lunarian, huh?
I saw the durability test earlier.
I'm impressed that you withstood
that raging fire...
You're impressed because
I'm a member of the legendary tribe?!
The Seraphim were indeed...
...augmented with his Lunarian blood.
Oh yeah?!
Then watch the flames on their backs
carefully, guys!
Your attack only works on them
when the flames are out.
What?
When it's burning,
they're almost invincible.
Nice try.
I'm sorry. My constitution is unusual.
Your sword attacks won't work against me.
I thought so...
When the flames on his back go out,
he gets faster...
But his defense gets weaker!
I had a hard time with it.
So that's how it works.
I'm sorry I wasted your energy!
I should've noticed it sooner.
No, it's just in time.
Now we know how to fight them.
King's characteristics are white hair,
dark skin,
black wings,
and the flames on his back.
What?!
You should have noticed sooner!
Hey! Where are you going, Helmet?
I have an idea of one place
where Stella might be.
I'll leave this to you.
Go!
Sorry to give you trouble.
Don't get in our way! We're in a hurry.
THIRD FLOOR, BUILDING A
We're no match for him!
Let's retreat for now!
To where?!
Just follow me!
I know this lab like the back of my hand.
There are so many ways to get away!
Oh?! He's not following us!
What?
Where did he go?!
What?!
He got ahead of us!
Edison!
Edison-san!
I won't let you attack anymore!
What?
Brook!
Clonk.
Clonk, clunk, clonk, roll, roll...
Oh no...
Jinbe.
What should I do?
I can't harm him...
Pull yourself together, Nami!
Zeus!
He's not Jinbe. You must fight him!
I know!
But...
...he's just a child.
I'm your partner, Nami.
Trust me and let's fight together!
Let's go, Zeus!
Yeah!
He's not a child!
He's hurting my friends!
He half-destroyed Edison!
He's a killing machine!
He's not cute! He's not a child!
That's right, Nami! Don't hesitate!
Close your eyes if you want!
Push me out! Leave the rest to me!
Lightning Blast!
Not enough!
I won't let you get away!
I got you!
Sorry! Jinbe.
He dove down again!
Run!
Nami-san, he's coming from the bottom!
What?!
It didn't work!
The Constitution of Sanji Kingdom,
Article 1.
Those who scare Nami-san will face...
...the death penalty!
The Constitution of Sanji Kingdom,
Article 9.
Aubade...
Those who make Nami-san scream will face...
Raw Heat Strike!
Sanji-kun!
Nami-san, are you hurt? Are you okay?
Thank you!
I'm glad that you're fine.
I'll take care of him now.
I warned you! You shitty brat!
Whether you're a brat or Jinbe...
I'm gonna execute you!
Little Jinbe!
THIRD FLOOR, BUILDING C
How dare you turn York into stone!
What can we do?!
They're the strongest form of humanity, right?!
Just watch!
Enjoy the taste of the Bubble Gun!
Hey! It's not working at all!
What?!
You lowered your guard!
What?
The bubbles that are created in this gun
are filled with sea energy.
And Green Blood has the same weakness
as power-users!
So the bubble weakens you.
That's amazing, Lilith!
Yeah, isn't it?!
All right! It's our chance to restrain her!
Leave it to me!
Don't touch me!
You insolent fellow! Behave yourself!
It's already worn off!
It only grazed her arm.
It should at least be stuck to her!
Come on! Gee!
Come on! Come on!
She's pissed!
She's gonna shoot a laser!
Retreat for now!
Y-Y-Yeah!
Run!
S-Snake! Don't do it!
You're just a Seraphim! Don't be rude!
You're wide open!
How's that? You damn brat!
You're so smart, Franky!
Bubble Guns are useful!
Give up, you brat!
What?
I'm... in pain...
Sorry!
Perfume Femur!
No! I'm getting petrified!
Damn!
Franky is petrified!
That's not good! He's gonna die!
She's coming this way!
Stop!
Love-Love Mellow!
Usopp! Lilith!
Damn!
OLD DEVIL FRUIT RESEARCH LABORATORY
UNDERGROUND
The only place Stella could possibly be...
...is in this room...
What?
Who are you?
Are you the one who did this to us?
Don't tell me... you're the Cipher Pol agents
who came to the island a while ago!
Why are you here?!
Help us...
Please! Get us out of here...
GOOD
I don't wanna die...
Stella!
You're here!
Who did this to you?
Shaka.
I'm glad that you're okay!
I'll unlock the door now!
Hey...
Shaka... Who are you here with?
What?
Shaka!
He got shot!
Why?!
You are...
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
Still looking for the future
hontou no yakusoku wa
The real promise
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Lies much deeper in my heart
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
A dream that no one can catch up with
tada hitotsu dakishimete
That's all I hold on to
taiyou no youni warau anata e
To you who smiles like the sun
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
I'll sing the same song as that day
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
kono negai ga todoku made
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! King!
He is one of the Lead Performers,
the Supreme Officers of
the Animal Kingdom Pirates led by Kaido,
and a user of the Dragon-Dragon Fruit,
Pteranodon Model!
He is a survivor of
the long-extinct Lunarian tribe!
He was born on December 1st
and likes flying fish sashimi!
When he was a child, he was captured
and subjected to human experimentation.
He became very loyal to Kaido,
who rescued him.
Kaido-san is destined
to become the King of the Pirates!
I'm sorry but he won't.
The characteristics of the Lunarians
are white hair, dark skin, black wings,
and flames burning on their backs!
While the flames are burning,
they won't suffer any damage.
They're unbelievably durable!
When the flames go out, their defense gets weaker
but they become extremely fast!
In the Land of Wano,
he fought a fierce battle against Zoro.
He cornered Zoro many times
with his overwhelming physical abilities,
but got one of his wings slashed
and was defeated in the end.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Egghead is left alone and helpless
as a large Naval fleet closes in.
Who is the mysterious person
that prevented Luffy and his friends
from escaping and took out Shaka?
The mastermind of the plan to hunt down Vegapunk
is finally revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Second Ohara! The Mastermind's Ambition!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!