(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
Ask him this.
Does he really want to fight me now?
Or does he want to leave
the Road Ponegliffs behind and go away?
Tell him to pick one!
Meanwhile, Egghead was in turmoil
due to the dark activities of a traitor.
That traitor was...
York!
"Clash! Shanks vs. Eustass Kid"
SEVERAL HOURS AGO
Come on out!
Hey guys, please.
Help me.
Okay now, I want you to listen...
Trouble is, the World Government...
...seems to have decided to eliminate
not only Stella but also me.
I can't believe it! How annoying!
It's unforgivable! Right?!
Say something!
Yes, it is unforgivable.
Too late!
But if that's what they're up to,
I have a plan!
So...
First, I need you guys
to take care of the nuisances!
I closed the Frontier Dome,
so kill everyone other than me, Stella,
and the hostages underground!
Roger!
And when you run amok,
they'll begin to wonder who ordered it.
If they find out,
I'm not strong enough
to compete with those people...
S-Snake!
Yes, ma'am.
Put on a show of petrifying me
in front of them.
Yes, ma'am.
Undo it when no one's looking!
Yes, ma'am!
And I'll tell you the places in the lab
that should be left intact.
This is for all of you.
So listen carefully...
So the hunting...
...starts now!
Hurry up! Everyone, get on board the ship!
We've got to get off of Egghead!
ELBAPH, WAR-LAND, NEW WORLD
Are you guys...
...ready?
Our opponent is Red-Haired!
I can't believe we're fighting another
Emperor of the Sea after beating one.
I can't stop trembling with excitement!
You guys are high-spirited!
Guys!
The tides that have begun to change
are unstoppable.
Just like us...
...the Kid Pirates!
Don't fall behind!
Follow me even if it means death!
Yeah!
Hey y'all, Kid Pirates!
Our chief is Red-Haired Shanks...
There you are, underlings.
Don't croak... Oh! You hop...
Captain stumbled over his words!
Don't think you have a chance
to see him-ribbit!
FROG-TOES GEROTIN
CAPTAIN OF THE PUDDLE PIRATES
He'f wight!
Pops, your dentures!
FUGA THE ADDENTURER
BANDMASTER OF THE SOCIAL CLUB
Yeah! You fool! I hate you!
I will...
...never ever...
...let you see Chief-chan!
You're so brave! Princess!
PURURU THE BRR-RAVE
PRINCESS OF THE BOURGEOIS PIRATES
Hey!
I said "Hey"!
Is this a joke?!
--Stay away from us-ribbit!
--They're Red-Haired's allies?!
--I will not be defeated!
--I thought we were in the New World!
I know what you mean,
but there are some famous ones, too.
So don't drop your guard.
No matter if they're small fries,
I won't cut corners, but...
Not that way! This way!
No, it's this way!
Oops.
We're gonna set sail soon!
Boss!
They went out to stop the enemies.
Tell them to retreat!
Once the damage is done, it's too late.
Whoa-whoa-whoa, wait, wait, wait.
What are you talking about, Chief?!
What are you guys doing?!
I won't let them touch you!
Yeah!
Well, it means a lot to me you offered!
But don't go out to sea.
Hey, get off of me already!
Don't go.
Let us fight, too!
Whoa-whoa, guys...
Don't be so cold, Chief!
--Well...
--Yeah. Don't leave us behind!
Hey, hey!
When it comes to this,
even an Emperor can't hold his own!
You're right!
No! Chief, are you leaving already?!
Yeah, Chief! We finally got to see you!
Sorry. We just dropped by
on our way to somewhere else.
Now guys, let me go.
We ran into a big name
because we stayed too long.
Now let me through!
--Summon us anytime!
--Yeah!
I love you!
Oh, I'll repeat myself.
Tell the ships to retreat!
Our allies are famously weak.
How could you say that? Jeez!
We survived thanks to you!
We've been protected by your flag!
Yeah! Mind your own longevity
more than your enemies. Crone Oli!
Shut up, Chief! How dare you!
You're so popular, Boss!
Oh please...
Boss! Don't worry.
We'll take care of him.
Whoa-whoa, he is worth 3 billion.
Don't underestimate
how fast young people grow up.
But have their wounds from
the Land of Wano healed already?
Yeah.
They look fine. They're so ready to fight.
That's good...
Did you get any updates on Blackbeard?
No, he's definitely
left the Pirate Island, but...
I thought he'd show up at the Land of Wano.
Hongo!
Here. Info about Captain Kid.
That's our Hongo-san!
You're well-prepared!
Shut up! Keeping loading!
He's from the South Blue.
He has run wild quite a bit...
How many ships are there?
Nine.
There are some faces
I've seen on wanted posters.
Ribbit!
I don't care who the opponents are!
I'm gonna annihilate them in 10 seconds!
With...
...this Damned Punk!
Isn't the ship... getting pulled?!
What's that?!
A cannon?!
What can he do with just a cannon-ribbit?!
Don't flinch, youf guyfs!
Look how they squawk.
I have no business with small fries!
Those who...
...get in my way...
Get wiped away!
Show yourself!
Red-Haired!
Oh no!
Tell the fleet to spread out!
What's wrong, Boss?!
Dorry and Brogy, get ready!
Okay!
Hard to port!
There'll be too much damage...
I guess he saw an ill-fated future...
Get wiped away!
That's what I'd expect from him.
Red-Haired!
Divine Departure.
Partner.
Yeah.
We're almost there.
Yeah!
We won!
Just one more Road Ponegliff!
Just one more
to become the King of the Pirates!
Kaido! Big Mom! Red-Haired!
They're just old-timey scrubs!
We're the strongest!
No one can keep up with us!
The one who'll become
the King of the Pirates...
...is me!
Killer, you bastard!
Why are you laughing...
Boss... Boss!
Open your eyes!
Kid!
Kid-san!
Boss!
Boss is not moving!
He's gonna die!
Damn!
Killer-san went in to cover Boss
and got hurt, too!
We surrender, Red-Haired! Help us!
Don't kill our boss!
Hey Emma, bring them to me!
--What?
--Hurry up!
Th-These are the Road Ponegliffs!
This is all we got!
Please don't kill us!
Chief! This way!
H-Hey...
Look at the island!
A devastating attack...
...is coming!
Hey, small humans!
If you point a gun
at someone else's hometown...
Be prepared to be attacked yourself!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
At Elbaph in the New World,
the Kid Pirates led by Eustass "Captain" Kid
with a bounty of 3 billion berries were...
...destroyed.
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
Still looking for the future
hontou no yakusoku wa
The real promise
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Lies much deeper in my heart
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
A dream that no one can catch up with
tada hitotsu dakishimete
That's all I hold on to
taiyou no youni warau anata e
To you who smiles like the sun
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
I'll sing the same song as that day
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
kono negai ga todoku made
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Shanks!
He is the chief of the Red-Hair Pirates
and one of the Four Emperors.
He was the man who inspired Luffy
to become a pirate!
He was born on March 9th
and likes kimchi fried rice and lobster!
When he was a kid,
he was an apprentice to the Roger Pirates.
He and Buggy, who is also an Emperor,
have had an unsavory tie since then.
Shanks later formed the Red-Hair Pirates,
and stayed at Windmill Village
in the East Blue for a while.
There, he met Luffy.
Luffy wanted to live freely like Shanks
and decided to become a pirate.
Shanks lost his left arm saving Luffy.
And he left his straw hat with Luffy.
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
Luffy is now a great pirate
who is also one of the Four Emperors!
Will they be reunited soon?
Not even Punk Records can predict that!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Koby becomes a decoy and tries to escape
in order to free slaves
on the Pirate Island of Beehive.
Pirates from all over the island
come attacking to block his way!
Will Koby, alone and helpless,
be able to do what is right
and pave the way to liberation?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Run, Koby! A Desperate Escape Strategy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!