(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Are your dreams still pure?
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
All of us tabibito e tsugu
All of us, I tell you travelers
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
No such thing as a pointless fight
barabara no bunmyaku ga
When random contexts
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
Start to make sense on their own
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
You're annoying me.
I'm broken-hearted and angry.
So imagine whose fault it actually is.
"The Navy Surprised!
The Navy Headquarters' Former Admiral, Kuzan"
Screw you!
You're broken-hearted?
Is it about Akainu?
We need more booze!
You're quite the drinker, Ice Pop!
You too, you scummy son of a bitch!
And what did Akainu say?
"We enlisted the same year
and are now in a deadly battle."
"I feel a hot lump in my throat."
Yeah, that's because...
...you're magma!
Man! He launched an awful attack on me...
Because of that, look!
I'm one-legged now!
So that's what happens
when two admirals fight!
What about Akainu?
Did you at least pull one of his arms off?!
No...
But I'm sure he's covered in scars.
Speaking of scars, he might know
the Man with the Burn Scar, Commodore.
Huh? The Man with the Burn Scar?
What? You don't know?!
There are four important
red Road Ponegliffs in the world.
And it seems like Kaido and Big Mom
have one each...
But we can't find...
...the other two!
That's another example of fate...
Yeah...
And they say that the Man with the Burn Scar
has one of them.
Maybe that's me.
You just got that scar recently!
Rumor has it that...
...that man sails a pitch-black ship...
And if someone approaches...
he'll create a giant whirlpool
which swallows you up.
He might be a Devil Fruit power user...
I believe he works for the Government.
In fact, the World Government
has a deep dark side.
If they just hold on to one of the stones,
that'll help prevent pirates...
...from reaching
the great treasure of the One Piece...
Now, tell me. Do you know something?
The Ponegliffs...
I only have bitter memories with them.
If I had seen such an eye-catching
red stone in Ohara, I would remember it.
All I remember...
...is my best friend
who rebelled against the Government...
...and the sad-looking eyes of a girl...
...whose fate was in my hands.
What kind of a dull story is that?!
Commodore, what should we do?
If we take his power for ourselves,
it'll be a considerable asset to us...
I heard that, you pieces of shit!
Do you all wanna go to the world of ice?!
Stop, stop, stop!
You don't need to freeze all of us!
Look at that.
What a fascinating power.
The Chilly-Chilly Fruit, huh?
It'd be nice to have that power...
Oh yeah, I heard that...
...you guys were hunting
Devil Fruit power users.
Bring it on!
Wait!
I'm sorry!
What my crewmember said was ridiculous.
I wasn't gonna do that.
I rather wanted to ask you...
Do you wanna come aboard my ship?
What? Captain, are you crazy?!
You're unemployed now, aren't you?
Do you have a place to go?
What are you gonna do now?
After getting thrown out
by the guardians of justice.
I've sunk so low...
...that a pirate is worried about
my employment.
Wherever you go, whatever you do,
you'll always get involved
in some kind of strife!
So what flag are you gonna fight under?
Huh?!
I'm different from the people in the Navy!
My brand of justice
is different from theirs!
Don't be silly!
How can I trust vermin like you guys
just after a few drinks together?!
Whoa-whoa! I think you misunderstand
what pirates are.
We're not a group of good friends!
For a pirate group...
...all that matters
is that we share mutual interests!
You're free now...
What do you want to do?
Hey, Kuzan!
Thaw out Hibari!
Allow Koby to escape!
Come back to the Navy!
Kuzan-san!
You haven't changed.
You say whatever you wish.
I can't let any of that happen, Garp-san!
Stand back, Koby.
Yes, sir!
I really like...
...how straightforward you are...
...so I'm living the way I want to now!
Idiot...
Ice...
...Ball!
Vice Admiral Garp!
In order to save your beloved pupil,
can you kill your pupil from the past?!
Don't live in the past, you idiot!
I taught you to live in the moment!
It didn't work!
Listen, Kuzan!
Those who waver...
...are weak!
Blue Hole!
Meanwhile, at Winner Island...
WINNER ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Since you lost your ship,
you're no longer a pirate group!
You have no means of escape, either!
The 100 pirates who got their hearts stolen
by you at Rocky Port...
...are still living in fear
on the Pirate Island!
If I bring back your heart,
they'll make a toast in joy!
We're getting the Op-Op Fruit.
This is a truly wonderful twist of fate.
It is!
Oh boy...
I have to save him...
I gotta save him... no matter what!
You really made it for me!
But I can't guarantee it'll work.
Now...
I'm having a hard time deciding
whether to sell or use the Op-Op Fruit.
It can even grant me perpetual youth,
can't it?!
Leave Captain...
...alone!
Bepo...
What?! Sulong?!
No way! The moon isn't even out!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Captain!
Damn! He fled to the sea!
Don't let him get away!
Go back, Bepo...
I can't... leave my friends... behind...
No, I won't!
Trust them, Captain!
From the extremely cold port of the north
till now...
we've always survived!
So...
...none of us will die here!
We've overcome so much together!
So, Captain!
Don't die!
Please...
...don't die!
At Winner Island in the New World...
The Heart Pirates' submarine,
the Polar Tang,
...sank.
The Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law...
...were defeated.
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
Still looking for the future
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Trafalgar Law!
He is the captain of the Heart Pirates
and a former member of the Seven Warlords.
He is an Op-Op Fruit power user
who is known as the Surgeon of Death.
He can operate on anything
in a space called Room!
He was born on October 6th
and likes onigiri and grilled fish!
He suffered from White Lead Disease
when he was a child,
and was forced to eat the Op-Op Fruit
by Doflamingo's younger brother Corazon.
His disease was healed because of it,
but Doflamingo killed Corazon.
The grown-up Law
reappeared in Doflamingo's presence.
Whatever I do before I die...
...is all attributable to Cora-san's legacy!
Together with Luffy, he watched
Doflamingo go down after the hard battle.
Later, in the Land of Wano,
he collaborated with Kid
and brought down the infamous
former Emperor of the Sea, Big Mom!
Now he is a great pirate
who has the whole world's attention!
But he clashed with Blackbeard
and got defeated!
What's gonna happen to him?!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Driven by an ambition
he abandoned 24 years ago,
Buggy bares his soul
in front of the Cross Guild members.
Does the title of the Emperor of the Sea
make one conceited?
Now that he is on equal footing
with Shanks,
he reaches for the dream he once had
and declares he'll try to become
the King of the Pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Let's Go Get It! Buggy's Big Declaration"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!