41 years ago.
There was a man who created trouble in the Wano Country named Kozuki Oden.
His followers came together,...
...and he stepped into the lawless land, Kuri.
Moving Fate Drift Ashore!
Whitebeard Pirates!
You're Kozuki Oden, right?
I've been disavowed,
so I no longer have a name!
Anyone can enter,
but those who try to leave will be killed!
Especially samurai!
It is so restrictive!
How can anyone live in a place like this?!
That's hilarious.
You'll never be able to get out of here!
I mean, don't even try to get out!
"Don't even try to get out"?
That's my least favorite rule!
I make rules in this area!
Cut him!
Are you the boss?!
Oden... I'm gonna kill you!
Try your best!
Oden-san!
sign: Kuri
Look! The gate has been broken!
You fools who grew up pampered in the capital...
...can't understand what it
feels like to live in hell!
Is that what you wanna say?!
I'm gonna kill you all!
Stop barking in a small yard like this!
おでん二刀流 Oden Nitoryu, Oden Two-Sword Style
侍魅しみ大魂 Shimi Daikon, Great Spirit of Samurai
Look!
Up there!
Oden-san!
Oden-san! We're here to back you up!
Sorry.
I've just finished it all.
It took me a whole day, all through the night.
Kill me already!
I know what the future holds anyway.
I have no regrets!
He's the infamous Ashura Doji?!
Hey, guys!
Do you still love me?
Help me with your wisdom and strength!
I've decided to head up this helpless scum...
...as their king!
Shogun-sama! It's Oden-sama again!
What? What did he do this time?!
Look at this!
That lawless Kuri...
Only he could do this...
Is this all true?
Leading the roughnecks of Kuri,
the bloody, hellish land,...
...Oden utilized their abundant energy
and turned the wild land into a habitable place.
In reaction to this accomplishment,
Kozuki Sukiyaki, the Shogun, dropped his disavowal,...
...and gave his son the title
of the Daimyo of Kuri.
Our great Oden-sama
will become the Daimyo of Kuri!
Yay!
Then it'll become a full-fledged province!
I can't believe it! But we stuck it out, too!
Kin-chan...
Congratulations! Our precious Oden-san!
Yay!
You're amazing, Oden-san!
You finally became Kuri's...
Oden!
That's right!
Daimyo!
Oden-sama! Oden-sama! Oden-sama! Oden-sama!
Oden-sama! Oden-sama! Oden-sama!
What's wrong, Ashura?
I...
...have never seen peace before.
Thank you, Oden!
Stop it! Don't creep me out!
You bastard!
What are you doing?! Stop it!
Hey!
I said "Stop"!
Enough!
Screw you!
Knock it off already!
Now, a Daimyo needs vassals.
Rather than being assigned with
some wise and sober men,...
...I want you guys.
Be my samurai!
Oden-sama!
S-S-Stop! You're snotting! It's coming out!
Oh, it's on me!
Stop!
Then, six years later...
...33 years before the present day,...
...elsewhere across the world, the remnants of the disbanded legendary Rocks Pirates...
...each formed a new crew,
extended their influence, and became infamous.
Are they animals?
Just hairy men?
Odd-shaped creatures?
Did you get it?
Yeah...
Far back, several hundred years ago,...
...we Minks
and the Kozuki samurai of the Wano Country...
...made a pledge and became sworn allies.
Damn! The Wano Country is the worst!
Dammit! Get me down!
I'm a kappa!
So you're an imp!
I wish we never set sail!
I wish we didn't come here!
Screw that sworn ally crap!
A cat monster, dog monster, and a kappa...
Is this beach cursed? Let's burn them alive!
Don't do it!
I got enough ingredients for today's oden...
You bastards!
Shame on you, you pricks!
You fear those who aren't like you
because you're ignorant!
How could you bully those little ones?!
Thank you...
All right, then...
Don't leave us like this!
Who are those little creatures?
They followed me.
Thank you for saving us!
It's hot!
Sign of hunger and the shipwreck,
we were almost killed by violence!
Hey! This is too hot to eat!
Whoa... I can't get used to
seeing animals talking.
The Minks! My father once told me about them.
I thought so!
We have that symbol in our country, too!
You-gara people and us are brothers!
And you saved our lives!
We were starving...
I see... Eat as much as you want.
Thank you, savior!
Don't be shy. You'll like radish.
I won't forget this favor.
Have some hanpen.
Konnyaku...
No! It's too hot to eat!
I have a sensitive tongue!
You evil cat!
Hey, wait, Neko!
Hey, Neko!
If it didn't boil...
...it wouldn't be Oden!
That's kind of cool!
To me, it's delicious.
Who are you?!
The ship we were on sank
and my mother and I...
...were cast ashore in this country.
We asked for help, but the people threw rocks at us
because we were Fish-Men.
My mother got hurt,
so we couldn't go back to where we came from.
Before my mother died, she told me.
"The Fish-Men suffer discrimination,
so claim that you're a kappa."
I'm Kawamatsu the Kappa.
I've been living off leftovers.
Thank you for saving me
and treating me to such a delicious meal.
I'll never forget this.
Can I eat all of it?
Well, we'll cook a new one, so wait for that.
No, that's not necessary. It's still edible.
Oh, no. I behaved rudely.
I wasted food.
You've grown up.
I'm sorry-meow, Kappa!
I'll eat it, too!
It's still too hot!
What a funny cat!
Neko!
There are still creatures
I've never seen out there.
By seeing you guys,
I can't wait to set sail again one day!
Great!
This world is a big place!
Okay. Take care!
Well, I mean... Take care.
Let us stay here!
Were you listening to us?!
We have no place to go!
All right! All right!
Yay! Yaaay!
We got more people.
I guess you can't reject anyone...
That's fine, but we're in a bind.
You lent money to Orochi without asking me again!
He's a scumbag!
Well, he's independent now,
but he's still tied to Yasu-san.
I must help him...
Without noise, on tiptoe, stealthy.
Okay? Those are the basics.
Okay!
Let's go! Don't be afraid of Yasuie!
Without noise, on tiptoe, stealthy.
Without noise, on tiptoe, stealthy...
Why did you try to steal this much money?!
Oden-san is out of money!
If you wanna kill us,
just do it, you hedgehog!
If it'll help Oden-san...
I'm happy to die!
Oden... he took such strange people in...
You can have the money!
What?!
Yasuie-sama! What about Hakumai's finances?!
And...
You guys, use this money.
I will give it to you!
More money?! That can't be true!
Is it a trap?!
Do you like Oden?
Then, use this money to fix yourselves up,
learn good manners,...
...buy books, and get yourself educated.
That doesn't sound like us!
I...
No! Speak from your stomach!
With hoodlums like you as retainers,
Oden will humiliate himself.
Oden-sama, will you please elaborate on
how you feel today?
This ganmodoki is exquisite!
What's wrong with you guys?!
You're so creepy these days!
He will become the Shogun of the Wano Country.
Those who support him ought to be
the best samurai in the Wano Country!
Of course, you must protect your lord!
But someday, be the guardian angels of...
...the capital and the whole Wano Country!
The party of Kuri's Daimyo
will come to the capital.
Don't get robbed.
Oden-sama's vassals are ruffians.
Look! They're here!
What?!
Whoa! What happened to those samurai?!
Were Oden-sama's vassals always that cool?!
No, they've changed!
It's like the Shogun's procession!
The regal postures of those samurai were
so glorious that some people even forgot to breathe.
And one could have seen people's knees
give way everywhere in the capital.
Hey, Father!
Oden! You became such a great man!
Everyone is surprised!
I've only been made great.
I haven't changed at all.
I-I-I cannot believe
you feel grateful to others!
Don't be frightened!
Hearing about his father's illness, Oden rushed to the capital and was relieved to see him fine.
However, this was the last time
they would talk to each other.
People are living here.
オヤジ Oyaji, Pops
Oyaji, it'll take a week to repair it.
The cargo is mostly water damaged!
We need to go get food and supplies.
Who wants to go?!
Almost everyone
since we all need some exercise.
I'm coming, too!
You can't. You're an apprentice!
We climbed up the falls, right?
Why is there sea and an island here?
Getting in fights and tossed about in raging waves
doesn't deter Oden's ambition!
He dreams of the unknown world,
and to make his way out, he'll tackle any hardship!
Will Oden be able to win Whitebeard and his people's hearts and set out for an adventure with them?!
Next time on One Piece!
Oden's Determination!
Whitebeard's Trials!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Oden's Determination!
Whitebeard's Trials!