Oden transformed the lawless land of Kuri
into a habitable place,...
...and was given the title of the Daimyo of Kuri
by Kozuki Sukiyaki, the Shogun at the time.
Out at sea, there must be
extraordinary things that are beyond my imagination!
I wanna see them!
I wanna experience the world!
We climbed up the falls, right?
Why is there sea and an island here?
Don't tell me they are...
We have a problem, Kanjuro-dono!
What is it?
Calm down, you're too loud!
We got a report
that a pirate ship docked at Itachi Port!
Pirates?!
Oden-sama! Where are you going?!
To the port!
Go! Go!
Okay, we'll go get food and supplies!
I'm coming, too!
You can't. You're an apprentice!
Don't say that!
オヤジ Oyaji, Pops
Oyaji! Can I go?!
Do as you like.
All right! Let's go!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I said no apprentices allowed!
Stay here!
What?! Oden-sama went to the port?!
Why did you let him go?!
I heard there's a pirate ship at Itachi Port!
It's not like the other ships!
They say it's big and the pirates look tough!
We must stop him!
He just went to chase them away, right?!
No way! I am sure that you are aware of...
...Oden-sama's dream!
Is that it?! A pirate ship?!
I've been waiting...
...for this moment!
We're in trouble!
Hey, back off, you guys!
What?
Someone's coming!
Someone out of the ordinary!
Welcome!
Through bad weather and up the falls,
I'm glad that you made it here!
I've been waiting for you!
Pirates!
Oden's Determination!
Whitebeard's Trials!
You stopped my katana!
Impressive!
Old man! You're awesome!
How dare he ridicule Oyaji!
I'll make him pay for that!
Oden-sama!
The rumor is true, they are pirates!
Don't get in my way, Kin'emon!
Oden-sama?!
He's underestimating me...
Bring it on, you punk!
I've been waiting for someone like you!
My name is Kozuki Oden!
I don't know who you are,
but let me ride...
...on your ship!
おでん二刀流 Oden Nitoryu, Oden Two-Sword Style
桃源とうげん白滝 Togen Shirataki, Paradise White Waterfall
You're annoying!
Get out of my sight!
Damn you!
Who do you think he is?!
He is the Daimyo of Kuri, Kozuki Oden-sama!
Do you know the consequences of
pointing a katana at him?!
He is a Daimyo?
You damn pirates! Get out of this country now!
Screw you! I'll make you regret...
...messing with the Whitebeard Pirates!
I wanna explore the world! It's my dream!
Let's set sail together!
We should leave now!
You cannot do that!
Shut up!
I wanna leave this restrictive land!
I wanna see the free world!
Please! Take me with you!
Oden-sama! Raise your head!
You tried to kill our captain, didn't you?!
I'm begging you!
Stop it! He is a pirate!
You are a nuisance!
Get out of this country now!
I wish I could...
But our ship was wrecked on the way here
and we can't go anywhere.
That's a shame! Let's repair it quickly!
Damn! If you stay here, Oden-sama will...
Repair it immediately and leave!
Yeah, we will do so.
Hey! Carry it there!
Hey! You-gara guys!
It's time to eat!
Now, help yourself!
It looks delicious!
This is Oden-sama's special oden!
If it didn't boil it wouldn't be Oden!
Here!
Do you like it, Whitebeard?
Thank you, Oden!
I've never tasted something quite like this!
So this is the taste of a foreign country!
It's alcohol made from grapes.
There are tons of things that I don't know,
aren't there?!
Let's go out to sea!
Show me the world that I've never seen!
You're not the type to serve under someone!
If you come on board...
When selfish people like you come together...
Thump!
...what will happen to a team?
It's too hot!
I learned it the hard way
in my previous pirate group.
Set sail on your own!
If I could do that, I'd already have done it!
I tried dozens of times, but I failed!
I have zero skill at navigating a ship!
Then give it up and do your job as a Daimyo!
This country is so restrictive!
I can't stand it! Take me with you!
Whitebeard!
The Wano Country has a law
that strictly bars people from leaving the country!
Oden-sama is now the Daimyo of Kuri,
so it would be inexcusable for him to break the law!
Don't tell him about that!
That's good to know!
We're like-minded!
I have no intention of taking Oden, either!
I don't care about the national laws!
Oden, you still have some work to do here,
don't you?
What?!
Oden-sama is an indispensable person in Kuri
and the whole Wano Country.
Shut up, Kin'emon!
Let me aboard your ship, Whitebeard!
No!
I'm gonna go out to sea!
This country is so restrictive!
I don't wanna go home!
Untie me! Stop it!
Open it!
I won't give up!
Wait for me!
Whitebeard!
Five islands in the world?!
That's totally wrong!
What?!
There's more than 10 or 20 million!
There are that many?!
You don't know anything?
Adventures are fun! You must be interested!
Of course, I am!
Stop it!
I won't let you go!
That's enough!
The world is big!
No one can count how many islands there are!
W-W-W-Wait...
Good job, guys!
The Moby Dick's repairs are complete!
Now, get ready!
We'll set sail!
Where are you going?!
Whoa! Izo!
Where are you going, Oden-sama?
You scared me!
That may be so but where are you going?
Let me go to the bathroom whenever I want!
I thought I was a Daimyo!
I am sorry... The night can be cold.
I have to pee!
I feel bad for Oden,
but we had to sneak away at night.
Considering his strength,
he may have been an asset.
And Oyaji kind of liked him...
Huh?! What are you talking about?!
Don't play dumb!
Even if I took a liking to him,...
...it's akin to kidnapping royalty...
There'd be hell to pay.
Did you leave the treasure chest as thanks?
They gave us food and timber...
Hey! What's going on?!
I knew you would do this!
Whitebeard!
Oden?!
Let me on board the ship!
Oden-sama! I knew you would do this!
I won't let you go!
That fool!
Let me come!
Show me the world!
Come back! You are the next Shogun!
How reckless!
So long, Oden! Give it up and go home.
Wait, Marco!
What?!
Bring in the one who came after him!
Boy...
Everyone, hold onto the ship!
This is no time for you to worry about others!
We're flying over the falls!
Oh, no!
Hey! Why did you save me?!
Oden-sama!
Help!
Oden-sama is gone!
Whitebeard's ship left the port, too!
I was afraid of this!
Izo-nii-sama...
Inu-chan and Neku-chan are gone, too!
Don't cry, Okiku!
Instead of fearing the worst,
let's look for them!
Okay?!
Mm-hm.
Search! Search across the country!
Hey, Whitebeard! Pull in Oden-sama!
He will die!
He carries the future of the Wano Country
on his shoulders!
You saw me turning him down
many times, right, kid?
But he still left the country!
So we'll play by our own rules!
Damn...
Please!
I can't just take in a dangerous guy like him
and put my family in jeopardy.
If you wanna stop him,
you need to convince him.
Listen, Oden!
Three days!
If you can hang onto that chain for three days,
I'll welcome you on board!
You sure, Whitebeard?!
Yeah, you have my word!
I'll get on board that ship!
Wait for me, Whitebeard!
Is Oden still there?
Yes, he is...
But he looks terrible...
His face is swollen beyond recognition
from the collisions and the water!
Like it's gonna burst!
An hour to go!
Hang on, Oden!
Hey, why are you cheering him on?!
Because if he pulls this off,
he'll join us, right?
Oden will become our crewmate!
Oden will become our crewmate?
Hang tough, Oden!
Go for it, Oden!
Don't give up, Oden!
Those fools...
I won't forget you
for giving my lord such a hard time!
Whitebeard!
Oden, keep it up!
Oden!
A little more to go!
Oden-sama!
Let go! Do not touch me!
She's so beautiful!
Very classy!
Why are you running, you tramp?!
We'll take you to the Wano Country
by ship like you wanted!
Come here! We don't wanna hurt you!
I know you do not!
That is a slave ship!
If you hurt me, my price will go down!
I cannot believe I was fooled
by you evil-looking miscreants!
I am so stupid!
There's only the sea behind you!
You have nowhere to run!
Just give up!
No, I have a place to run!
The only place you belong is on our ship!
We'll treat you nicely!
This is it...
Let's go forward into the future again.
What?
What?!
W-W-What the hell is that?!
Sea Spirit!
I heard a woman's voice...
screaming for help...
A monster?!
Are you all right?!
What?!
You're not hurt, are you?
Oden's great adventure begins!
Meeting new people, facing challenges!
He travels across an unknown world
beyond his wildest imagination!
The story of the troublemaker Oden instantly
becomes known across the world,...
...and finally comes to this man's knowledge!
Next time on One Piece!
Whitebeard's Little Brother!
Oden's Great Adventure!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Whitebeard's Little Brother!
Oden's Great Adventure!