Oden joined the Roger Pirates,...
...and sailed across the New World...
ロード歴史の本文ポーネグリフ Road Poneglyph,
Road Text of History
...seeking the Road Poneglyphs
which detailed the location of the last island.
Guided by the four Poneglyphs,...
...Gol D. Roger finally made
it to the last island!
People lavishly praised
Roger's accomplishment!
To the Wano Country!
The Roger Pirates Disband
Oh, Oden.
What did you think of the last island?
I thought it was great!
My body still burns with excitement!
I feel the same!
Oh, Roger!
Rayleigh, you're here...
Roger...
Do you remember what you said to me
when we first met?
Yeah, I do...
"Turn the world upside down," wasn't it?
You also said, "We were destined to meet."
Is the promise fulfilled?
Yeah!
B-Buggy!
Captain's...! Captain Roger's...!
They came back!
They flashily came back!
Captain!
Redtaro asked Roger
who came back from Laugh Tale something,...
...and broke into tears...
The world went wild
over the birth of the King of the Pirates,...
...and the Marine started acting aggressively.
"Wealth, fame, power...
The man who attained everything...
The King of the Pirates, Gold Roger"!
It's Gol D. Roger!
But being called the King of the Pirates
isn't so bad.
Now I understand why the World Government
wants to cover up your name like that.
The world called
everything that Roger gained collectively...
...the great treasure of One Piece!
They don't know anything!
But because of your fame,
everyone's coming to get you, Roger!
Take down Roger!
Find Roger!
Plunder his treasure!
Gold Roger has everything!
Looking back, it has all been miraculous.
With such a limited life expectancy,
I can't believe I made it this far.
I have nothing but gratitude for you guys!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
Why are you speaking formally like that?!
Damn you, Captain!
Don't make me blush, you fool!
Fool!
Then I'll just say it!
Come on! I'm ready!
The Roger Pirates are disbanded!
Will be born...
Our ruler will be born...
Another will be born in a distant sea...
Even whales are happy to know
that the two rulers will meet again one day...
We have been waiting for so long, too...
It will not be long...
It is going to work out this time...
10 until the birth.
15 until growing up.
Who are you?!
How can you talk so deep under the sea?!
Hey, Shyarly,
when will the Mermaid Princess be born?
10!
That voice...
Voice?!
I guess it's telling the truth.
Someone will be born.
And that person will surpass us...
We came too early...
The One Piece, huh?
I wonder who will find it.
I think that will be my son.
You don't have one.
I'm gonna have one in the future!
All right! Let's drink!
Sail towards somewhere where there's no Marine!
I'll disembark first!
Yeah!
Guys! Take Oden home next!
Of course!
Oh, yeah, Oden!
I'm thinking about meeting Whitebeard before I die.
Do you want Izo to return
to the Wano Country, too?
No...
He meshed with the crew of the ship.
Tell him to take care of White-Kichi-chan.
Okay, I got it.
After some words to Rayleigh,
the longest-serving member known as the Dark King...
Roger left the ship.
He received a bundle of medicine
from the ship's doctor Crocus.
He was reaching the final
stage of his illness...
But just like the farewell of every man,
no one cried a single tear.
The King of the Pirates' crew...
...don't shed tears.
It's still astonishing!
Wrecked ships that couldn't
enter the country...
Yeah...
If you catch a wrong current,...
...the ship will be destroyed
without getting near the Wano Country.
In the past, this isolation
policy had a point.
But we must open it up
before "Joy Boy" comes one day!
Thank you for everything!
Sure!
Take care!
Yeah!
Oden!
That bastard! He's flashily walking away!
Be well, guys!
I am not dying.
So we said goodbye smiling.
Because I will see them again someday!
Oden-san!
I missed you!
You guys!
Go, Hiyori!
Toki!
Momonosuke!
Hiyori!
I missed you all, too!
There, Hiyori! Up you go!
What are those?!
Father!
What did you just say?!
Yes!
I called you "Father"!
I'm impressed!
Oh, you've grown so much, Momonosuke!
Yes! I hope all is well with you, too!
How polite!
Welcome back!
You bastard!
How could you be so impolite?!
You think you deserve politeness?!
Oden-sama!
Oden-sama! Welcome back!
I'm happy for you, Otoki-san!
Look how popular I am!
I was neglecting the country for so long.
I thought I'd be criticized more...
Thank your wife, Toki-sama!
She is a very wonderful person...
When she recovered from her illness,
she went down...
...to the town and helped citizens every day.
She has never acted arrogantly
as a Daimyo's wife.
She labored with everyone
and cheerfully shared the stories of your adventure.
Toki-sama and your children are
extremely popular in Kuri now!
And they kept saying nice things about you...
At some point,
everyone stopped speaking ill of your selfish behavior!
I see! Thank you guys!
Don't mention it!
We really love you! Right, kids?
I'm jealous! I wanna be loved, too!
Kiku! I must tell you about Izo...
Inu-chan and Neko-chan told me!
I'm fine as long as he's doing well!
Okay!
By the way,
what happened to Denjiro and Ashura?
I didn't see them a year ago, either...
Ashura became the boss of the yakuza
and mountain bandits in Kuri...
...to keep them under control!
Denjiro is wandering about,
borrowing money and paying it back.
Neither wrangling bandits
or borrowing money sound like comfortable lives.
Yes.
There is another reason that everyone is happy
about your return.
I will tell the story from the beginning.
After you left, we managed to run the Daimyo-less Kuri
with the citizens' cooperation.
Oh, that must have been hard.
Anyway, how is my father doing?
Shogun-sama...
I see!
So he wasn't well...
What a shame that I couldn't be with him
when he died.
The problem is the Shogun-sama's successor!
It is hard to understand,
but at your father Sukiyaki-sama's request,...
...that Orochi became...
Please lend me money!
I got confused by listening to him.
Orochi is like a little brother to me?!
I only lent him money
out of respect for Yasu-san.
He did not pay me back even a Silver coin!
I also learned that Orochi is a
descendant of the Kurozumi Family...
...that once caused some big trouble.
It seems like Kurozumi Orochi is now sitting as the Shogun
as a proxy for me.
I am sure you saw them on your way here,...
...but each region has several weapon factories
and people who oversee laborers.
And the men of each region
are forced to work there...
...earning poverty wages by the Shogun's order.
Why is that?!
Why does everyone listen to someone like Orochi?!
That is because a pirate named Kaido
is supporting him...
...and he is monstrously strong!
Because of that,
Orochi is doing whatever he wants!
Yes! We tried to attack Orochi...
No, Kin'emon!
Do not tell him!
No, tell me! What happened?!
Raizo!
Take Momonosuke-sama and Hiyori-sama
out of the room!
Pardon me!
So what happened?
Yes, about half a year ago...
...a man who refused to labor at a weapon factory
and his family...
...were executed!
We could not take any
more of Orochi's cruelty,...
...and motivated by anger, we
marched into Orochi's place...
...in the Flower Capital with
katanas in our hands...
But we got outsmarted and
Kaido's subordinates arrived at Kuri at the same time!
They invaded this castle...
...and we let them attack Momonosuke-sama
who is Kozuki's next heir...
...in the line after Oden-sama!
In the end...
the enemies were taken down by...
...Kawamatsu and Inuarashi
who stayed to guard the castle...
But the one who saved him
from their first arrow attack...
...was Toki-sama who threw
herself in front of it!
I am deeply sorry!
Because our reckless action,
Toki-sama seriously injured her leg!
We put your family members' lives in danger!
I am sorry!
Let me see, Toki.
Do not worry, Oden-san!
It is already healed!
Thank you for protecting our child!
It must have been hurt!
Wait, Oden-san!
If you lose your temper over a little thing like this,...
...we will be attacked again!
A... A...
A little thing?!
Toki, you...
...have not heard about the
stories of my old days?
Your old days?
Well, um, since he was a
child, Oden-sama was known...
...for drinking and fighting,
and ended up being arrested!
He was a rough neck
who everyone in the Flower Capital was afraid of...
I understand the way Orochi does things!
Guys! Protect my family!
Oden-san!
Protect Kuri!
Oden can't tolerate Orochi's
evil acts and becomes furious!
With Emma, he aims for nothing less than
taking the Shogun's head!
When the fate of the Wano Country
is about to be turned around,...
...word from the King of the Pirates
echoes over the East Blue...
...and throws the whole world
into rapture and turmoil.
Next time on One Piece!
Sad News!
The Opening of the Great Pirate Era!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sad News
The Opening of the Great Pirate Era