In the second year
since Oden returned to the Wano Country,...
...the battle between the Gecko Pirates and...
...the Beasts Pirates
took place in Ringo.
Gecko Moria and Kaido clashed.
Go to hell!
At the same time,...
...the God of the Blade Ryuma's
grave was vandalized.
And even under these circumstances...
Oh, radish, ganmo!
sign: Eggs
Chikuwa and eggs!
One, two, three, go ahead and eat!
Oden showed up in the Flower Capital once a week
and made a fool of himself.
I wanna dance, too!
Don't.
The essential factor for
the taste is the stock!
it wouldn't be Oden...
...it wouldn't be Oden!
It's that silly lord again.
I feel sorry for the people of Kuri.
The silly lord of Kuri, huh?
It's overpraise to even call him a lord.
Is it okay for you guys to
still serve me as my retainers?
Where else would we be?
We've seen Oden-sama's naked dance
since the old days.
Yeah, it's nothing new!
Alright then, I'll keep working on my dance!
My naked dance!
Oden-sama...
Konbu, important!
The Kozuki Family has hit bottom.
I heard his son and heir Momonosuke-sama
is a fool, too.
The essential factor for
the taste is the stock!
If it didn't boil...
...it wouldn't be Oden!
The whole family will dance naked in time!
Raid!
Oden and the Akazaya Nine
Hey, wait, Hiyori!
No!
I said "Wait"!
I finally made my family targets of scorn...
Father!
Aren't you gonna practice today?
I love your dance!
Me, too!
Toki...
Yes?
Do you want to leave me?
Are you kidding?
Are you trying to make me angry?
The silly lord of Kuri.
The whole Wano Country called him so,...
...and only his family, retainers, and a few supporters
would speak with him.
You'd like to see Boss Hyogoro?!
Whoa-whoa!
Stay away from him, you silly lord!
Stop it!
Don't get cocky! Stand back!
Ma'am!
Got it!
My lady!
I'm sorry. Now come in and have some tea!
Hyo-san! Oden-chan's here!
Orochi won't leave me alone!
Who would wanna serve a guy like that?
Well, don't put yourself in danger, Hyo-san.
I saw you the other day.
Oden-chan, your dancing's improving.
Oh please, my lady!
Come on. Have another cup!
Three years pass.
Oh, radish, ganmo!
Chikuwa and eggs!
Look, he's here again this week.
Even in this snow?
He's a helpless silly lord.
Oden wouldn't be oden...
It's Oden! You idiot!
He's as stupid as always.
You fools do not know anything!
I know Oden-sama has a good reason.
That is why he...
Yeah, that dance is getting
better and better.
Let's watch him no matter
how long it goes on.
The snow is killing me...
Shame on you!
You're disgusting!
So annoying.
Go away!
In a flash, four years passed,
but nothing changed in the Wano Country.
In the fifth year, Orochi made a move.
It's the Shogun! Shogun Orochi!
I was expecting you!
Shogun!
It's been a while, Oden.
It has been exactly five years since that day.
The time has finally come...
The time for what?
I don't remember.
How did you make that wild Kuri
into a nice little town like this?
I'm impressed!
I wanna build several weapon factories here.
What?
Understood?
I need your cooperation, Oden.
Well, Shogun, what about the ship?
About the promise you and Kaido made...
What are you talking about?!
If I catch everyone around here
and force them to labor day and night,...
...we'll have good productivity!
Right?!
Let's make...
...the Wano Country a
weapon manufacturing hub!
P-Please wait!
Oh, yeah, by the way...
Hyogoro was too much to handle for me,...
...so I left him in Kaido's hands.
What?!
I wanted to have the Wano Country's...
...underworld ruler as my
subordinate, but I gave up.
Well, he might be killed soon.
His underlings annoyingly fought back.
Give us back our boss!
So it took more trouble than we thought.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Speaking of which,
remember Hyogoro's wife, that old bag?!
I heard she screamed
and threw herself on them, too!
She got shot to death!
No!
Stop it! Don't take him away!
Hyo... san...
As the wife of a yakuza,
she shouldn't have acted so disgracefully!
By the way, your children...
Momonosuke and Hiyori.
How old are they now?
Children are cute, huh?
I guess they're extremely cute now.
Take good care of them.
I leave the construction of the factories
to you!
Don't...
Don't!
Oden-chan.
It must've been cold today to dance.
You're working hard!
My lady, coldness isn't a big deal to me.
I heard someone threw a stone at you.
That happened today, too!
You're hanging tough!
You're welcome to visit us anytime.
We're always on your side.
Father!
I want to be like you!
Yeah? Then, eat a lot!
I want to dance like you!
Oh, you're all here.
Father!
Oden!
Oden-chan!
Hey, don't do it...
No! Don't do it!
As his family and retainers had expected,...
...this great samurai has been carrying something
on his shoulders all by himself for five years.
Orochi...
...and Kaido...
Let's get them!
We have been waiting for you to say that
all this time!
We'll go to his island!
While he sleeps after drinking,
we'll cut his head off!
What you are about to see...
...is Kozuki Oden's commotion of a lifetime
which the whole Wano Country wept at.
Nine men who he took in
to become samurai gathered.
It was twilight.
The bright red sun tinged the men
marching bravely into battle with burning red,...
...and even the katanas worn at their waists
displayed burning souls.
People later honored their intense loyalty,...
...and called them the Akazaya Nine.
I'm jumping higher than you!
No, I'm jumping higher than you!
Their enemy was Kaido.
Without setting their sights on anyone else,...
...they marched on,
but this is sadly a thing of the past.
What's waiting for them is
Kozuki Oden's public execution.
Until the legendary hour
that would go down to posterity,...
...please watch without blinking your eyes!
What?! From Oden?!
I am going to Kuri. Bring me my horse!
Brother, what is this?!
Stop it! That book is important to me!
No way! What is this all about?!
I didn't expect this!
Kaido's subordinates!
Are they all...?!
There are hundreds of them!
No way! Why is he here?!
Kaido!
I wasn't expecting a war.
Why are they so prepared?!
How did they know that we were coming?!
Maybe there is a spy in your castle.
I don't wanna turn my newly built mansion
into a battlefield...
So I came all the way to you.
On that day, five years ago,...
...I made a promise with you two...
That was all a lie, wasn't it, Kaido?!
That's right.
That was all a lie.
At that time,
we thought we were at a disadvantage.
You'd just come home
and if you joined hands with Hyogoro,...
...all samurai and yakuza in the Wano Country
would've become our enemies.
We didn't have that many
underlings back then...
If you were a crazy man who wouldn't care
about the toll of human life just as I heard,...
...it would've been a tough battle for us.
But you believed Orochi's words
and chose the way that no one would be hurt.
Newgate and Roger were
certainly that kind of pirate.
They're strong, but naive in a way.
You're just like them!
A fool who kept dancing!
Naked, laughed at, and scorned!
You no longer have the old Kozuki dignity!
I made a good choice that day.
Let's talk about the future now.
Follow Oden-sama!
Wait, wait! Is this how strong samurai are?!
Don't hesitate! We're not outnumbered!
Advance, advance!
Follow Oden-sama!
Brother, let's play!
Stop it, Hiyori!
Let's play!
I received a letter from Oden by a messenger.
It says, "My wife and children will be targeted.
Please save them."
Dropkick!
How dare you!
Wait!
Momonosuke...
I mean, Momonosuke-sama is already eight...
Otoki-san, you have to be prepared.
If Oden loses...
...this country is finished.
Kaido's attack turns the
Wano Country into a battlefield!
Burning with a flame of
hope they almost lost,...
...Oden and the Akazaya members
open the way for the future!
Putting the suffering he has
shouldered to the blade,...
...Oden fights the source of evil head-on!
To take back the Wano Country!
Next time on One Piece!
The Moment of Conclusion!
Oden vs. Kaido!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The Moment of Conclusion!
Oden VS Kaido!