Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Toki...
When the time comes, read this.
Good luck in battle...
"A long winter is coming to the Land of Wano.
Toki, I want you to use your power.
If I die."
Kozuki Toki and Kozuki Oden.
They left the Land of Wano
to the new generation,
and fell.
"Back to the Present Day!
20 Years Later!"
It's cold! It's cold! It's cold!
Too cold!
I told you to boil the water!
It's already boiling, Orochi-sama!
No, it isn't!
It's cold!
It's cold, it's cold...
Orochi-sama!
It's hot!
Orochi-sama, it's already scalding hot!
You'll get burned!
Shut up!
I feel cold! I can't stop shaking!
Bring me the Kozuki samurai retainers' bones!
Why can't you find them?!
Show me the proof of their deaths!
Cast nine shadows on the
night woven of 20 years
and you shall know the
brilliance of the dawn!
The dawn...
It's still a long way to go
until this country sees its dawn!
"20 years"?
Toki-sama...
Are they alive?
Kappappa, kappappa!
Kappappa and pa!
Come on!
Kappappa, kappappa!
Kappappa and pa!
Princess! This is the Kappa Dance!
Kappappa, kappappa!
Kappappa and pa!
Oden-sama! Toki-sama!
Hey, you!
Look at you! You're filthy!
Do you really live here in the capital?
We don't want you here!
Hey! Are you listening?!
You son of a...
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Damn you!
Hey, please wait!
--You're quite strong!
--Where are you from?
Let us follow you!
What's your name?
My name?
Let's see...
Kyoshiro!
KYOSHIRO
Hmmm... So you guys are
the Kyoshiro Family...
Yes, sir!
Lift your head up!
You have a good reputation.
Would you like to serve as my guard?
It would be an honor, Orochi-sama!
Mm-hm! Good, good! That's great!
In that case, I have a
little something for you...
Please accept this!
Very nice!
Does it make you happy?!
Just like this, money, ladies, soldiers...
I can provide everything you need!
Very nice! Very nice!
I feel extremely honored, Orochi-sama!
Too good to be true! Who is he?!
How resourceful! And he can fight!
He's a yakuza
who's taking the place of Boss Hyogoro!
The Kyoshiro Family dominates
the Flower Capital!
He has a weakness, too!
Yeah, he always looks tired...
So people call him Napping Kyoshiro!
Probably too much nightlife!
It's Ushimitsu Kozo!
He stole money from the storehouse!
USHIMITSU KOZO
Hiyori-sama!
Princess-sama! Where did you go?!
Why...
Hiyori-sama!
Oh?
Big Sis, this girl...
Boss-san!
We have a cute girl here in the doorway...
She must be an orphan
slipped into the capital...
The poor thing is starving...
Hiyori-sama!
This must be hard to understand...
Although I am identifying
myself as Kyoshiro now,
I am actually one of the Akazaya Nine,
Oden-sama's retainers...
I am Denjiro!
What?! Denjiro?! You?!
Yes, it is true. Hiyori-sama.
It has been a while!
Denjiro...
I didn't expect to see you again...!
How have you been?
Kawamatsu helped me escape.
Oh, he did...
But then, where is he now?
If I had stayed with him,
he would've given me all his food,
and he wouldn't have eaten at all...
He would've died!
I was scared...
Hiyori-sama, look at me closely.
Look at my face!
My face is haunted by a ghost called wrath...
...so much so even Kin'emon and the others
would not recognize me.
And that is what we want!
Until the moment the great
battle begins someday,
do not tell anyone, even
our allies, about me.
Instead of Kawamatsu,
I will protect you from now on!
Tell others that your name is Komurasaki!
Take this...
Ushimitsu-san.
I got money again.
Do not be reckless...
I will make sure to distribute
it in Ebisu Town.
Mm-hm!
Listen. As I told you many times,
carry fake blood under your kimono every day.
Orochi is fixated on you...
without knowing that you
are Oden-sama's daughter...
It must be tough for you.
In case of an emergency,
I will tear Orochi away from "Komurasaki" with "death."
I will make the people of the Flower Capital
believe that Komurasaki is dead.
We're almost there, so I'll be fine.
It's been almost 20 years!
And now it's almost present day...
A few months before Luffy's raid
on the night of the Fire Festival...
A FEW MONTHS BEFORE THE FIRE FESTIVAL
They're here!
The ghosts are really here!
So Toki's power was real!
Kin'emon, Kanjuro, Raizo,
Kikunojo, and Momonosuke...
Five of them!
They came jumping from that day 20 years ago!
Is there really such a power?
From that burning castle?
Isn't someone playing a joke
to freak you out more?
Look!
Look at this letter!
Look, look...
Keep an eye on the sea coast!
Someone will try to leave the country!
Yes, sir!
Don't kill them if they're alive.
After 20 years,
there's something I wanna ask the remnants of the Kozuki...
Anyway, your spy is quite competent.
Listen, he's a trustworthy man...
He was born and raised in a theater troupe.
But one day,
as a result of persecution in the Land of Wano,
he lost his parents while they were on stage.
They're the family of the Daimyo killer!
Serves them right!
--Yeah! Yeah!
--They deserved it!
By playing characters,
he survived.
YOU'RE A DESCENDANT OF
THE KUROZUMI CLAN'S MAIN FAMILY?!
That's right.
I killed those who slayed your parents.
But our revenge is just started!
Live your life as a real Kozuki retainer,
and die as a Kozuki retainer
without letting anyone know!
That's the important role
that you've been given in this big play!
Can you do it?
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR A PLACE TO DIE
IT'S AN HONOR
His only pleasure is to play someone else!
Every time I went to Oden Castle
to borrow money,
he brought out
twice as much money as I asked for.
I could ally with you
because I had that money...
I'm sure that the information about
the silly lord Oden's raid was helpful for you, too.
He's so crazy...
...that he was really ready to die...
...with Oden and the others
in the execution.
He has no mind of his own.
Until I stop him,
he'll live as a real Kozuki retainer,
and matter-of-factly send information...
...in an eerily loyal manner...
FLOWER CAPITAL, PRESENT DAY
Well then, the legendary samurai
has passed down to posterity.
It's been 20 years since
Kozuki Oden's tragic death.
This is the story of the two opposing clans,
the Kozuki and the Kurozumi,
and the pirate, Kaido!
To fulfill Kozuki Oden's dream of
opening up the borders...
the samurai retainers
jumped 20 years into the future.
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
GRAVE OF KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
Time passed and it's present day...
Three samurai and a ninja
successfully traveled through time.
With them is Oden's son
and the future Shogun of the Land of Wano, Momonosuke.
They must head for
Zou the Phantom Island whose location is a mystery!
However...
Their ship was wrecked when they almost reached Zou
and they were separated from Raizo.
Later in Dressrosa, Momonosuke
got on board a mysterious ship.
Kin'emon pursued the ship,
separating from Kanjuro.
And Kin'emon arrived at...
...the island of fire and ice, Punk Hazard.
Oh, I'm finally separated from it-bu!
What?!
The lower body just talked!
What's going on?!
Kin'emon finally met...
...the Straw Hats!
Momonosuke happened to eat the artificial Devil Fruit,
which enables him to transform into a dragon,
and soon after met Luffy.
Then Kin'emon and Momonosuke reunited,
and headed for Dressrosa with Luffy.
Let's sail out!
In Dressrosa...
...their samurai colleague, Kanjuro,
was waiting for them.
A deadly battle against a tough enemy,
Donquixote Doflamingo, who ruled Dressrosa ensued.
After taking down the Doflamingo Family,
the group left Dressrosa!
After that, they finally got to their true destination,
Zou the Phantom Island.
There, they met Cat Viper and Dogstorm
who lived in Kuri when they were young!
And...
People from the country of Zou!
I'm a retainer of the Kozuki Clan from the Land of Wano,
named Kin'emon!
I'm here to look for my comrade named Raizo
who is a warrior from the same country!
Has he been here?!
Raizo-dono is...
...safe!
They reunited with Raizo
who was protected by the Minks from Kaido's subordinates!
I want to bring down Kaido!
I got it!
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Let me have Kaido's head though!
Thus, the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance
was formed.
For months, they risked their lives
to recruit allies who'd fight with them.
Their persistence must've paid off
because 4,200 people stood up to fight!
Weapons and ships are ready!
Plenty of troops for the
raid are gathering...
...at twilight today, the day of the Fire Festival,
at Tokage Port.
Head for Onigashima!
Kaido...
...will be taken down by us!
Yeah!
Kin'emon decides to advance
but faces challenges!
Their retreat intercepted by Kaido's army,
the Akazaya members are driven to a corner!
The Straw Hats are nowhere to be found!
Betrayal and despair! Wavering bonds!
Will the turbulent opening
instantly bring the curtain down?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Sea Is For Pirates! Raid! To Onigashima!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!