mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
While the Golden Festival was in full swing,
the Tobi Roppo who had gathered around Kaido
were assigned a job.
Now, here is what I want you guys to do.
My foolish son Yamato disappeared today,
and I want you to bring him to me!
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others who snuck into Onigashima
to take down Kaido...
Hey! You're all covered in red-bean soup!
You don't eat red-bean soup!
You cover yourself in it!
Bring the soup!
We'll pour it on each other!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Why can't you sneak in quietly?!
"Fighting Music!
An Ability That Harms Luffy!"
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
But these fools
intentionally spilled red-bean soup!
What? Red-bean soup?!
In that case, I gotta cut them all up!
Yeah...
It's so yummy!
What kind of surprise is this?
Red-bean soup?
How come they got mad over such a thing?
Is that something that triggers them?
I don't get it...
That group is hopeless.
I can't work with them.
It was impossible for those fools to keep a low profile
in the first place.
What should we do?
Forget it. We gotta keep moving.
We're so close to them!
We made quite a scene after all.
Well, we had no choice.
Yeah, we had no choice
since red-bean soup was involved.
But it's not time to start a battle yet.
I know.
They still have no idea who we are.
Are you happy now?
Yeah!
Then...
--Let's run!
--Yeah!
They're running away!
Catch them!
Hey, what's going on?!
Don't tell me they are...
A-pow-pow! Yo, check it out!
Queen-san, I need to tell you something important
Listen up!
Yo! Check it out!
Okay! Apoo! Apoo! Apoo!
Tell me the important thingy
With Brother Apoo's nice rhyme, pooh!
Okay, okay! A-pow-pow!
What's wrong, Kid?
It's my time! I'm gonna risk my life!
Gotta send out good vibes!
This voice...
Check it out!
In Udon under your domain
Jailbreak attempts are all in vain!
No way out for captive rats
But look at those two!
Oh, should we fight?
Made a mess and got loose!
I remember that face!
No way!
That's right! They must be...
Straw Hat Luffy and Pirate Hunter Zoro!
So he broke out of the prison...
How is that possible?!
Clank!
Yo, this is Queen!
This is Chief Warden Babanuki from Udon!
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain Kid,
and the other hoodlums
are all quietly behind bars.
I see...
I just called you to say
everything's okay here...
Damn Babanuki!
Did he lie to me?!
Today's the happy Golden Festival!
Catch them as a gift for me!
Hey, Queen-san!
What will the one who catches them get?!
I happen to wanna get rid of someone...
...from the Tobi Roppo!
I'm gonna eliminate someone from the Tobi Roppo
and give the rat-catcher the vacant post!
The Tobi Roppo.
Now that's my kind of a reward!
I'll get the post!
Hey, wait, Kid!
What a great reward!
Don't miss your chance!
Anyone who wants to do it
Put your hands up!
I knew it was you!
Hey, Captain Kid!
You look annoying as always!
Scratchmen! What are you doing?!
You made a big mess out of our lair!
I was making sure that you didn't have any snipers.
Anyone would do so when he gets summoned
by his enemy.
See, Killer?!
This is why I told you not to call him!
Calm down. He's a powerful man.
How thoughtless of you to
keep a guest you invited waiting.
You assholes...
I'm gonna kill you both now!
What is that monster?!
Damn! My head hurts!
I guess it's hard to die.
I survived again!
He managed to pull off dying...
That old man, Whitebeard...
I have no choice now, do I?!
Straw Hat Luffy! Trafalgar Law!
Those brats think they're something
just because they brought down a Warlord!
They must realize they messed up my business!
Screw them!
Hey, you!
Tell those idiots from your generation!
"You'd better run!
What we were doing was just playing at being pirates!"
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
Apoo!
That must be Kaido's castle in the back!
Let's cut down on fighting and just get in!
Okay!
Only the troublesome ones are here.
I guess they're all Smile power-users.
Luffy!
This is the Emperor of the Sea's castle!
If we rampage without thinking,
we'll run out of energy...
...to beat Kaido!
Okay!
A-pow-pow!
Feel this great rhythm with all your senses!
What's this sound?
Listen to my Fighting Music!
Scratch!
Bop!
Luffy!
What? I just got punched?!
That guy was Jaggy and the others' ally...
Slash!
Zoro!
I got cut?!
But he didn't have a blade
and I couldn't see his line of attack at all.
What kind of ability does he have?
Boom!
Luffy!
Ch-Ch-Ch-Ch... Check it out!
Whoa-whoa, that was easy! Gee.
It's no use! We gotta get out of here!
Hey, you guys! Don't let them get away!
If you wanna be part of the Tobi Roppo,
work for it!
If we take a beating here...
We won't be able to fight Kaido!
As expected, it's not just their numbers.
They're all strong.
The Tobi Roppo position is mine!
I'm sorry. I'm okay now.
Of course you are.
Don't give me trouble.
There's no point in wearing these anymore.
You're right. It's hard to fight in them, too.
All right.
No more disguises!
Let's break through here quickly!
Okay!
It's no use. You guys are in my range.
Check it out!
Slash!
Zoro!
Bop!
Luffy!
He has the ability to use music as a weapon...
How should we protect ourselves?
Scratch!
Check it out!
I'm gonna kill him!
Don't, Kid!
Your identity will be revealed, too!
I don't care!
What the?
Surprise!
That damn traitor!
You're to blame for everything!
Go to hell, Apoo!
Kid!
Punk...
...Gibson!
Apoo...
One of the supergiant Numbers appears!
He rampages about and the banquet becomes a living hell!
While their plan starts going wrong,
Sanji gets a shock?!
The red-light district filled with temptation!
The closer you step, the more your desire grows!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"His Dream Broken?! The Trap That Lures Sanji!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!