mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Advancing their raid,
Luffy and the others have infiltrated
Onigashima one after another.
It's the New Onigashima Project!
20 years ago, I witnessed Oden's execution...
...the Legendary Hour.
There was no samurai as great as him.
The ones who killed him...
...were Orochi and my father...
...Kaido!
Now that the Akazaya samurai are dead,
someone has to inherit Oden's will!
That's why...
...I'm gonna open up this country!
Let me fight alongside you!
You said you were Kaido's son.
Kozuki Oden was a man, right?
So I became a man, too.
You're really strong.
You remind me of Ace.
"Explosive?!
The Handcuffs that Shackle Yamato's Freedom!"
AN ATTIC
You know Ace?!
Yeah!
He came here once to take Kaido's head.
He talked a lot about you.
I see...
When he and his group were leaving,
I actually wanted to go on
an adventure with them!
Why are you still here?
There's a reason why I can't go.
BACK ENTRANCE, ONIGASHIMA
Oh?
Captain, we won't fight alongside them?!
I have my own purpose.
Come with me now!
Aye-aye, Captain!
Law-dono!
Thank you for everything.
I wish you the best of luck!
Good luck!
Everyone, are you ready?
Of course! I'm glad that I made it!
One cat isn't so great a reinforcement.
What?!
Can you-gara say that after seeing this?!
--What is it?
--Isn't it cool?!
This will fill Kaido with bullets!
Cool...
Kiku, I have so many travel
stories to tell you.
Yes, so do I...
But...
...we must take down Kaido first!
Okay!
Our lives were saved by Oden-sama...
Let's wager those lives tonight!
They're coming!
Yeah!
They're...
They...
...must've been drawn by him!
Is he up there?
I knew you would come...
Though we couldn't find any sign of
samurai warriors entering,
it was hard to believe that
you guys weren't here.
I know how persistent you guys are
more than anyone!
You're really here!
After hiding like rats for 20 years
since the boiling!
Kanjuro...
Did you betray us?!
I won't let you raid us.
Izo, you're back... to
fight this losing battle?
Warriors who fight even after
their heads have been severed... Nicely drawn.
They look just like you guys, don't they?!
Even after you lost Oden as your head,
you loser samurai still wriggle like worms.
So that's who you really are...
What a great actor!
We still have our head!
Our lord is Momonosuke-sama!
Is Momonosuke-sama okay?!
I can't say for sure...
What do you mean?!
He was trying the best he could to escape.
How can I get to Orochi-sama?!
Stop!
I'm not gonna be their burden!
What are you doing?
If you get away,
I can't fulfill my part!
I was just gonna knock him out,
but I overdid it a little...
Thanks to him clinging to life,
I could hand him over to Orochi-sama.
Momonosuke-sama!
You bastard!
How could you do that to someone
who was once your lord and is only a child!
It's nothing compared to
what the Kurozumi had gone through.
And that was only a taste.
On the stage inside,
Momonosuke's public execution
will soon take place!
All we have to do is stop you right here.
Kozuki's history will end
in just a few minutes.
Don't mess with us, Kanjuro!
To fulfill Oden-sama's long-cherished dream
that he entrusted to us,
we endured hardships,
kept low profiles for 20 years,
and even traveled through time!
We're not going to stop here!
If you try to stop us,
we'll just slice you up and carry on!
All right...
In that case, we must fight
and have it out with you here.
We'll not only stop you,
but fight you revenge-thirsty Akazaya...
and eliminate you to the last man!
Kanjuro!
Advance!
Kappa Style!
Yorikiri!
Flower Shuriken!
Go to hell!
You-gara! What happened to your leg?!
It's my Two-Sword Style!
Isn't it cool?
It's cool!
What's the matter, Kiku?
Aren't you gonna attack me?
Before that, let me ask you something.
I know you deceived us...
But we spent a lot of time together, too!
Was it really all a lie?!
Was there no truth to our friendship?!
I'm so happy...
...to hear such compliments on my acting!
You're still trying to believe in me
after a betrayal like that,
which means I played my
role quite well, right?
I told you!
I became emotionally numb
when I was a child!
That's why...
Daimyo!
...I could smile when you guys were around
even though I wasn't having fun!
Open up the Land of Wano!
Run! To Kuri!
And I could cry even though I wasn't sad.
Now I'm filled with feelings again, Kiku.
My acting was perfect, right?
Yes, cry your eyes out!
The more you cry
the more I can feel that my acting was worthwhile.
The more I can feel that I
successfully fulfilled my role.
What's wrong, Kiku?
Cry... cry more!
Come on...
Come on!
Please cease speaking, Kanjuro-san.
To me, Evening Shower Kanjuro...
...was a precious friend.
Prepare yourself.
The wound from this sword
will follow you to your grave.
KIKUNOJO OF THE FALLEN SNOW
A RETAINER OF THE KOZUKI CLAN
Just like snow remaining in the spring,
it'll continue to torment your soul!
Bring it on, Kiku!
Stop!
I won't let you get away!
If you get caught, he'll take you to Big Mom!
No! I'm sure I'll get chewed out!
Help me, you guys!
Shamisen!
What are those monsters?!
They're yokai! The fictional creatures
from the Land of Wano ghost stories!
Oh, no!
Thunderbreed Tempo!
Thanks!
Let go of me!
Shinobu-chan, run!
I can't do that...
If you get caught too,
who will rescue Momo-chan?!
Oh, stop!
Let go of Nami!
Hey! Turn on the Video
Transponder Snail already!
Kaido-san's speech has started!
Shut up! I'm working on it!
I, as Kozuki Oden...
...thought you, Ace's brother, would let me
on board your ship so I gathered info on you.
Hey! Everyone loves Kozuki Oden!
You can't just be him!
I know you're more Oden than me!
What do you mean I'm more Oden than you?!
Although I'm Oden, I'm not free...
Because of these cuffs!
I wanted to set out to sea
along with Ace and the others...
but I've been held captive on this island
since I was eight!
Aren't those for prisoners?!
Yes! My father said they'd explode
if I left the island.
To be honest, I think he might've lied...
Because what kind of a parent
would blow up their own son?!
But when I think of the worst case scenario,
I feel weak at the knees.
Because my father is that jerk!
Do you want me to take them off?
What?!
Do you really wanna fight alongside us?
Even if you're there,
I'll be kicking Kaido's ass right in front of you!
I wish I could do it myself!
I don't know how many times
I've been beaten by him since I was a kid!
Every time I challenged him,
I got defeated!
I see. Okay, I'll take them off for you!
Take them off?
They've restricted my freedom for 20 years...
It's not that easy to...
It's been two years since the Paramount War
against Whitebeard!
It's footage from the Performance Floor!
The world has finally started moving!
They decided to abolish the
Seven Warlords of the Sea
not because the Government went nuts!
It's a sign of their confidence that they
can bring us under control
with the Navy HQ's new force.
But while the World Government
is convinced of that,
we'll collect the most powerful
forces in this world,
the Ancient Weapons!
To accomplish that...
we allied with Big Mom!
Did you...
OLIN THE OIRAN, CAPTAIN OF THE BIG MOM PIRATES
BOUNTY: 4 BILLION 388 MILLION BERRIES
...call me, Kaido?!
Kaido sets into motion to
obtain the great treasure,
but his act of violence shakes Onigashima!
Under the fearful circumstances,
Kanjuro mocks the Akazaya members!
Okiku who cries over his betrayal
draws her sword and charges
to save her comrade who
got lost to the darkness!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Akazaya Face-off! Kikunojo vs. Kanjuro!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!