Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Gear Four!
Bounce-Man!
What are you up to?
Did you infiltrate us by yourself
or with other people?
Who are you?!
You'd better come clean.
What should I do?
Even if I run from them,
I'll be surrounded
by a legion of the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
I guess there's no hope...
Amazing!
Are you gonna talk or not?!
All right.
This is...
...a thank you gift...
...from me!
Duck!
Gum-Gum...
Get out of my way!
Juki!
X...
Kong...
--...Gun!
--...Calibur!
Please!
Let me fight alongside you guys!
"A New Rivalry!
Nami and Ulti!"
He's so fierce, like the God of Fire himself!
X. Drake!
Did he change sides?!
That bastard!
He's that perv who saw...
...Nami-san and Robin-chan taking a bath
the other day in the Flower Capital!
What?! That's unforgivable, Drake!
I can't believe it!
That's very powerful, Nami-san!
Happy punch!
What?!
The shape of Nami-san's body
was like a magnificent mighty river flowing...
He's so despicable!
No, you are!
I'm glad that you didn't drown in the pool of blood
that shot from your nose...
That's right, Robin-chan!
I have hot blood running through my veins!
I don't mind losing everything for you!
Cut it out!
Don't try to pass your nose bleed off as cool!
What's with that guy?!
He wants to fight alongside us?!
How could he say that
after slicing his ally?!
He just turned into something like a dinosaur!
He must be one of the Tobi Roppo officers.
But that's peculiar...
What does he think he's doing?!
Hey, Drake!
Why did you attack one of the Numbers?!
Luffy-san is amazing!
Luffy-san makes you...
...feel very close to him if you're his friend,
JUSTICE
but if you become his enemy,
he'll just leave you in the dust...
That's who he is!
What do you mean?
Luffy-san has the ability to draw people in.
If you deal with him seriously,
I'm sure you'll learn!
Drake-san!
I know you!
You wanna take down Kaido too?!
I can't tell you why,
but we have the same goal!
Don't try to use a shitty trick at this stage!
Luffy!
Just like Hawkins, he became Kaido's subordinate!
But now I got kicked out!
That's why you wanna side with us?!
How can we trust such a shallow bastard?!
Stay away from Luffy, X. Drake!
Even the world of pirates is governed by a moral code!
You can become my ally.
You sure?!
Yeah.
No!
Stay out of it, Captain! You moron!
Either way, I'm just gonna take down Kaido!
You can do as you like too!
Franky! Jimbei!
They say rearguards are
the true heroes of the battlefield!
Hurry to the castle, Luffy!
Okay! I'll leave them to you!
Once a traitor...
...always a traitor!
I can't let you get close to Luffy!
I don't blame you!
Sanji! Let's go inside the castle!
Yeah!
Okiku-chan is waiting for my help!
You two, save your energy and hurry forward!
Yeah! We're counting on you!
The man in the straw hat...
I guess he's the boss of all the pirates and samurai!
Let's go, Big Sis!
--Wait!
--What are you doing?!
Pay-Pay, I can't go on!
I fought against Yamato before
and I'm exhausted!
You're as fit as a flea!
Carry me!
Keep these two away from Straw Hat-san!
Yeah!
Get out of my way, you damn samurai!
You uber-idiots!
You shitheads!
How could you cut in
when Pay-Pay finally carried me like a princess?!
That's not important!
I fought those two in the castle!
That's...
The dinosaur from the Flower Capital!
But...
...who's that cutie right beside him?!
You'll never see Kaido-san again!
Straw Hat!
Special Attack Green Star!
Skull Blast Grass!
Pay-Pay!
Wh-Who is that?!
I'm Nami!
What's wrong with you?!
Nothing I like more than exterminating lizards.
Now prepare yourself!
What are you doing?!
Just leave it to me!
I'll get us out of this situation without fighting!
Lizards?!
Do you want me to pour
lizard poison on you guys?!
Don't hide!
How dare you shoot me!
Who did it?!
Oh, Pay-Pay! It's that tramp!
That's right!
I'm the Great Lizard Buster Nami!
Remember my name!
I said stop!
It wasn't me, but it doesn't matter!
The battle is already on!
Now...
Bring it on!
What?!
What you're saying doesn't make sense!
Look who's talking!
--I won't let you get away!
--How could you hurt Pay-Pay!
--Look...
--...how fast...
...we can run away!
Stop!
I'm counting on you, Usopp!
Protect my Nami-san!
Let's go, Luffy!
To where Kin'emon and the others are!
Yeah!
Hey, Sanji! Cover your ears!
O-Okay!
Listen to my Fighting Music!
Slash!
SLASH
What the hell is this?!
Looks like you got smarter, Straw Hat!
But...
...being unable to hear while fighting
is gonna be hard!
Check it out!
AN INFORMANT OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
(CAPTAIN OF THE ON AIR PIRATES)
SCRATCHMEN APOO
BOUNTY: 350 MILLION BERRIES
Jaki!
Goki!
Juki!
It's so painful to see you guys like that!
Th...
The ten of you...
...have destroyed a lot of towns!
That is why...
...it's not fair to get your asses kicked
while drunk...
...at such a delightful banquet!
Right?!
Don't you think so?! Haccha!
Are you sober now?!
There are ten of them?!
I need more cola!
Whatever it is, any "number" of them is a threat!
Show them what will happen!
If an Ancient Giant really goes out of control!
What? So he's their tamer?!
That jerk!
Just leave it! We gotta go!
All right! Let's go!
Yeah!
It's almost showtime!
There's no room for you to perform!
It's a solo show!
Don't stop, Luffy!
Yeah, all right!
Look how strong he is!
Is he gonna use his comrade as a weapon?!
Oh, no!
Franky! Run straight out of the dome!
If we let the giant thing run wild here any longer,
the samurai won't be able to take it!
I-I got it!
--I'm counting on you!
--Yeah!
Does he think General Franky is a toy?!
I won't get caught!
I'll make him regret...
...thinking that it's a toy!
At least...
if you guys win,
it's more favorable for me than them winning.
Is that convincing enough?!
I see. You're quite honest.
But...
You're still hiding your identity!
We can't fight together with a guy like that!
I'm strong enough to become a Tobi Roppo member!
I'm gonna be a big help to you for sure!
I know that!
Answer my question!
My identity?
I can't reveal it!
If I say it, it will doom us to fight!
I got an idea!
Let's summon more Numbers!
Hey, guys!
Sober up and come here!
Stop doing that shit!
Drake!
Yo! Yo! Drake, I heard!
You're a traitor, right?!
Are you gonna parasitize
that weak little pirate group this time?!
Scratchmen Apoo!
I've always hated him!
I'll kick his ass,
but I'm not doing it for you guys!
Slash!
Zoro!
I got cut?!
Oh, we have something in common.
I don't like him, either!
Our alliance is formed!
What did you say?!
Drake!
Don't think you can get away, you traitor!
I mean, you must be a spy!
You've got another freak coming after you...
Did you think I'd be taken down
with crap like that?
--Ow, ow, ow...
--Hey, stay with me!
Ouch! Dammit!
You're okay! It's a shallow wound!
This is...!
Don't tell me...
...this bullet is...
Defying their inferiority,
the Sulongs keep beating the enemies.
The thriving Minks trouble Jack.
The Akazaya members
raise their fighting spirit even more
and close in on their arch enemy, Kaido!
The 20-year-old grudge burns up like an inferno!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Heroic Blade! Akazaya vs. Kaido, Again Once More!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!