The battle between
the Akazaya samurai and Kaido continues.
Meanwhile, Luffy and Sanji
keep fighting to reach the rooftop of the dome.
Get out of my way!
Come jump into my arms!
And Yamato chases Momonosuke.
Don't underestimate...
...the samurai!
People will talk about how heroically you died
for generations...
I don't mind being forgotten!
My spirit...
...will live on!
Oden Two-Sword Style!
Paradise Totsuka!
"The Power of Ice Oni!
A New Version of the Plague Rounds!"
I feel cold!
Help me!
This is bad... Stay away from them! Get back!
Get away from them!
They're all samurai...
Why are they splitting up?
It must be the "plague"...
Queen!
Drake! You'll eventually end up like them!
You'll freeze and attack
everyone you see, then die!
You deserve to die pathetically like that,
you sneaky rat!
A samurai...
Zorojuro-dono! We'll help you!
I remember you!
Stop! Come to your senses!
You're a samurai!
Don't touch him, Zoro!
Don't, Zoro!
If you touch him, you'll become an oni, too!
You'll turn into an oni just by touching them.
It's incredibly infectious...
Yeah...
And they'll attack anyone!
But we can't fight back since they're our allies!
We don't wanna fight!
It'll alter not just your appearance,
but also your soul...
By that I mean, it'll rip it out!
Just like that time...
When they turned into mummies in Udon...
How could he spread such a virus!
He himself is an oni!
Clank.
Seal off the exits to the other floors!
This floor is doomed!
Clank.
This is my masterpiece!
Plague Rounds: Ice Oni!
Outta my way!
I gotta make it there! Don't get in my way!
You bastard!
I said "Outta my way"!
Wait, Luffy!
What are you doing?!
You're gonna fight Kaido, right?
Save your energy for now!
Take Straw Hat's head!
Outta my way, whirly eyebrow!
Let's do it!
I can handle all of you fools by myself!
Party Table Kick Course!
Damn you! How dare you do that to my men!
Sanji, thanks!
No problem!
What the?!
A gorilla?!
I won't let you through here!
Prepare yourselves!
BRISCOLA
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE GORILLA SMILE FRUIT
Why's the gorilla growing out of there?!
You think so?!
Then why don't you teach me
how a gorilla should be...
...growing out of you?!
How would I know?!
GORILLA PUNCH PUNCH
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Wow! He's not that weak!
The Gorilla Punch is a killer!
I won't let you go even one step farther!
Water Shot!
Oh! Jimbei!
I thought I'd find you around here.
I was right...
Briscola-san!
Are you okay?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey! Are you okay?! Stay with me!
Hey, you!
How dare you attack us!
Okay! I'm gonna fight you this time!
How many times do I have to tell you
to save your energy?!
It'll take a while for you
to beat this many enemies!
Shut up! I'll polish them off in 10 seconds!
Do you have any problem with that?!
Yeah! It'll only take
three seconds if I help!
Only a seven second difference!
Why can't you wait?!
Seven seconds is a big difference!
You're so impatient!
You're too slow!
Hey, don't ignore me! Prepare yourselves!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Fish-Man Karate: Shark Brick Fist!
Briscola-san!
Oh, good job!
You're great, Jimbei!
Luffy!
I'll escort you to the rooftop!
You need to save your energy for now!
Why are you taking control?!
I helped Luffy get this far!
Okay. I'm sorry!
Luffy! Our allied samurai
must have reached by now!
Let's meet up with them!
All right! Got it!
You grasped the situation perfectly!
How could you take down Briscola-san?!
Get them!
Listen. Luffy'll fight
whenever he sees a chance.
Let's keep an eye out!
Sing! Dance!
You gotta have fun!
It's the Fire Festival today!
This Flower Capital is the only place
in the Land of Wano that's prosperous.
Just like the rest of the nation,
the people who live there...
...hide a lot of tension and terror
behind their smiles.
"Someday, the Kozuki samurai
will save this country."
They could carry on...
...because they all believed in
such a seemingly true legend.
It's delicious!
This is why it hits me so hard!
Hey, look at this, Uncle Minatomo!
My dad bought me this!
Oh, is that a candy apple? Good for you!
Mm-hm!
It's so sweet and yummy!
Hi, Minatomo-san!
Oh, hey! Have a drink!
Thank you!
The Fire Festival is fun...
Yes...
It feels like going back to the old days.
The old days, huh?
Sukiyaki-sama was still alive and the daring Oden-sama
was also here in the Flower Capital...
I wish we could go back...
I wish today would never end...
And last forever...
It's delicious!
We get to drink such clean water.
Today's a great day!
The air is fresh...
Let's take deep breaths.
Once the festival ends,
we can't drink...
We have to wait a whole year again!
Damn!
If only Orochi didn't have Kaido's backing!
No one's gonna get killed today.
What a wonderful day!
Orochi will be back tomorrow though!
I'm guessing that the Kozuki Clan
is in a battle right now!
Oh, even if it's not so, that's still interesting!
Keep going!
Okay! They brought back warriors
from all over the world,
and now they're slicing up
Orochi and Kaido at Onigashima,
and creating havoc!
Keep going!
You're allowed to share your fantasy today!
Did we do it?
Did we defeat him?
Yes, we did!
We... We finally took down Kaido!
That Kaido!
The two-sword style we
inherited from Oden-sama...
...brought him down!
That's right! The late Oden-sama
has given us the courage and the power!
We did it, Oden-sama!
Oden-sama, the long night will soon end...
And daybreak will come to the Land of Wano.
When that happens,
please continue to watch over us.
I thank you all!
I really do!
Wait, Kin'emon!
What is wrong, Ashura?!
Don't celebrate yet!
Cut his throat!
It's not over until we decapitate him!
You are right! Finish off Kaido!
I saw Kozuki Oden's shadow
in the spirit you all displayed!
I wouldn't mind if I got killed...
Every time this scar tingles,
I remember that fateful day...
Help!
Father!
Father, help me!
It's me!
If only no one got in our
way at that moment...
But you guys are not Oden after all...
I'll never see another
monstrous samurai like him!
Too shallow!
You guys aren't strong enough
to reopen the scar from that day!
You guys can't do it!
Invisible slashes?!
Kiku!
Due to King's plot, Momonosuke is cornered!
While the officers of the Animal Kingdom Pirates
try to turn the tables for themselves,
the furious Chopper
stands up to stop the atrocities of Queen
who plays with people's lives
using the Plague Rounds!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Won't Forgive Him! Chopper's Determination!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!