Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
You guys...
You fools are already done for!
Kaido!
I am going to take you down!
Luffy is dashing towards
Kin'emon and the others.
Meanwhile, each of his crew members
are fighting a desperate battle.
Everyone, listen!
I'm a doctor!
I'll save everyone, both allies and enemies!
So survive!
Don't let that nefarious man kill you!
How nice, raccoon!
What the...
How impatient...
Momonosuke-kun!
Your survival is the highest priority!
Let's get out of here by ship!
We gotta hurry up!
I have a bad feeling!
What is going on, Yamato?!
Dragons fly through the air
by creating Flame Clouds!
That means now...
...Kaido is lifting up Onigashima!
He's gonna relocate the island
to the Flower Capital!
Th-That cannot be true...
Are you satisfied now?
Kozuki is finished.
The Land of Wano, I mean, New Onigashima...
...will become a stronghold for pirates.
Let's usher in a world of violence!
"A Turnaround Move!
The Flames of Marco the Phoenix!"
The island is hovering?!
Can this be real?!
How powerful is Kaido?!
Damn old man!
What?!
Why?!
How come?!
Marco the Phoenix?!
MARCO THE PHOENIX
A FORMER MEMBER OF THE WHITEBEARD PIRATES
Ohmasa!
Everyone, listen up!
Use fire against Ice Oni!
Warming up your bodies will halt
the progress of the virus!
Oh, thanks!
Only Raccoon-san could figure it out!
But since the virus has already been widely spread,
it's hard to get sources of fire for everyone...
It takes time to produce many antibodies!
Meanwhile, the virus will keep spreading
and more people will get infected!
So please find some!
Fire! Flame!
Sufficient time for survival!
Then let's do this-yoi!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Chopper-san!
It's hot! It's really hot! It's burning hot!
Burn, burn, burn, burn...
I'm gonna be burned to death!
I got what you asked for,
fire and flame-yoi...
Hey! You're burning him!
I thought you were on the same side!
--Marco-san!
--Marco!
They're short-tempered-yoi...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Chopper-san! I'm gonna put it out!
My arm! It's burning!
I'm gonna be burned to...
Or not?!
This flame is...
--Ouch! Ouch! Ow, ow...
--Chopper-san, relax!
Ouch, ouch...
Or not?!
I'm on fire but I'm not getting burned!
It's not too hot or cold...
This flame is comfortably...
...warm...
Dr. Chopper!
We're ready to produce the antibodies!
Come here quickly!
TRISTAN - A NURSE
DOCTOR MIYAGI - A MINK
A swarm of Ice Oni!
Miyagi! Tristan! Run, you two!
Everyone needs the warmth anyway!
Phoenix Pyreapple!
Ouch!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
It's not that hot...
The chill is going away!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
What?!
Wh-What was I...
Ohmasa!
Great! You came to your senses!
I can feel Marco-san's warm-heartedness
from this flame!
But I don't have skin to feel warmth though!
Thank you, Marco!
Your flames are halting
the progress of the virus!
Well, I'm not doing much-yoi.
Like you said, it's raising your body heat.
Once your physical stamina runs out,
you'll turn back into an oni again!
I just bought you a little time-yoi.
Thanks!
That little time is what I needed!
Miyagi! Tristan!
Are you guys okay?!
Y-Yes!
We're fine!
Let's get down to it!
We're gonna help you!
Thank you!
In that tower, I can focus on producing them!
Everyone!
I'll produce antibodies
for both my allies and enemies ASAP!
So stop fighting for now!
I promise...
...I'll save every single one of you!
We trust...
...Raccoon-san!
That raccoon said he'd save us, too...
Yeah... Should we trust him?!
Raccoon-san!
Marco!
That bastard and the damn raccoon
are a pain in the ass!
Hey, guys! Catch the raccoon already!
Don't tell me you fell for the raccoon's words
saying that he'll save everyone!
That was a lie!
Why would he wanna save you guys?!
That shitty raccoon is trying to deceive us
and bring us all down!
But that raccoon...
Don't waver!
If you don't wanna die, get rid of the raccoon
and take back the antibody!
As soon as! Hurry up!
Otherwise...
...I'll kill you all!
Chopper-san,
we want you to focus on producing antibodies.
We're gonna punish those hardheads!
An infection, an antibody,
and a biological weapon...
I see...
I've got a pretty good idea of what's going on-yoi!
Hey, Roronoa!
Don't you have to go and cut Kaido up-yoi?!
If you wanna get to the rooftop...
I'll fly you!
You guys are too good
to be dealing with these small fries.
But we have to help Chopper-san...
Don't worry!
Skeleton-san!
We will protect Raccoon-san!
Samurai of the Land of Wano!
Charge!
Everyone...
Let's do our job!
Okay!
Boss! Everyone! I'm counting on you!
Wait, you bastard!
Apoo!
Give me back the antibody!
If I lose it...
my life will end!
How persistent!
He's tough to beat!
Let's finish one more job!
Raccoon-san, get inside the tower now!
Apoo-san!
X. DRAKE - A FORMER MEMBER OF THE TOBI ROPPO
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
ALLOSAURUS MODEL
That fool...
Drake! You scumbag!
Drake-san?!
So he completely changed sides!
Dr. Chopper!
Let's get down to it! We gotta hurry!
Roronoa Zoro...
If you can trust me as your ally,
let me handle this and go ahead!
Looks like you have a knack for
betting on the right horse.
FOURTH FLOOR, INSIDE THE CASTLE
Sanji! Sanji!
Where is he and what is he doing?!
Sanji might have sensed a powerful enemy
and is holding them on the third floor!
You're right!
My Color of Observation Haki
isn't good enough yet!
I can't even sense Sanji's presence anywhere!
If he really did sense a
powerful enemy's presence,
then maybe he's mastering
the Color of Observation Haki!
Do you sense anything, Jimbei?!
Yeah...
There are so many of them...
And...
...they're all strong!
You're right...
Seems like one of us should
remain on this floor!
I'm gonna draw their attention so go ahead!
I'll fight, too!
Fish-Man Karate!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Just go!
Okay!
Remember we still have to make that toast!
Jimbei!
Yeah, that's an important promise...
I'll fight you guys as much as you want!
How scary!
Don't get so fired up!
As a former Warlord, you sure are strong!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
Here we go!
General...
...Left!
...Launcher!
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER
INSIDE THE DOME
Now it's a total mess!
General...
...Cannon!
Get back, guys!
How dare you shoot that thing like crazy!
Don't push your luck!
Well, don't you look great!
A triceratops!
SASAKI - A MEMBER OF THE TOBI ROPPO
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
TRICERATOPS MODEL
So you're a dinosaur!
Just give up!
It's the strongest creature that ever lived!
The strongest creature?!
Just the thing to test my strength!
This pirate made of iron!
Iron Pirate!
Feel the power of
the world's strongest robot General Franky!
Super!
I'm gonna tear you apart and scrap you!
You can't destroy the glitter of Wapometal!
They're the Tobi Roppo!
ULTI - A MEMBER OF THE TOBI ROPPO
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
PACHYCEPHALOSAURUS MODEL
PAGE ONE - A MEMBER OF THE TOBI ROPPO
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
SPINOSAURUS MODEL
Where did they go?!
I'm so frustrated-arinsu...
I'll crush her damn head-arinsu! That bitch!
You stupid monkey!
You're gonna learn what an instant kill means-arinsu!
Pay-Pay!
It'll only take a second!
I'll tear apart
and beat the hell out of that brat and Komainu too-rinsu!
Hihimaru!
Hold them there for three minutes!
He hasn't learned...
A monkey will be a monkey
till the day they die!
It's been three minutes now!
I hope he got away safe...
Hihimaru!
Why did I get so heated over a monkey?
We spent too much time on him-arinsu.
We've got to hunt them down now-arinsu!
FORBIDDEN STOREHOUSE, INSIDE THE DOME
It's safe in here...
Where are we?
It's a storehouse.
I'm afraid we can't get off
of this island anymore.
We can hide out here for a while
since we won't be seen by anyone.
Shinobu! Are your wounds okay?!
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm sorry I let you down.
What are you saying?! I am grateful for you!
I am still alive thanks to you!
No... It's more than I deserve!
You shouldn't move yet!
He is right! You should be resting!
Then please allow me to accept your kind offer
and get some rest...
Yamato...
Call me Oden or Father.
What is this?
A statue of a dragon.
It used to be at the entrance of the island,
but my friend broke it, so it was abandoned here!
Your friend?!
Yes...
Several years ago,
he came to kill my father!
The man who once came to
kill Yamato's father, Kaido.
A pirate named Ace
invaded the New World wrapped in flames!
Kaido's son Yamato who was in despair
over his unfulfilled desire confronted him!
Ace's fire that devastated Onigashima
lit up Yamato's disappointed heart!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Yamato's Past! The Man Who Came
for an Emperor of the Sea!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!