iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
"A Faint Memory!
Luffy and Red-Haired's Daughter Uta!"
Say goodbye to everyone
who stands against us
No one has the power to stop a change
that comes through music
No, you can't stop magic
Close your eyes and
you can see the future before you
What's that song?
Every note I sing is bringin' you closer
to your purpose
You don't know?
It's popular around the world.
Once your there don't let go
You wanna play a real game,
unfurl the chain
It's an amazing melody that makes
your heart beat wildly before you know it.
Melody strung out like
we're walkin' on a tight rope
Don't wanna cry, don't wanna try,
wanna forget
I don't have a heart though.
Just let me live inside a dreamland
Wanna be free!
This song may cheer you up...
And let a brand new era dawn
...even when you're about to
die of cold on a snowy mountain.
I know that we can
Create a New World!
You're scaring me, Robin.
We can choose the way of our future
Try a brand new path
If I change the worldc
This boundless music brings transformation
Messages in song
Reach even further
This dream will come true
I believe in you
The show will start soon...
Say goodbye to everything
that's weighing you down
Transcend beyond reality to
colorful worlds of music
We need to keep on rising
My singing voice will echo
around the world.
Close your eyes and take my hand
we're runnin' together
We don't have to live like this,
I know we can all do better
I sing for liberation
You wanna play a real game,
unfurl the chain
Melody lighting up the path to new horizons
Don't wanna cry, don't wanna try,
wanna forget
Just let me live inside a dreamland
Wanna be free!
And let a brand new era dawn
I know that we can
Create a New World!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
Bang!
Ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba...
It's you again!
Sorry, Mayor.
Idiot!
Stop fooling around,
and why don't you help
the other villagers sometimes?
Nope!
Don't say it with a smile!
Stop eating!
--Well, I found it on the ground.
--Luffy.
Luffy, I bet you're hungry.
You can eat these.
Do you want these?
Let me spar with you.
If you win, you can have them all.
Ouch!
Yes!
I win!
You can have half.
Have some more.
Don't spit seeds at me!
You sank like a rock as always.
You can't become
a great Navy soldier like that.
I'm not gonna become a Navy soldier!
You must become
the strongest Navy soldier in the world.
I don't want to!
I'm gonna live more freely than that!
Uta...
Oh, that's cute!
Thank you, Shanks!
How do I look?
Uta, sing a song for us.
--Let me present to you!
--Uta! Uta! Uta!
She's the diva who enchants the world!
Uta!
This is a concert venue with
famous artists from all over the world.
And I'll be...
...the headliner!
The audience is very excited.
I said the audience is very excited!
Forget it. It's my bad.
Shanks...
Shanks, what are you doing?
Is that for me, too?
No.
Even though you're my daughter,
I can't give you this.
What a cheapskate!
Don't say that.
Look.
That's the Goa Kingdom.
We'll be based there for a while.
Why does grandpa's punch hurt like this?
I'm not gonna become a Navy soldier!
I'm gonna get out of this village
and do something big!
Is that a pirate ship?
What a lovely place. There's nothing.
Windmill Village is
a remote area of the Goa Kingdom.
What?
Are you guys pirates?
Yes, we are.
Do you have a problem with it?
If so, you can tell me.
I'm Captain Shanks' daughter, Uta.
If you're pirates, go away!
Or what? Are you gonna fight us?
Stop it, Uta.
We're not here to fight.
I didn't know there was
a tough sheriff in this village.
Who are you?
I'm Shanks, the captain of this ship.
If you trouble us,
I'll make you pay for it.
Shanks! I wanna become a pirate!
Stop saying that to me every day.
Being a pirate isn't so nice.
But I heard pirates are
really strong, fun, and free!
Whoa-whoa, who encouraged him?
Meat!
Let me tryout again today.
Again? Why don't you give up already?
I'll pass it this time!
All right.
Where's the coin?
I'll let you aboard if you guess it right.
Then, this one!
This?
What?
He failed again.
--He has no chance.
--Boss is terrible.
The answer is...
That's not fair!
Guess where it is.
In your mouth!
No!
Then, open it.
See? Not here.
Hey, you.
Don't get so close to Shanks.
I said don't get so close to Shanks
in that tacky outfit.
It's not tacky!
Our diva is quite fashionable.
I'm a diva.
I'm the musician of the Red-Hair Pirates
and Shanks' daughter.
Pirates and singing are inseparable.
Oh...
All right, I'm gonna sing one for you.
Okay, okay, okay...
There!
Where did it come from?
Where could this wind be taking us?
I look up to sky hoping for answers
But there is no reply
Where will it end up,
This song that I've been a vessel for?
I look within knowing I'll find the answer
Even on my own
Let's row out to the open sea,
Far as we can go
To the unknown
I've got to keep on dreamin'
No surrenderin'
Go on
Hoist the sail inside my open heart
And let me heed the call of the sea
I've got to keep on singin'
Until you feel it
Just hold on
Oh, the winds will change, I promise you
My voice will see us through
To the end
How was it?
You sing well.
I can sing, too!
The sky in the east is up early
The weather is so fine
There are only fools there
The island in the east is...
That's bad. You suck! You're off pitch!
That'll make the Red-Hair Pirates IQ drop!
Yeah?
Yes!
That's not true!
Shanks!
You two are the same age. Be friends.
I'm nine. Don't group me together
with a seven-year-old kid.
Luffy! Show Uta around Windmill Village.
Are we gonna climb here?
I don't wanna do that!
It's gonna mess up my clothes and hair!
Divas are meant to be the stuff of dreams.
I don't get it.
Of course, you don't.
If you can't even climb an ordinary cliff
like this, how can you help Shanks?
Don't underestimate me.
It's not like I can't climb it.
If you're too slow, I'll leave you behind!
I'm quite impressed with you...
You should be! There isn't even a thing
that you can beat me at!
What?!
Do you wanna compete?
Then I'll teach you a lesson. First...
A height contest!
A cuteness contest!
An arm-wrestling contest!
I win!
You cheated!
A shout contest!
Ya-hoo!
Okay, one more competition!
You always run around like this?
It's boring to stay still.
You're really just a kid.
Why?
Because you haven't realized that
the most fun place in the world...
...is inside myself.
In myself?
Inside myself, I always see great concerts.
This field of grass is my stage.
This open sea is my endless dream.
Let's visit your stages.
I know a lot of them.
What?
Shanks is so strong.
Huh? You've never seen him fight.
I know him like you don't.
He may not look it,
but he has a childish side.
Hmm...
That's a flaw then!
That's the cute part of him!
Cute doesn't sound like a pirate.
But I like it!
I wanna get on board his ship.
What? We still have to walk?!
The Red-Hair Pirates are the best.
Not only Shanks...
...but I love all of his crew!
Sometimes they're too silly though.
I saw them drink too much and sleep naked!
They do that often!
You're not that boring after all.
You, too.
This is my stage.
It's not bad.
But since I've been to so many seas,
I've seen lovelier sceneries than this.
I can't wait to become a pirate
and go to sea, too.
We can choose the way of our future
Try a brand new path
If I change the world
I'm now going to make my dream come true.
I've had it ever since I was a child.
It's a dream of my own.
A New Genesis
Big adventures to the sea and
to the mountain!
Luffy and Uta strengthen the bond between them
through competing with and
encouraging each other.
The diva dreams of a new genesis.
The two pledge to make their massive dream come true,
but the unexpected occurs.
Luffy weeps at the words Shanks tells him.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Pledge for the New Genesis! Luffy and Uta!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!