Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The two dragons, Kaido and Momonosuke,
finally clashed.
Who is that dragon?
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
I am the one who will become
the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
Blast Breath!
That's it, Momo!
"A Legend All Over Again!
Luffy's Fist Roars in the Sky"
Momo!
You bit...
...an Emperor of the Sea!
Is there anything left in the world
that can scare you?!
N...
No!
Momo, go!
You can fly!
Yeah!
Go stop...
...Onigashima!
I'll defeat...
...Kaido...
...at any cost!
Luffy...
...is back in full force!
Do it, Luffy!
Super!
Did you hear that?
What a funny guy.
What he said was no surprise!
Where has he been?
Luffy!
Momo-kun!
Luffy...
Luffy does everything he says
he's gonna do!
Big Bro!
Momo-kun!
Gee...
Do it, Luffy!
Oh boy, Luffy-san, you're so cool!
The Land of Wano
will soon see the dawn, Robin-san!
That's just what you'd expect from
the future King of the Pirates!
Stop running around like a rat!
The time has finally come.
Yeah, this is just the beginning...
Why are you guys laughing like fools?
Your captain...
...lost to Kaido-san once!
It doesn't matter how many times he tries!
Who do you think he's fighting against?!
He's none other than
the future King of the Pirates!
That's not the future we see!
It's an era you can't even imagine!
What did you say, you shitty brats?!
They're overpowering the Lead Performers!
Their techniques have become even sharper!
Luffytaro has a strong presence...
He's like what Oden-sama was to us!
All right!
Is there any chance you could beat me?!
As long as I live,
there are infinite chances!
Big Bro...
Luffy...
I read it in his journal.
When Roger and Whitebeard clashed...
the heavens cracked open!
I have something... to report...
The heavens... cracked...
TREASURE REPOSITORY
Don't say anything.
Who's lucky now-meow?
It's getting exciting, isn't it? Kaido...
Now...
We gotta do this, too!
Thunder Bagua...
I thought I fully defended myself...
...but it wasn't perfect...
Yamao!
Help that gutless fool!
Wh-Who did you call a gutless fool?!
That's enough, Momo!
S-Shut up! I know what I need to do!
Don't think people can change so easily!
Don't worry, Momonosuke-kun!
I got your back!
I'm sorry that I left you earlier!
Yamato!
All right, let's stop Onigashima!
I'm counting on you, Momo!
Hey, Yamato!
Momonosuke!
Where are you going?!
Give me power...
Kin'emon!
Kiku!
I will surely...
Hurry up, Momonosuke-kun!
The Land of Wano is finished!
Give it up, Yamato!
Screw you!
The dawn of the Land of Wano
will break soon!
Yamao!
I know!
You wanna fight him alone, right?
Yeah!
I'm going to die!
M-Momonosuke-kun!
Grab the sky!
Grab?!
Listen, Momonosuke-kun!
Dragons can create clouds!
C-Create?!
You're a dragon now!
You're a giant dragon
soaring through the sky!
You can do it!
I am... a dragon.
I create...
...clouds!
I know!
I know how!
That's it!
Kin'emon!
Take Momonosuke-sama and run!
I will...
...surely come back for you!
Dragons don't fly!
They create clouds and grab them...
...and run through the sky!
That's what dragons are!
I am flying!
The name of these clouds is...
...Flame Clouds!
Oden...
...One-Sword Style!
Feline...
...Frenzy!
You piece of shit!
Canine...
...Cleaver!
Pedro...
I wish I could have a drink with you
while watching the moon...
Master Cat Viper!
Oh, Carrot!
I'm so happy! You're so impressive!
That was amazing, Master!
Yeah!
You finally did it, Master!
Pedro... should be happy!
You-gara guys...
Be careful.
Or you'll transform in a Sulong.
I don't know why...
...but now the moon is totally visible...
This is the rage of all Minks!
I can't believe Jack is...
I didn't expect
a Lead Performer to be taken down...
But that doesn't matter to me!
If you lose,
everyone in this country will be a slave!
They'll have to live for me,
and they'll have to die for me...
This island will soon...
...land at the Flower Capital!
We'll destroy the Flower Capital,
and the Land of Wano will become
a pirate empire called New Onigashima!
Momo will stop this island!
Stop your barking, Straw Hat Luffy!
Keep your cool!
Those brats are helpless!
They can't do anything!
And you...
You must die here!
I'm gonna give you a special treat!
A large stock of explosives and weapons.
If they fall, they will explode.
Onigashima, transformed into a giant bomb,
looms over the Flower Capital!
To stop the flying death fortress
that has begun to collapse,
Yamato and Momonosuke's
top-secret operation is launched!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Situation Has Grown Tense!
The End of Onigashima!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!