iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
As Onigashima closes in on the Land of Wano,
Luffy and the others continue to fight
for the cause they believe in.
There are only a few left...
...but the important thing is...
...whose lives are in them!
What?!
I suddenly got stabbed!
You can only kill me...
...by killing your own captain.
Damn you!
I'm gonna kill you both!
Enjoy each other's company
in the afterlife, too!
Now, do what you gotta do.
Don't hold back!
You're disgusting!
"Death to Your Partner!
Killer's Deadly Gamble"
Straw Sword!
What's wrong? Is it already over?
No way!
Why are you laughing?
I thought you weren't the kind of guy
who laughs so much...
Don't tell me you ate a Smile!
Hey, Killer!
If you eat this,
I'll give you a chance to save your captain!
Now, what are you gonna do?
That's the apex of misery, Killer!
Not only can you not help laughing
even when you're sad...
...but you also can't fight back...
...and you're getting tossed around
like a doll.
Shut up, Hawkins!
I think you're mad...
...but you don't look like it.
If you wanna shut me up,
why don't you fight back?
Now, cut me.
You don't need to hesitate.
Whether it's my leg, arm or head,
go ahead and cut wherever you want.
Do it!
Hey, look!
Killer-san!
You guys!
Your subordinates are here.
Basil Hawkins!
You wagged your tail at Kaido!
How could you betray us!
Please... don't!
I won't give you permission to harm him.
Killer-san! Why can't we help you?!
Because Kid will die!
I have taken your captain as a hostage.
This is Kid's straw doll.
He'll take all the damage that I would have.
If you guys chop off my head,
it's Kid's head that will fall off!
If you stab me in the heart,
it's Kid's heart that will stop.
Screw you!
Seems like he's fighting
against Big Mom now,
it's already a losing battle...
If he takes damage he shouldn't have,
he won't survive for sure.
You're not fighting fair!
Damn! What should we do?!
It wouldn't take much thinking.
You guys don't have many options.
Killer-san!
You can either get chopped up...
...or leave Kid to die and fight me.
I'm not gonna attack you... Never.
That's a boring choice for a sideshow.
In that case,
I have an idea.
Oh? Oh? Oh?
What's the matter?
Damn...
Hey! What's going on?!
Eustass-ya! Fall back already!
Shut up!
I'll give you a cure
that works really well against bad brats!
Punk...
...Gibson!
Rest in peace!
An old bag worrying about me
doesn't make me happy!
You shitty brat!
You should be honored!
How rude!
Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Grill these assholes!
Heavenly Fire!
You need to be punished.
Trafalgar!
That wasn't necessary!
What are these pains?!
Hey, what's wrong?!
What's the matter? Having a migraine?
Kid!
Damn!
Let's go, Hera!
Yes, Mama!
Napoleon!
If it hurts so bad,
I'll chop your head off for you!
Combine!
Thank me!
What are you doing?!
You're useless!
You're in my way, you quack!
Chambres!
Counter Shock!
Mama!
How dare you do that to her!
Stolen Fire!
Mama-Raid!
Now...
A ballsy idiot's head,
and a quack's arm...
Which one should I cut off first?
Damn...
I've finally got to face
an Emperor of the Sea!
If I die here, what was...
...my pirate life all about?!
You're so funny!
Kid!
Eustass-ya!
I think you're gonna die anyway
even if I don't kill you.
Stop!
Stop it, Hawkins!
You're pathetic, Killer.
Don't!
Damn...
What the hell is going on?!
Release Kid!
In return...
...you can have...
...my life!
Killer-san!
Once Kid is gone,
things will get easier for you.
All your miseries
can be traced back to him.
This is so frustrating!
The fires are closing in, too!
We gotta get out of here soon!
If you didn't rebel against Kaido-san,
you wouldn't have to
suffer such a miserable fate...
You don't understand...
Hawkins.
He's right! How could you turn
Killer-san into a cheerful character?!
We're gonna become
a cheerful pirate group, then!
I'll send everyone
who laughs at you to hell!
Kid is the guy who'll surpass the Four Emperors
and become the King of the Pirates!
And we're not gonna die here!
Stop it already!
Hunting the Four Emperors
and becoming the King of the Pirates?
It's a good thing you have big ambitions!
Then don't get in our way!
If I'm in your way,
cut me up with those scythes!
Or you can surrender.
I'll put a word in for you with Kaido-san.
Are you telling me to
come under Kaido's rule?
That's pathetic...
Shut up!
You guys can't fight this battle anyway!
You saw the harsh reality, right?!
Now you know the reason
they've ruled over the sea for so long!
I know your animal instinct
is telling you!
There's no way you can win!
Don't raise your voice...
You're regretting it, aren't you?
The choice you made.
He managed to pull off dying...
That old man, Whitebeard...
You guys are
from the Worst Generation, huh?
You brats are trying to act strong.
If you're gonna become my subordinates,
I'll welcome you...
If you refuse...
Because you were afraid of dying,
but we're still alive.
You'll see which one of us
will regret our choices!
Okay.
Then I'll...
...try not to have regrets.
Let's sink or swim!
It'll only wear you out!
Bye, you shitty brat!
I have two questions for you.
What will happen if you take damage...
...that has nowhere to go?
What are you talking about?
You know how it works!
Kid will take all the damage I get!
As long as his straw doll
is stored inside my body!
I see!
Why did my own arm get chopped?!
All the damage must...
Kid...
...doesn't have...
...a left arm!
Damn! That was unexpected!
The second question.
If I take this away, how many more lives
are left to protect you?
Congratulations! That's the last one.
The pain is gone?
Straw Man Cards!
Death, Upright.
The card of the destruction!
BEHEADING CLAWS
Beheading Claws!
The Strawman got...!
The Strawman won't die!
If the card says so, it'll return!
Reveal the outcome of this battle!
The Tower!
Spin & Sonic!
You did it! Killer-san!
Hawkins-san!
Straw Man Card... The Tower...
It means...
..."the collapse of the old"...
What's wrong?
You suddenly came alive.
Kid!
My body feels light.
Its hidden meaning...
...is "a new path."
Go, Partner!
Orochi's persistence gradually swells
even as he is in a predicament.
That revives the dying Kanjuro's spirit
as an actor.
The castle which is in chaos and surrounded
by hatred transforms into a grand stage
for a once-in-a-generation performance by
the Kurozumi Clan, burning with flames of vengeance.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Shadowy Figure Pulls the Strings!
Onigashima in Flames"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!