Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The armory is at the lowest level
of the basement!
Can I get there in time?
Momonosuke-kun!
Slow the island down even a little bit!
Ring, ring, ring...
I snuck one into your belly band.
Just in case
you die in a gutter somewhere.
Stupid Cook!
Don't bother me!
It won't take long so listen.
We're gonna beat
the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Yeah, of course!
But after the battle,
if I lose my mind,
you must kill me.
Hey.
Okay, I got it.
I'll make sure to kill you myself!
I don't know what the deal is,
but I got something to look forward to!
In that case,
don't die until then!
Thanks.
Clank.
I haven't felt this much pain...
...in decades...
I recognize you both...
Trafalgar Law!
"Captain" Kid!
And Straw Hat Luffy...
You guys really came to take my place...
I can't believe
we can't even study history...
...without taking down
a monster like this!
As long as you live, don't hold back
from exerting all your strength!
Even if I die,
I'll dislodge her from that position!
"The Onslaught of Kazenbo -
Orochi's Evil Clutches Close in"
Damn!
I'll make it painful,
agonizing,
and messy for you.
Guys, make mincemeat of them.
Yes, Mama!
Room!
Oh?
An inedible hamburger patty is done!
Mama, leave the final touches to me.
If we're gonna do it,
I'll make him charred.
I'm gonna burn you to the ground,
bones and all.
When she's that big,
it's just that much trickier.
But sloppier, too!
I'm used to crushing up...
...rude brats!
I'm gonna burn you!
To a crisp!
I'm gonna make mincemeat out of you!
Please take me straight to the castle.
What's the matter-yoi, Izo?
Why are you making the injured fly?
Sorry.
But they said...
...a giant specter appeared
on the second floor and I feel uneasy.
Where has it been all this time?!
I heard the castle's on fire.
Don't drop your guard-yoi!
Yeah!
Hurry up! The monster's coming!
The damn samurai are blocking the exit!
A cannon... Bring a cannon!
The castle is a burning hell!
Secure an exit!
Kick those samurai's asses!
Let's get out of here
or we'll be burned to death!
Let's jump!
Robin-san!
I'm okay, Brook!
It's good for you, Young Master Yamato!
Listen to me!
It's a really, really good plan
that you won't regret hearing!
Apoo! You're doing it again!
Hey, think about it, Drake!
This is good for you!
This is our first and last big chance
to take him down!
Are you gonna suck up to
Yamato this time?!
Young Master!
Stop, Apoo!
I said that I'm busy! Don't come after me!
Fuga!
It's been a while.
But I'm in a hurry now!
If you wanna play, maybe later!
I can't play with you now...
From the second floor of the castle
to all floors!
The giant flame specter
is heading down to the basement!
What? A cushion?
No, these are...
...hairs.
Whose?!
Nico Robin...
They're coming!
Yes.
We won't let you flee!
We have to fight!
What?
What is that?!
--A lump of flames?
--How annoying...
What's that?
It's huge!
The flame specter's intentions
are still unknown!
Fuga, run! It's coming!
The flame specter is descending!
I repeat!
It's descending!
TREASURE REPOSITORY INSIDE THE DOME
Get burned!
Burn!
Burn them all up!
Burn everything to dust!
Kazenbo!
Into the abyss!
The fuse to light up hell!
The Kurozumi Clan's wrath and grudge...
...will now blossom!
The Kozuki bloodline will end.
It's my victory!
No! No! Not enough!
I gotta create a bigger
and stronger Flame Cloud than Kaido's!
This is my...
...Flame Cloud!
Yes! I did it! Luffy! Yamato!
ZORO VS KING OUTSIDE THE DOME
When he pulls that crest,
is that what happens?!
What is he doing?!
Imperial Deep Pride...
...Stake!
Unblockable?! It's like a laser beam!
In ancient times,
this is how Pteranodons...
...hunted their prey.
Damn! I didn't know that!
I gotta hit him somehow
or I'll only be exhausted!
Don't tell me that flame on his back
was also a Pteranodon's feature?
No!
It wasn't?!
How dare he talk to me from up high!
I have to strike him down first!
Three-Sword Style!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
Why is his body so unusually solid?!
I guess both dragons and dinosaurs
are known for their solid bodies?
Yes.
But I'm more than that.
I might be a little unique.
I'll give you the sword fight you want.
I like swords, too.
I've slashed him several times.
Ultra...
...Tiger Hunt!
But he's not bleeding.
He can move his wings.
They're not just for show,
but I haven't seen him flying with them.
The flame on his back is still burning.
I thought that was part of
his Devil Fruit power, but I guess not.
The blood of the Fish-Men or the Giants?
I suppose it's the power of a tribe
that I don't know about...
You're looking for an answer...
Your eyes are confused.
This is not good...
Unless I figure out what it is,
I don't think...
...I can...
...beat him.
What's that sound?
Is that a shamisen? No way.
What's going on?!
Enma is...!
What's that?
The sound of a shamisen?
No way.
Why's anyone playing it
on a battleground like this?
Is it coming from the room next-door?
I-Is it an enemy?!
Who is it?
I don't think
anyone's having a banquet now.
It's too bright and I can't really see.
Ko... Komu...
Komurasaki!
Am I in the afterlife?
Or am I dreaming?
Since that day, there's not a night
that I don't dream about you.
I couldn't forget you!
I could not forget you, either.
My lord.
I am always with you.
If this is a dream, I don't wanna wake up!
Zoro is unable to compete
with King's unpredictable techniques!
While at a disadvantage where even his best blows
have no effect on King,
the raging Enma sucks out his Haki!
This volatile situation will give him hell
whether he advances or retreats.
Will his dream of becoming
the greatest swordsman be crushed halfway?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zoro Faces Adversity - A Monster! King the Wildfire"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!