iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Onigashima is steadily
nearing the Flower Capital.
On it, many fierce battles
are taking place.
I'll make it painful,
agonizing,
and messy for you.
What is that?!
--A lump of flames?
--How annoying...
What is he doing?!
Imperial Deep Pride...
...Stake!
This is not good...
Unless I figure out what it is,
I don't think...
...I can...
...beat him.
Is that a shamisen? No way.
What's going on?!
Enma is...!
My lord.
I am always with you.
If this is a dream, I don't wanna wake up!
"Zoro Faces Adversity -
A Monster! King the Wildfire"
What's that?!
It's moving through the walls!
Into the abyss...
Shoot, shoot!
I repeat!
From the second floor to all floors!
The flame specter that's heading down
to the basement continues to descend!
Descend?!
CURRENT LOCATION / ARMORY
That's not good!
If it keeps descending,
it'll reach the armory!
If that happens...
it'll light up the stockpiled explosives...
I gotta hurry!
Fuga!
I want you to help me with something!
This way! Help me!
I wish we could rest
on this nice soft bed for a little while,
but we should get going.
The CP-0 agents are
just behind the flames!
They'll come after us soon!
Let's hurry up!
Nico Robin...
We won't let you get away...
Smile!
I'm taking a commemorative photo for you!
"Celestial Dragons' Pets
at Kaido's Castle!"
This is a scoop!
Maybe I'll sell this story to Morgans
of the World Economic Journal!
The headline will go like this!
"The Government
That Lost Their Broker Doflamingo...
...Finally..."
Hey! Apoo?!
You're sticking your nose in too far.
X. Drake.
Do you think we don't know
who you really are?
Then try to come up with a cover story!
Such an inconvenience...
...must be erased.
Scratch...
Finger Pistol.
Boom!
Damn!
It hurts!
You Government assassins!
Oh, you're alive.
Shut up! I defended myself
with the Color of Arms, you fool!
I'll make them pay for that!
And you're from the Navy, aren't you?!
Shut up.
Are you in or out?
Well, they started this fight!
No, you did.
Of course, I'm in!
I can do it! I know I can!
Just like Luffy! Just like Luffy, I...
All right!
Stop!
Why suddenly...?!
Enma!
Who authorized you to unleash your power
without permission?!
What's wrong?
Having a falling out?
What?!
What do you want?!
I'll give you a chance.
Do what you want.
Don't underestimate me!
Jackpot!
What?!
I am...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
My promise to Luffy!
Yamato's confidence in me!
And the many lives of the Land of Wano!
I will not betray them!
That is why I transformed myself
and that is why I risk my life!
Where did you go?!
Is that a science thing, too?!
Judge's son!
Hey, don't add fuel to the fire!
It's already burning!
I'll show you hell!
Hell Memories!
That was a good one.
But not quite satisfactory.
I wish I could've seen Germa's suit!
I told you not to add fuel to the fire!
Don't try to act strong, Judge's son!
You asked your friend for help
because you're mentally weak.
If I lose my mind,
you must kill me.
You were calling Pirate Hunter,
weren't you?!
He can't defeat King!
That was close...
If I'd been slow in using the Color of Arms,
I would've died...
Such a huge explosion...
Was he planning on dying with me?
Why is he alive?
Only a guy who wants to sacrifice his life
would do that.
No one can escape death...
So I'm gonna just keep trying
until he dies!
He's a remaining survivor of the Lunarians
who were thought to be extinct!
They're monsters who were able to
survive in all natural environments!
Long ago, they were known as "gods"!
And?
Why did they become extinct?
Huh?! That's something...
...you should find in a history book!
One-Sword Style Iai...
...Death...
...Lion Song!
That didn't work at all?!
That was obviously a stronger attack
than the one that hit you!
A shamisen?
Whoa, wait! Enma!
Imperial Deep Pride... Stake!
Enma! Not now!
I've never seen a swordsman
who is held back by his sword!
Kitetsu III!
That one!
You have to choose that one!
Kitetsu III!
A cursed sword, huh?
You knew?!
No. I can just tell.
You're right.
Starting with the very first one,
all the Kitetsu have been superior swords,
but every last one is cursed!
Many famous master swordsmen
have met tragic deaths
after taking up Kitetsu swords.
These days, there ain't a single person
who uses a Kitetsu.
Because you'll leave this world
even if you use them unknowingly!
I like it! I'll take it!
A-Are you a fool?! I can't sell it!
If you die because of it
then it'd be like I killed you myself!
Then let's do this.
My luck, and this thing's curse...
Let's see which one's stronger.
If I lose, it just means
I'm not good enough to go any farther.
What?!
Stop! It'll take your whole arm off!
Its sharpness is the real deal!
I'll take it.
That Kitetsu looks different now.
It seems like he met a good owner.
Kitetsu III which you wield is my craft.
Is that so?!
Are you gonna die to save your sword?!
That was hot!
Oh, good. It didn't fall off.
Wado Ichimonji.
Sensei!
Let me have her sword!
Yes. You can have it.
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to heaven!
I'm going to be
the world's strongest swordsman!
Squirt.
Hiyori-sama gave you Enma, which I'm guessing
fits oddly comfortably in your hand, doesn't it?
It follows the same logic of
cursed swords.
The weak cannot handle them.
But the biggest reason why it fits comfortably
in your hand is, in a twist of fate,
...that Wado Ichimonji and Enma
were crafted by the same person!
The legendary swordsmith,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo.
It all happened so fast,
so I never really thought about it...
But how did a sword of the Land of Wano...
...end up in a remote region
in the East Blue?
Zoro still can't bring Enma's power
under control and is cornered.
In the midst of despair, a memory surfaces
of an unnamed sword that he once held.
What is power?
The thoughts of the predecessor,
which are embedded in the blades,
now transcend time and space
to pose this question.
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Secret of Enma!
The Cursed Sword Entrusted to Zoro"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!