Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
"The Strike of an Ifrit!
Sanji vs. Queen"
Germa's blood in your veins
is actually making you excited, right?!
I want them to be monsters.
Winning wars is all that matters.
I'll give my children
the ultimate strength!
Whoa-whoa!
It's really a shame about that raid suit.
Stop saying that.
I won't let you forget it!
Because you blew my chance!
--Your chance?
--That's right.
All of you Judge's sons...
...are cyborgs with not just modified bodies
but also hearts.
So it was my chance to
beat up one of them, kick his ass,
and smash him into smithereens
with my scientific acumen!
But since you're here,
let me show you my scientific capability
before you die, Vinsmoke!
Sparking...
...Queen!
Beams from his eyes?!
Don't tell me...
Osome,
is the wound that guy gave you okay?
Chuji!
Osome, what happened?!
You're bleeding! Who did this?!
Are you okay? Let me help you!
How could you do this
to a young girl like her!
Wait! There's been a misunderstanding!
Shut up!
You're from the army of
the Land of Wano, right?!
Yeah...
How dare you do this to your own?!
No! Listen to me!
I'm sure I...
I didn't do anything...
Didn't do anything...
...to her...
I think...
Stop lying!
Osome ran from you!
Get out of here! We're hiding in here!
I can't believe you'd assault
an innocent woman!
That can't be true! I...
You brute!
To hell with cowards!
Just go away already!
I...
That's impossible...
I would never assault a lady...
It stopped bleeding, so I'm okay now.
Oh, that's good.
Is everyone alright?
--It's dangerous to be here!
--Let's retreat farther back!
--Chuji's gone!
--What?!
Blown out by the blast?!
We've got to go!
It could happen again soon!
I...
I don't want to go on without him!
Osome!
Henry...
...Queen!
Was that Niji's move?
That's correct, Vinsmoke!
I'm gonna get you!
How do you rate me?
I did thorough research
on Germa's technology.
I can replicate
all of you brothers' moves!
Stop lumping me in with them!
I was actually gonna show it to you
after you transform yourself!
If I knock you down in the suit,
I could prove to Judge...
...that I'm a better scientist than he is!
I don't care about
the rivalry between you two!
Don't be so mean!
Winch Queen!
How's that? Did it work?
I guess you were familiar
with that one, too!
Hey! You guys are the culmination of
Judge's technology!
His magnum opuses, right?!
Then, let me have a little more fun!
You're so weak without the suit...
As a final touch,
I'm gonna break you into pieces
and send you to hell!
Vinsmoke!
It's not over yet.
My arm!
You damn brat!
I warned you.
Don't mention their names in front of me!
Are you trying to take away
my freedom of speech?!
You're so impertinent!
And another thing.
Suit or no suit,
the one getting knocked down...
...is you!
Flanchet...
...Strike!
Do you still think
you have the upper hand?
It seems like you forgot
that I sent you flying earlier...
Bien Cuit...
...Grill Shot!
But I'm sure that one was effective.
We've been fighting for so long,
so you must be getting weaker!
Damn you...
On the Performance Floor,
you kept telling me to wait,
and running around pathetically!
You can laugh at me all you want, Queen.
I...
...have already accepted my fate.
I'm not the same guy you saw before!
How are you different from before?!
After all, you refused to become
a cyborg with a heart of ice,
so you can't beat my power
which surpasses Judge's technology!
Say what you want.
Maybe one day,
I'll be a cold-blooded monster...
...without even realizing it...
If I continue to refuse it,
I may die helplessly like a dog...
But...!
Right now, I just wanna take you down!
And that's it!
Cut the crap!
My science is invincible!
The strongest! The greatest!
The best in the world!
A weakling like you...
...can't take me down!
How's that? Next one is your move!
Stealth Black!
I can see you but you can't see me!
This is so stealthy!
You're even able to replicate that...
This is it!
Your back is completely unguarded,
Vinsmoke!
What?! He disappeared, too!
But he doesn't have the suit!
He became invisible
just by moving at high speed!
He'll eventually run out of energy
and show himself!
If I can hide myself until then,
and take him out with a next single strike,
it'll be my big victory!
What a stupid tactic!
Damn Queen...
He's completely erasing his presence
despite his gigantic body!
What is this mouse doing here?
Chuji!
You're okay!
She's...!
Hurry up!
We don't know
when they'll begin to fight again.
Osome!
I can't believe
that tramp is still moving!
That "divine punishment" earlier
wasn't enough?!
Where did you go, Vinsmoke?
I'm not Kaido's subordinate!
I'm just a geisha
brought from the Flower Capital!
Osome! What is she doing here?!
She turned down my request
saying she had a headache and was in bed,
but she looks alive and kicking!
I tried to be a good customer for her
and be nice, and she got so cocky! Damn!
How could you fool me?!
Now that Komurasaki-tan is gone,
you're my number one!
I won't forgive you!
For lying to me
and turning me down dozens of times!
This is divine punishment!
Please let me go!
Punitive justice. Cause and effect.
It's only natural!
This is punishment!
Seems like you needed more pain, Osome!
If you're still not sorry
for what you did...
My ideology...
My beliefs...
I was afraid that Germa's power
would change everything about me.
I can't tolerate anyone who hits a woman!
It didn't occur to me at that moment...
I was a fool!
What I gained...
Exoskeleton, muscle strength,
and mobile speed.
Those are just additional tools
in my arsenal...
By overlaying the exoskeleton
with the finely honed Color of Arms,
my leg will be covered in
tougher and hotter flames!
Ifrit Jambe!
Better acceleration! Heavier weight!
And the mystery is solved!
Men should never hit women!
That's been common sense
since the age of dinosaurs!
It was you, wasn't it, Queen?!
You scum! Collier!
What?! Queen-sama?!
Don't worry! Leave him to me!
O-Okay!
Vinsmoke Sanji!
Basses Cote!
Paleron!
Jumeau a Bifteck!
Tendron! Flanchet!
Queue! Poire! Jarret!
Germa, Germa, Germa.
That power is so Germa!
Shut up already!
That name has nothing to do with me now!
I can see...
...how that evolving power will turn out
and your future, clearly!
You said you were not gonna
become Germa...
No matter how much you deny that power,
you're still Judge's son!
You are...
...a failure.
You only bring shame to the Vinsmokes.
It's a shame that
I don't want anyone to know!
You were born a cyborg!
So what?!
No matter what my past may have been,
I'll carve out my future
with my own hands and legs!
So your stupid provocations
can't confuse me!
I'm a first-rate cook of the sea.
No matter how much my body mutates,
I am who I am!
And I'm also a pirate...
...Black-Leg Sanji of the Straw Hats!
I haven't given you the final touch yet!
I can even cook scrap meat
to be delicious!
Bring it on, Queen the Plague!
Shut up!
My science is the number one in the world!
I'll get rid of all the rest at once!
Boeuf Burst!
Fly away, you asshole!
Don't worry.
He looks alright.
Chuji! I'm so relieved!
He was in danger, so...
Th-Thank you!
He was making food for rats again!
Don't leave her side.
How is...
How is your...
...wound...
Are you okay?!
Somebody!
Bring me the first-aid kit now!
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life
and he was born with
the spark of humanity.
That's why you're...
...kinder than everyone else!
The Battle of the Pleasure Hall
in the Left-Brain Tower in the Skull Dome.
The winner is Sanji.
We'll feature Zoro taking on King the Wildfire,
the invincible man and
a Lead Performer of the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
You'll see all the details of the fierce battle!
If he defeats the Lead Performer, it'll give us
a glimpse of Luffy becoming the King of the Pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Recapping Fierce Fights! Zoro vs. A Lead Performer!"
Luffy's gonna become the king of the seas!