Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy and Kaido
continue their match to the death.
Suddenly, changes have occurred to Kaido
after he drank alcohol.
Why are you drinking booze now?!
You are drunk!
Even if you lose,
don't use an excuse like "I was drunk"!
You idiot!
Why would I wanna make myself weak?
I've accepted you!
It's fun to be drunk...
Stop trying to sober me up!
Be more creative!
It's not entertaining at all!
No, that's impossible!
That fruit became a mere legend,
even to us now.
It hasn't awakened for centuries.
Then, why did the World Government...
...bother giving that Devil Fruit
another name?!
To hide its name from history.
"The Destruction of the Alliance?!
Fire up, the Will of the New Generation!"
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Oh, fire!
Undo the Paralysis Jutsu! Raizo!
Both of us will die!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Get out of here!
Yeah!
Damn... It's hot!
It's too hot, we're gonna die!
Hey, look!
Watch out!
The ceiling's gonna collapse!
We're doomed!
You guys shouldn't be here...
Get out of the castle now!
You're Jimbei from the Straw Hats!
You're so strong!
The fire hasn't spread that way yet!
Save yourselves!
Yeah, we're indebted to you.
You should not die, either.
Uh-huh! Go now!
Okay! Everyone, hurry up!
Yeah!
Why did the fire spread like this?!
Dying in battle is one thing...
But there will be so many casualties
from the fire!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR
It's too dangerous to be here...
We better get away.
Dr. Chopper?
What the...
I changed back!
Doctor... That's great!
Now you're freed from the side effect of
a longer gigantification time!
Yeah!
I didn't expect to become Baby Geezer...
The effects are great,
but so are the risks.
The strong side effect
made me smaller and weaker.
BABY GEEZER CHOPPER
(SIDE EFFECT OF THE RUMBLE BALL)
The strong, unpredictable side effect?
Miyagi... I'm worried about Zoro.
Yeah, because of the "medicine," right?
He had 20 to 30 bones broken
and was battered and badly wounded...
In exchange for
the temporary super healing,
he'll suffer twice
as much as he did before, right?
Yes.
I wonder if he won the fight.
Twice as bad as the severe wound
that immobilized him...
Zoro...
You won't die, right?
Who the hell are you?!
H-Hey...
What's going on? I can't...
...move my body!
Don't do it... Stop...
Don't do it!
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER INSIDE THE DOME
ZORO   FRANKY
Get out of my way!
Where the hell did Zoro go?!
CRAWL SPACE, FIRST FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Damn!
Why is the commander
who served Whitebeard...
...helping those stupid punks?!
Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates!
I'll take your life!
W-Wait! Please!
FIRST-FLOOR BASEMENT INSIDE THE CASTLE
I made a blunder...
They're the Animal Kingdom Pirates
after all...
Kiku... Kin'emon...
I hope they escaped successfully.
Cipher Pol!
Indeed, we're "Aigis" Zero.
We knew you were here, but...
Izo, let's pretend
we never saw each other.
We're not in a position where we can ignore
the remnants of the Whitebeard Pirates...
...for committing a historical crime...
But we only have business
with the Straw Hats right now.
I'm sure we'll meet again somewhere.
No, wait...
CP-0!
ARMORY, BASEMENT OF THE CASTLE
YAMATO
Into the abyss...
Gotta make it in time!
There it is!
And everything...
...will reach the grave.
No, no! Wait! Please!
Namuji...
...Glacier Fang!
If this many explosives blow up,
everything'll be over!
Don't touch the explosives!
Mahoroba!
Stop, specter! Or I'll finish you!
Orochi-sama!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR
Damn!
You ill-mannered shitty brats!
I'll educate you
on the etiquette of fighting!
Trafalgar!
You better pay attention!
Don't mess with your elders...
...who have survived!
Fulgora!
Stop it, Big Mom!
Our bosses can't move anymore!
If they receive any more attacks,
they'll really die!
Give them a break already!
Your subordinates are pitying you.
You're losing your prestige.
Hey, hurry up!
Boss! Stay with us! Is he breathing?!
Medics! Save Captain!
Shut up! This is a battlefield!
You garbage!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
I'll burn even non-burnable garbage!
Let's go, Tristan!
Dr. Chopper?
I'm a doctor!
Doctor!
Gotta treat them now...
Lives aren't garbage!
By the way... I still haven't heard
Kaido's shout of victory yet.
Don't tell me he's still fooling around
with that little punk Straw Hat.
Kaido!
Hera!
Let's go to the rooftop!
Yes, Mama!
I'm tired now.
Let's get it all done at once!
Turning your back on a battlefield...
K-Room!
Anesthesia!
Let's wrap it up!
Mama?!
Mama!
Big Mom is dead!
Tra-guy! What's that gigantic sword?!
I know the earlier attack
worked against you, too.
The penetration itself doesn't hurt.
But...
S-Stop! This is...
Shock Wille!
Mama?!
How dare you do that to Mama!
What the... I'm getting pulled!
You noisy steel beams!
Obey my magnetic force!
Are you still gonna fight, Kid?
I guess you want my head that bad...
You brats!
For some reason, I feel like I'm being
driven by a different purpose right now...
I guess it's about time
for Kaido up there, too...
Even dripping water can hollow out a stone
over time.
No damage?
There's not a single object in the world
that can't be damaged!
PUNK CORNA DIO
Punk Corna Dio!
What the hell is that?!
It's bigger than the gigantified Big Mom!
Hey.
Listen, old bag...
Even if it means death...
We won't let you go to the rooftop!
We'll feature Law and Kid taking on
an Emperor of the Sea, Big Mom!
You'll get to see the two of them
fighting all out in the fierce battle!
We can't enter a new stage of history
without taking down the Four Emperors.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Recapping Fierce Fights!
The Countercharge Alliance vs. Big Mom"
Luffy is the man
who'll become the King of the Pirates!