Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Burn him to death, Misery!
Yes, Mama!
Do it, Eustass-ya!
"Here Comes the Main Act!
Powerful Techniques of Shockwave and Magnetism"
Into the abyss...
Get out of here!
If the explosives blow up,
an awful lot of lives will be lost!
Into the abyss...
I will save everyone's life at any cost!
Because they are all fighting
for the Land of Wano!
I cannot be the only one to lose!
Father...
Mother...
Hiyori...
Watch me!
I will save the Land of Wano!
It is moving!
It is moving backward!
Keep it as far away
from the capital as possible...
I will not let...
...this thing crash into the capital!
Did someone call me?
What?
My head...
Why don't you shut up
and go down already?!
Big Mom was sent flying!
You're not gonna get taken out,
are you, Big Mom?!
Boss Kid!
--He did it!
--Yay!
Yes!
Captain!
It started working, didn't it?!
You shitty old bag!
Hey, Eustass-ya.
That was the second time!
After my powerful strike, you launched
a showy attack and acted like a winner!
I'm not your opening act!
Who cares! Don't say such a stupid thing!
Why don't you attack her first, then?
Give her a huge blow!
I'll finish her off!
Don't tell me what to do!
The ace up my sleeve
will bring the old bag down!
Oh, what comes after the bull?
A hippo? An elephant?
Shut up! Why should I tell you?!
Captain...
How dare he accuse Boss of such bullshit!
Hey, look!
Shockwaves from within...
My ribs must be broken.
Trafalgar's technique is dangerous.
Seems like she likes my technique.
You dickhead! Don't get carried away!
I'll give you life.
Come back to life, my bones!
Yes, Mama!
I'll tell you something. It's no joke.
I'll be out of energy in the next barrage.
I'm gonna finish this with the next shot!
I'm not gonna fail! So I want you to...
I just told you not to tell me what to do!
Prometheus!
Napoleon!
Hera! Let's do it!
Yes, Mama!
I can keep knocking you back all day!
Maser Saber!
It's useless!
Because it's just metal scraps!
You guys are useless!
You squirts! I've sunk hundreds of punks
like you into the sea...
We've reigned for decades!
From when...
...you guys were still drinking milk!
Assign!
"S"!
"N"!
What?!
Mama, get away!
I'm stuck!
What?! She took the tower with her?!
Hey, thanks for putting it on my back!
That's insane!
Damn you!
You crazy old bag!
You brat... Know your place...
Mother's Visit Cannon!
3,000 Leagues of Misery!
3,000 LEAGUES OF MISERY
What the hell is that?!
I won't let you get away!
What's that?!
The attack itself came to life?!
Do it, Misery!
Destroy those punks!
Takt!
Mama?!
K-Room... Anesthesia!
This trick again! Trafalgar!
What's that?!
Damn you!
You've got a lot of balls!
Are you gonna hang on to me?!
Trafalgar!
Captain!
What are you doing?! Captain!
Get away! You're gonna die!
Not yet! Go deeper!
What's wrong?! Are you dead already?!
Puncture...
What?! Stop it!
Wille!
CANDY APPLES
What?!
What is that giant hole?!
What's that hole?!
Burn him to death, Misery!
Yes, Mama!
Do it, Eustass-ya!
What?!
What's that?
Don't make me repeat myself, Trafalgar!
Don't tell me what to do!
Damn you fools!
Bring it on, you little punk!
Do you think you can take me down?!
I'm Big Mom!
That's precisely why
I gotta take you down!
Damned Punk!
The era that you guys reigned over...
...has ended!
While receiving the upstart's raw, powerful attacks,
Big Mom remembers Roger's words!
An adolescent ambition
and a reckless dream.
What will be waiting
at the end of the wild blue sea?
When the sound of the old era is lost,
Kid and Law unleash the last deadly strike!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the New Era! Settled! The Determination of the Brats"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!