iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
To stop Onigashima's explosion,
Yamato gets to the armory.
Into the abyss...
On the Performance Floor, the battle
between Law, Kid and Big Mom continues.
You squirts! I've sunk hundreds of punks
like you into the sea...
We've reigned for decades!
They've already exceeded their limits,
but are still fighting fiercely.
You brat... Know your place...
You crazy old bag!
Destroy those punks!
Takt!
K-Room... Anesthesia!
What's that?!
Puncture...
What?! Stop it!
Wille!
Do it, Eustass-ya!
Damn you fools!
Damned Punk!
The era that you guys reigned over...
...has ended!
"To the New Era!
Settled! The Determination of the Brats"
Who is doing this?!
The capital is going to be destroyed!
Sink, old bag!
Mama!
Big Mom is...!
Your luck has run out!
This is...
...quite impressive!
Hey, brats!
I guess you really, really like me!
You must be getting
to the end of your rope by now.
You probably thought
you drove me into a corner,
but you couldn't finish me off.
You can't defeat me.
Why?! Why hasn't she gone down yet?!
Even all those attacks
can't bring her down?!
Boss!
No way!
Both guys on our side
have reached their limits!
I won't let any of you walk away alive!
Choose...
...what you want to happen to yourself...
...the moment I repel this attack!
Either you forfeit
50 years of your lifespan...
...or stay alive and become my slave!
Life...
...or...
...slave!
That's the Soul Pocus!
Don't freak out! Don't be scared!
If you don't,
your lifespans won't be taken away!
Boss, let's get out of here!
Hurry!
She'll take our lifespans, too!
No, no, no!
Oh, no!
Damn! Don't!
Don't! I don't wanna die!
A dying creature
shouldn't be that powerful!
I'm scared!
Captain, run far away!
What?!
You guys should run.
Cut the crap!
Forfeiting my lifespan?
Becoming your slave?
Stop joking.
How could I get freaked out
by the incantations of a half-dead old bag!
Not even a second of their lifepans
has been taken away!
Don't they feel even the slightest fear
of an Emperor of the Sea?!
Re-Room.
I bet your dying scream will
ring unpleasantly in my ears.
In that case...
Calm.
Hey, Law.
I love you!
This is what the guy who saved me
would do.
You're such a poor loser, emperor.
Let me help you...
...get to hell!
Silence!
The sound is gone!
Silence.
The technique cancels out
all the noise you make.
I can't hear you...
What?! I can't let out my voice!
Mama!
Captain, behind you!
Here's another! Damned Punk!
Mama!
Prometheus!
Hera!
What are you doing?
Come help me!
What?! Big Mom?!
Why can't I hear her?
Nothing I touch makes a sound!
What have you done to me, Trafalgar?!
No!
It'll cause an explosion!
Orochi-sama...
What?! What's happening?!
What's going on?!
What's that?!
What?!
Big Mom?!
Did somebody finally take down Big Mom?!
I have got to do this, too!
I will not let Onigashima fall!
I was this close
to becoming the King of the Pirates...
Those shitty squirts!
Dammit!
When you think about it...
Hey, Roger.
Why did you say that?
Hey, King of the Pirates!
Where did you hide
all the treasure you found?!
You got it, didn't you?!
That legendary treasure!
That great treasure!
The One Piece!
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
The whole world bought it.
Great Pirate Era?
Roger.
It didn't affect you
since you were about to die!
But so many brats have stepped up
across the world...
And we're the ones who're obliged
to deal with those annoying punks!
Who the hell are you?!
H-Hey...
What's going on? I can't...
...move my body!
Don't do it... Stop...
Raizo!
Are you insane?!
NIN
Water!
What?! What's going on?!
What happened?!
Is anyone there?!
Answer me!
Are you listening to me, Roger?
You should've told us before you died!
The One Piece...
Is it real?
What is it?!
Where is it?!
It could be found in this country, too,
couldn't it?
It's frustrating!
Kid!
Law!
I won't forgive them!
Damn!
You better not think...
Not think...
...that this is enough to kill me!
The Emperor of the Sea Big Mom
vs. the New Generation.
The battle on the Performance Floor
inside the Skull Dome.
The winners are...
Ya-hoo!
We won!
...Eustass "Captain" Kid...
...and...
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law.
Boss!
Captain!
We beat Big Mom!
This is a big deal! Extremely big!
I will not let it crash into the capital!
This pain again...
Who is calling me?
Do not tell me you are...
So it is you!
All right!
This will do for now!
I'll leave the rest to you, Luffy!
Nice! Keep it up, Momonosuke-kun!
Yamato, it's you!
Is that the basement?!
Oh, no! It's exposed!
That's right!
One of the bombs exploded
and it ended up like this!
So the explosion earlier
was caused by Big Mom?!
Uh-huh. I managed to freeze everything
before the whole armory exploded!
I see.
I am glad that you are okay!
I am tied up now, so just listen up!
The thing is, it is coming close!
Zunesha!
Zunesha?!
Is that the elephant Oden mentioned
in his journal?!
Indeed!
It was a companion of Joyboy
who committed a crime 800 years ago!
Kaido wails over Big Mom's defeat!
The situation has grown tense
on Onigashima!
The battle for the existence of
the people's homeland enters a new phase!
The melody of the shamisen
played by Komurasaki
embodying the vindictive spirit
of the Kozuki Clan terrifies Orochi!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Moon Princess Echoes!
The Final Phase of the Land of Wano!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!