Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Cipher Pol!
Indeed, we're "Aigis" Zero.
We knew you were here, but...
Izo, let's pretend
we never saw each other.
We're not in a position where we can ignore
the remnants of the Whitebeard Pirates...
...for committing a historical crime...
But we only have business
with the Straw Hats right now.
I'm sure we'll meet again somewhere.
Is it okay for you to die here?
I don't wanna miss another chance to die.
Big Bro... I...
Don't talk. It's bad for your wounds.
We can catch up as much as we want
after the battle.
But...
...I don't think I can...
As your brother,
I won't allow you to give up.
Okay?
Yes.
No, wait...
CP-0!
"Moon Princess Echoes!
The Final Phase of the Land of Wano!"
I am waiting for you...
Momonosuke...
I am waiting for your order.
I am here to...
...fight alongside you!
I had a little talk with Zunesha
a while ago.
That's awesome, Momonosuke-kun.
So you can talk to the elephant.
Just as Oden predicted.
You're the one who'll lead the world
to a new dawn!
But we do not know
the most important part.
By reading Father's journal, I understand
that I have to live no matter what.
But he...
...tore off
the most important page himself!
Laugh Tale...
The Final Island!
What did Roger, Father, and the others
see there that made them laugh?!
I do not understand
the purpose of this task!
Father was not a prophet!
If he were here now, would he say
"Open the borders" like he did before?!
I do not consider myself wise,
so if it puts the people
of the Land of Wano in danger,
I do not want to open the borders!
Am I a coward?!
Yamato!
Carrot! Get inside the dome!
We got our revenge!
But the battle isn't over!
Okay!
I gotta raise my spirits!
It could crash anytime...
Will this island be okay?
I won't let you fall!
You got beat up as always!
I'll pull you up now!
Hey, you're alive, right?!
Zoro!
You're not dead, are you?!
I won't let you die!
Stay with me!
Oh, no... No...
Looks like the castle's gonna collapse!
Where's the exit?! Hamlet!
Count on me, mister!
I'm counting on you!
This is in your hands!
Lives! Important! A safe delivery!
Big Bro...
Live!
If you guys really believe in
Straw Hat Luffy!
You too, Big Bro... You must...
...live...
You're already beat up.
You can't defeat us...
We only have one life.
Let's not waste it...
Finger Pistol!
Shave!
Survive!
Kiku!
Oh, no!
Maha!
Damn you, Izo!
He was gonna sacrifice himself
from the start...
Damn! Why would a remnant of
the Whitebeard Pirates wanna help those brats?!
I gotta find Nico Robin quick.
Ring, ring, ring...
--What now?!
--Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Hey, listen carefully.
It's an Imperial Command
from the Five Elders.
The Five Elders?
They said...
"Erase Straw Hat Luffy immediately"!
ANIMAL KINGDOM BATH
FOREHEAD FLOOR INSIDE THE DOME
Hihimaru... Komachiyo...
Both of you did great.
Hihimaru! Komachiyo!
I wonder if Usopp was able to
meet up with Kin'emon.
Marco!
That's what I expected from
Straw Hat's crew...
You're quite tough-yoi!
Just getting by...
I'm tired from helping people-yoi.
I think I'll rest here for a while.
Really?!
It's really great to have you here!
Boss!
Captain!
We beat Big Mom!
This is a big deal! Extremely big!
Big Mom won't come back again
this time, right?
Mama!
Hey, Zeus!
Who's more important to you,
Big Mom or me?!
You! Of course, you!
Master-sama! Stay close to me!
Stay alert until the end.
Right now, this is...
...the most dangerous island
in the world-yoi!
Luffy... Are you still fighting?
What are you saying?!
Straw Hat is fighting Kaido right now!
Are you telling me to
get in the way of Kaido's fight?!
That's impossible!
We know that it's not an easy task.
But it's too risky
to let him fight the world's finest.
Take a hint.
This is a necessary precaution.
Something that even the Five Elders
are cautious about...
We only know about it through rumors...
Clank.
I can't die without having done anything!
What's so special...
...about that pirate group?
TREASURE REPOSITORY, SECOND FLOOR
Damn! Damn!
Damn!
How long is he gonna make me wait?!
Oh! Komurasaki, don't worry!
We can get out of here soon!
Fukurokuju!
That piece-of-shit ninja!
What's taking him so long?!
He didn't run away alone, did he?!
Ninja have no freedom!
They should live alongside their lord
and die alone!
Did Kanjuro cause that shake earlier?
I hope that was the end of it.
H-Hey!
Komurasaki!
Why are you playing shamisen
at a time like this?!
That's enough!
Stop playing!
We're in a life-or-death situation,
but you even dressed up in a mask!
You've been wearing it this whole time...
Take off that mask!
Are you...
...really...
...Komurasaki?
I thought you had died.
Are you a ghost?!
Have you noticed it? Hey!
How could they...
Those fools!
Linlin has been defeated!
Jaggy and Tra-guy did it?
That's amazing!
Should we prepare for...
...Kaido?
No, not necessary...
If Kaido is the one who'll come down...
I don't have...
...enough energy left to fight back...
Hey, brat!
Do you have a mouth?
Hello?
Can't you talk?
How old are you?
15?!
So young!
Is this the first time
teaming up with Rocks?
He's a good-for-nothing!
Don't trust him.
If you have a problem, talk to me.
My name is Linlin!
I'm the woman
who'll become the king of the seas!
Good to meet you!
Looking back...
you and I have known each other
quite a long time.
Old bag!
I can't believe this happened...
...just as we vowed...
...to go get the One Piece!
TEARS IN HIS BEER
Gear Four!
Snake-Man!
Shut up!
I'm feeling nostalgic here right now!
I... I can't move...
I can't get out!
You were too upset...
so you didn't even notice.
Hey, Komurasaki!
Why are you just watching?!
Get the rubble off of me already!
Damn!
Why can't I transform?
In order to...
...prevent you from transforming,
a Sea Prism Stone nail was stuck in you...
...by me-arinsu...
Why?! What are you talking about?!
I thought that you loved me!
Love? That is funny.
I bear no love towards you.
What?
By a curious coincidence,
the piece you like...
"Moon Princess"...
You've gotten better, Hiyori.
I like that song!
Really?! It's called "Moon Princess"!
I'll try to get even better.
What a beautiful song.
Play it at my funeral.
Hey, Momo! Don't make your sister cry!
You made her cry!
What I said earlier?
I'm sorry. I was just kidding!
You were?!
I'm not gonna die!
...is the piece...
...that my father Kozuki Oden loved.
Every time I play it...
I remember my father's face...
"Father"?!
How could...
...I...
...smile...
...in front of you?!
Gum-Gum...
...Hydra!
I don't care what kind of ambition
you guys had!
I just know that'll make
the people of this country...
...starve even more than now!
This is my final Gear Four!
I won't stop attacking
until I run out of energy!
I can't tell where his punch
will come from!
I'm gonna...
...kick you out...
...of the Land of Wano at any cost!
There is only one enemy to defeat!
With the samurai warriors' wish in his fists,
Luffy fights head on!
Kaido exerts himself in
the pure battle for life!
As the end of the battle nears,
the two grow more determined!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"There is Only One Winner - Luffy vs. Kaido"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!