Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
As the castle is engulfed in flames,
Izo is fighting fiercely against CP-0.
Finger Pistol!
Oh, no!
Maha!
Damn! Why would a remnant of
the Whitebeard Pirates wanna help those brats?!
I gotta find Nico Robin quick.
Ring, ring, ring...
--What now?!
--Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Hey, listen carefully.
It's an Imperial Command
from the Five Elders.
The Five Elders?
They said...
"Erase Straw Hat Luffy immediately"!
What are you saying?!
Straw Hat is fighting Kaido right now!
Are you telling me to
get in the way of Kaido's fight?!
That's impossible!
We know that it's not an easy task.
But it's too risky
to let him fight the world's finest.
Take a hint.
This is a necessary precaution.
Something that even the Five Elders
are cautious about...
We only know about it through rumors...
Clank.
I can't die without having done anything!
That pirate group?!
Gear Four!
Snake-Man!
Gum-Gum...
...Hydra!
I don't care what kind of ambition
you guys had!
I just know that'll make
the people of this country...
...starve even more than now!
This is my final Gear Four!
I won't stop attacking
until I run out of energy!
"There is Only One Winner -
Luffy vs. Kaido"
Raizo!
Are you insane?!
NIN
Water!
W-Water!
Are you whining?
It's not like you.
Serving Orochi who is frightened by the past
and only thinks about controlling people...
...made you weak.
Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
This isn't hot! This isn't hot!
Ow! Ouch! It's hot! It's not!
No, it's... not hot! It's hot!
Nowadays, even we ninjas
should have some freedom.
Fukurokuju!
BATTLE IN THE CONNECTING HALLWAY
The battle in the connecting hallway,
the third floor inside the castle.
The winner!
WINNER: RAIZO OF THE MIST
Raizo of the Mist!
This way! Run now!
Oh, thanks!
The castle's gonna collapse...
Hey! Are you a samurai?!
Why aren't you running?!
You're Luffy-dono's...
I must go now!
You can't fight anymore!
Take a break already!
What a shame... I was all ready...
Hey! Do you wanna die?!
I need a favor!
FIRST-FLOOR BASEMENT INSIDE THE CASTLE
You're on the rooftop, huh?
Straw Hat Luffy...
"Precaution"...
That's the reason you'll get killed...
Why are you doing this, Drake?
Because I believe this is right!
I envy you...
Finger Pistol.
FLOWER CAPITAL
Did you write your wish?
Light up the Sky Boats!
Cool! Cool!
So cool!
--It's floating! Beautiful!
--It's beautiful no matter how many times I see it...
Okay, let's fly it!
Send your wishes to the sky!
Daddy!
Gum-Gum...
...Hydra!
He's bending
the trajectory of his attacks?!
That should be impossible
due to the nature of rubber.
Gum-Gum...
...King Cobra!
Ouch!
Stop it! It hurts!
It hurts so...
...please stop!
DRUNKEN BEGGAR
Are you still drunk?!
Don't think you're the only one
who can predict what's coming...
Let me copy your attack...
DRUNKEN THIEF
Like this?
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
He ate me!
Let me out, you bastard!
Let me out!
Blast Breath!
It's terrifyingly powerful!
The straw hat man is up against
that kind of attack?
Didn't you see Luffy
for a moment just now?!
What?!
Bounce-Man!
That bastard!
I'm pretty much beat up!
He came back.
How much longer will this last?!
This is my final Gear Four!
I don't have much time left now!
Don't fail me, Gear Four!
Oh, no!
I have to take him down soon!
I see.
It's more troublesome than I thought.
The Gum power.
I'll overcome it with my spirit!
Let's enjoy this, Straw Hat!
Shut up!
I've got to take you down no matter what!
The people of the Land of Wano...
...can hardly find drinking water!
They can't eat their fill!
As long as you're here!
Of course they can't,
because they lost the battle.
Thank me for not killing them!
I don't care who you side with...
...but the people of the Land of Wano
are getting used to being losers.
The pacified weak!
The honorable dead!
I've seen a whole bunch of
underdogs who made excuses!
I'm sick and tired of
seeing those resentful faces!
Shut up!
Samurai are strong!
Are they strong?
Or are they trying to act strong?
The winners don't need such praise!
Which one are you?!
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Over-Kong Gun!
Not yet!
I've got to bring him down completely!
While I can still use Gear Four!
Thunder Bellow...
...Bagua!
Don't escape, my energy!
BLOOD-THIRSTY DRUNK
Can you see...
...the outcome that I want?
One more shot!
Let's finish up the story.
If this doesn't work...
Bring it on, brat!
...I'll lose!
Gum-Gum...
...Over...
Thunder Bellow...
Iron Body!
What?!
CP-0?! Why is he here?!
The paramount battle at the Skull Dome
came to an unexpected end.
Deprived of a serious fight, an angry Kaido
confronts the wounded samurai with their defeat.
Now that 20 years' worth of hope
has crumbled before their eyes,
will they be able to find a way out of hell?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Is Defeated?!
The Determination of Those Left Behind"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!