iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
Another name for the Gum-Gum Fruit is...
The Zoan, Human-Human Fruit,
Mythical Type, Model...
..."Nika."
They say that his body
had the exact properties of rubber.
He fought as he fancied,
and made people smile.
Gear Five!
I'm sorry for what the idiot did earlier.
I didn't want to win like that.
No problem.
Let's settle this!
"The Ridiculous Power!
Gear Five in Full Play"
I was sure that you had died.
Me, too!
Since the Gum power is affecting
things other than your own body...
I guess we can assume
your Paramythia has awakened.
But it's a little strange.
That kind of transformation...
...is an exclusive feature of the Zoan type!
What's the deal with the Gum-Gum Fruit?
It's dark and stuffy in here!
You bastard!
Muscle...
...power!
Ya-hoo!
I'm a shooting star! Shooting Luffytaro!
Enjoy, go!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Stop messing around...
Damn you...
Don't fool around!
Take this fight seriously!
Looks like the battle is still on!
Let's go to the roof!
We've got to see what's really going on!
What?
Huh?
What?!
What's that?!
What's going on?!
I do not know!
Kaido got fat!
Did he have a form like that?
Damn! What's going on?
My body is not rubber!
This is fun!
I see two lights!
This game is not over!
Gum-Gum...
...Escape Rocket!
Luffy?!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant!
What?!
Oh?
Who's that?!
Why does he sound like Luffy?!
What?! Is that Luffy?!
Screw you!
Gum-Gum...
...Jump Rope!
Blast Breath!
Ouch!
Unforgivable!
Boss! Look out!
Straw Hat is alive...
So is Kaido.
The situation hasn't changed...
Rather, it's only gonna get worse.
The fire needs to be put out,
but we're in the air, so there's no way.
It's only a matter of time
before the whole island starts burning...
Even if this island...
--Zoro! Everyone!
--...burns down along with all of us,
unless Straw Hat-ya wins the battle,
only Kaido is certain to survive.
You said you didn't have
any energy left earlier...
Are you being a wimp?!
Didn't you say
you dreamed an impossible dream?
You're the one who's being a wimp!
Whether we have a chance to win or not...
I'm not gonna go down
before you and Straw Hat!
The straw hat man held out hope for us!
We can't allow ourselves...
...to give up on it and let it go!
Otama... Don't worry!
The one who will come down that hole next...
...won't be Kaido!
--Luffy!
Straw Hat...
Gum-Gum...
Conqueror of Three Worlds...
...Ragnaraku!
That hurts!
No!
What?!
Why does Straw Hat look like that?
Is that Luffy?! Why is he so big?!
What's going on?!
What is that?!
This is like a comic strip.
Ow, ow, ow...
It was an interesting show, but
aren't you reaching your limit after all?
No?!
You can't take me down.
Shut up!
I'm nowhere near my limit!
I'm tired.
Who the hell are you?!
Oh yeah...
I was on death's door...
This thing really wears me out...
Die in peace.
The story of the battle you guys fought
will be passed down by someone.
I...
...don't want that...
After you die,
all that is left is bones...
It really is Luffy!
His hair and clothes turned white,
so he looked like a different person...
But...
...his voice is fading away!
But it's not over yet.
We can't put an end to it yet, right?
Momo!
Mm-hm!
Tama!
Kin'emon!
Pedro!
GRAVE OF PEDRO
Hey, you'll die.
Do you think I'm afraid of that?!
Beat loudly, heartbeat!
Bring it on!
Yes, this is the beat I wanted!
Look out, Luffy!
What?!
Ouch!
What's wrong with him?!
Turning himself white,
and using both Color of Arms and
Color of the Supreme King,
he's fighting so freely
affecting things other than his own body.
I've never seen something like this!
Follow me! Come follow me!
That's an interesting attack!
Gum-Gum Counterblow!
Playing games with a kid is really...
...tiresome!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
This is fun, isn't it?!
Kaido!
This is pretty powerful and amusing, too!
I can't make up my mind...
What should I call the technique?
Gum-Gum what?
Gum-Gum... Gum-Gum...
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
I'm me!
It's been a while...
This rhythm... Joyboy.
Hey, Joyboy.
It's as if you're actually here.
I'm excited.
This all feels like fate.
I can't help counting on him!
Who am I?
Monkey D. Luffy!
I'll surpass you,
and become the King of the Pirates!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
Onigashima is ablaze!
While the fire closes in on Sanji, Jimbei,
and the others trying to find a way out,
Raizo stands up to the flame
with the ninpo of his lifetime!
Can his regret for not being able
to save his lord in the past
save the samurai on Onigashima?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"No Way Out!
A Hellish Scene on Onigashima"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!