With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo hayaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake jyanaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
Onigashima is engulfed
in inescapable flames!
Luffy and the others' hard fights continue!
What should we do?
The fire can't be put out!
It's gonna be all right,
so don't give up!
It's burning intensely!
Maybe there's no way for all of us...
...to run.
Oh, no. We can't get outside
because the yard is gone.
We're in the air,
so there's no place to go...
The fire and the collapse
and the ladies...
What should we do?
The castle is burning ridiculously!
I wanna save Kin and Kiku,
and myself as well!
Ninpo: Scrolling Jutsu!
The Elephant's Bath!
Restoration!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Run through every part of the castle!
I left everything below in their hands!
So I'll just...
...focus on kicking your ass!
"I Trust Momo -
Luffy's Final Powerful Technique!"
You can do it, Momonosuke-kun!
Create Flame Clouds!
That will not be enough
to sustain Onigashima!
Momonosuke-kun! Flame Clouds!
It is easier said than done...
I cannot do it!
They will not come out!
The future?
But I do not want to be apart from you!
Momonosuke!
Go along with Kin'emon and the others.
Leap 20 years into the future,
and rebuild the Kozuki Clan!
I cannot do it!
Then why will you and Hiyori
not come with us?!
I cannot do it!
Momonosuke-sama!
Your mother is suffering more than you!
This is the land of samurai!
Where shame alone could end your life!
For a man to complain
after a woman set her resolve...
...is mortal shame!
Now let's leap into the future together!
The future of the Land of Wano
rests on your shoulders!
I am only a child...
I am only a child, so I cannot...
...do anything!
With all due respect,
since Oden-sama is gone,
you are no longer an ordinary child!
What?
You are the son of the great samurai!
You will govern this country someday!
Oden-sama ordered me
to open the borders of the Land of Wano!
I shamelessly lived...
...at my lord's expense...
Now is not the time to die!
I am not allowed to just die!
Allow me to speak plainly!
Will you let us have
another chance to fight?!
If I am going to burn to death anyway,
I would rather die
wielding my sword for my lord!
Will you please give us a chance to die
as samurai?!
Momonosuke!
Mother...
I am going!
Yes...
Please live on...
I am too ashamed to face Mother!
Momonosuke-kun?
Stop saying "I cannot," Momonosuke!
You made your own decision!
I am not an ordinary child anymore!
I am the man who will become
the Shogun of this country!
Uh-huh!
I will save the Land of Wano!
Stop! Onigashima!
Wait! No!
No! Do not head towards the capital!
Gum-Gum...
...Lightning!
You mean you can grab lightning?!
How absurd!
What?
What an absurd power...
Gum-Gum...
You bastard!
--You can play around...
--Huh?
...all you want!
But...
A Devil Fruit power
will never conquer the world!
It's amazing how things work.
Just like how Roger
was not a Devil Fruit power user...
Only Haki...
...can trump all else!
Destroyer of Death...
...Thunder...
...Bagua!
To the deceased!
Set sail!
Let go of your Sky Boat!
Steady!
Steady! Steady!
The festival is almost over...
We must return to slave labor tomorrow...
I hope I can survive another year...
Steady!
Reach Father!
A Devil Fruit power
will never conquer the world!
He didn't have one, either...
What?!
What are you doing?!
Damn! Let go of me!
You're only betraying your location!
Dragon Twister...
...Demolition Breath!
Your vulnerability to cutting attacks
hasn't changed.
Come down!
Straw Hat!
Hey, it came off!
Some kind of tremor
pulled the Sea Prism Stone nail out!
Dammit...
I'll at least take you down with me!
Are you watching, Oden?!
I'll take...
...your daughter along with me!
Boss Hyogoro!
I heard Onigashima's gonna fall!
That means he cornered Kaido...
Hey, guys! Which one do you prefer?
If the straw hat man takes Kaido down,
we'll fall and die.
If we survive,
that means Kaido wins!
Oh, that's an easy choice.
I have a kid in Hakumai.
I have a wife in Ringo!
If Kaido gets taken down,
they can live happily ever after!
That would be great!
It's gonna be a good country!
Are you guys crazy, you damn samurai?!
That means you're all gonna die!
That's fine.
Straw Hat-san!
Kick Kaido's ass with all your might!
I don't wanna die! I don't wanna die!
Ow, ow, ow!
I don't wanna die!
The flames!
Don't give up, you fool!
I'm not gonna die!
Mister!
I'm gonna survive no matter what!
You're the best!
Water?!
Kiku! Kin'emon!
I'm not gonna give up!
To be able to drink clean water.
I want to see my mother again.
May my children grow up happily.
For Grandpa to get better.
--You can do it!
--Straw Hat-san!
Defeat Kaido!
Straw hat man, you're truly amazing...
I made a promise!
I'll make this country a place where
she can eat as much as she wants!
We're here to take down Kaido!!
This battle...
...is not only meant to take down Kaido...
To take back...
...the country that stood still
20 years ago,
we fought!
If we can bring smiles back...
...to our families, our children,
and our country,
we...
Hey, straw hat man!
A new dawn will surely come
to the Land of Wano.
Right?!
I can hear...
...your voice!
What are you doing, Straw Hat?
Why aren't you coming down?
Stop! Onigashima!
Hey! Momo!
Let's finish this up!
Onigashima is in the way! Move it!
Look at that...
He can punch a hole in Onigashima.
Stop! Wait, Luffy!
I still cannot...
Momo!
I trust you!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
People's day-to-day lives and their loved ones
were snatched away by Orochi's rule.
They weren't allowed to mourn,
but their hearts desired to be free.
Absorbing people's wishes,
Gear Five radiates!
That smile is a sign of the dawn!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"20 Years' Worth of Prayers!
Take Back the Land of Wano"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!