With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been
lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake jyanaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days
is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
"20 Years' Worth of Prayers!
Take Back the Land of Wano"
Look at that fist...
He can punch a hole in Onigashima!
Momo!
Move Onigashima out of my way!
Do not do it, Luffy!
You can do it, right, Momo?!
Wait! Move Onigashima out of your way?
I...
I cannot do it!
Let's settle this!
I got it.
Bring it on.
That burns!
That's right.
You don't have to grab me!
I'm not gonna run away!
You know something, Straw Hat?
20 years ago,
a hero of this country
was burned to death!
Since then, this country has been lawless!
You guys are the heroes
that they've been waiting 20 years for!
Flame Dragon Torch!
FLAME DRAGON TORCH
You're not going to throw that right hand.
Because you're gonna melt away.
Luffy!
I'm...
...not gonna melt!
I learned from the old man
how to throw a punch without even a touch!
You call it Haki,
but we call it Ryuo in the Land of Wano.
Don't strain yourself!
Allow the unused Haki in your body
to flow to your fist!
I'm gonna knock you down to the abyss!
Gum-Gum...
Rising Dragon!
Bajrang...
...Gun!
Flame Bagua!
What? What's going on?!
What's happening out there?!
Is it Straw Hat-san?!
Straw Hat!
It must be him!
I think it's Straw Hat-san!
Straw Hat-san!
Go!
Please, Straw Hat-san!
Go, Straw Hat!
Please, straw hat man!
--Please!
--Take him down!
Please!
I'm begging you! Please!
I'm counting on you guys!
Run! To Kuri!
Oden... sama!
Don't look back!
Run!
It's easy to guess
where the samurai are heading!
It's Kuri!
The Kozuki Clan's heir is at the castle!
Kill them all! Eradicate the Kozuki Clan!
Exterminate!
Exterminate them!
He had a child?
I'll go finish things up.
Stop!
Don't mess with the Kozuki Clan anymore!
Move!
You can shoot
whoever stands against the Shogun!
Witness how deep
the Kurozumi Clan's grudge is!
Take this!
Suffer!
You stupid Kozuki Clan admirers!
What happened to Oden's wife?!
We confirmed her death in Bakura Town!
No one else escaped from Oden Castle.
Now the Kozuki Clan is gone!
So you Daimyo, choose!
RINGO
Whether to enliven our Land of Wano...
UDON
...or to fight a war!
KIBI
You know what we'll say...
HAKUMAI
That's a nonsense question!
The Kozuki Clan is our only Shogun!
Avenge Oden!
Protect the Land of Wano to the end!
Don't be afraid of the enemies! Charge!
What's that?
Blast Breath!
Don't!
RINGO
HAKUMAI
UDON
KIBI
You guys are so weak!
"Samurai's determination"?
You can't live up to
your title as samurai!
You damn samurai are pathetic!
It must be frustrating for you to lose to me,
who you have looked down on as a fool.
The weak can't protect anything!
You fools! Listen carefully!
From now on, this country will be
tinged the color of the Kurozumi!
Serves you right!
Bring all the young men who can work!
Daddy!
Give me back my dad!
Don't take him away!
D-Don't shoot!
Honey!
I-I'm okay...
Don't worry.
Daddy!
Make weapons nationwide!
Don't rest.
Work yourself to death!
Burn all the useless trash!
Crops won't grow in this soil...
I can't take it anymore...
I'm sorry...
There is no drinking water or food...
What will happen to this country?
Somebody, help! Please!
Somebody, help!
If you wanna live today, work!
You vermin!
Those resources are more important than you!
If you handle them roughly, I'll kill you!
Scream if you want!
No one will come help!
This is an isolated country.
I can't take it anymore.
I'd rather die...
Don't jump the gun.
Winter's coming...
A long, long winter...
Believe...
...what Toki-sama said.
Night...
...is coming again...
Somebody... Please!
Help me!
I can't let my child die...
I can't!
--Fruit!
--Everyone, food!
Apples!
I bet this is a gift
from the Flower Capital!
I'll take some to my mother!
I haven't had anything in a while!
Let's share with everyone!
Thank you very much!
Someone left me an apple.
I'll eat it with gratitude.
Now I can breast-feed you.
Look, Kaido.
Those swine ate
the leftover faulty Smiles!
Eat! Eat!
Laugh!
And follow in Ebisu Town's footsteps!
Even when you're starved or
your family dies, you'll laugh foolishly!
It's only fitting for you maggots!
I'll give you wonderful days of smiling!
Don't start crying suddenly, you tramp!
I'm so sorry!
Stop crying! Laugh!
If you can't,
then die here!
Entertain me.
Excite me!
I said laugh!
That's hilarious!
Let's have a banquet!
Eat and drink...
...as much as you want!
My dad and mom are both dead!
Komurasaki!
Everything was exactly as I wanted it!
You started working at the Pleasure Hall
of your own will, you slut!
Do you wanna get your revenge on me
that much?
Stop playing the victim!
I still remember my grudge against
the Kozuki Clan and what they did to me!
What you're doing is
the same as what they did to me!
I'll kill everyone who rebels against me!
I'm not gonna just die!
Komurasaki!
I'll take you with me!
Let's drink together again
in the next life!
Those eyes!
Don't underestimate...
...my samurai retainers!
Stop!
Listen, guys!
Oden's legacy persists!
They will come!
To bury me!
Stop!
I was despised just for living...
You can't fathom my grudge against them!
Don't take the Kurozumi Clan's
resentment lightly!
I want everything to be destroyed!
"You are the moon unaware of the dawn.
May your purpose be fulfilled
and cast nine shadows on the night
woven of 20 years
and you shall know
the brilliance of the dawn"!
Foxfire Kin'emon and the Akazaya samurai...
I cannot wait to face them!
I will cut them down with a single stroke!
This is a dreadful scene.
MAY OROCHI BE GONE
GET US OUT OF HELL
"Move Onigashima out of the way"?
What should I do?
I was right...
I cannot do it!
I cannot!
I tried many times, but I could not do it!
Momonosuke!
Leap 20 years into the future,
and rebuild the Kozuki Clan!
Mother!
Don't worry. I know you can do it.
Your hard work and dedication
will touch everyone.
Hiyori!
Father!
I'm counting on you.
I have to hold on now!
Or I will bring shame to the Kozuki Clan!
Momonosuke-kun!
Everyone is believing in me!
I am not going to give up!
There! There they are!
Kin'emon! Kiku!
You're still alive, right?!
Don't ever die!
Don't you ever die!
Please, Straw Hat...
Take down Kaido!
If only Kaido were gone!
Please...
Straw hat man...
Our 20-year battle...
Until Kaido is gone...
Until Kaido is gone!
It will never end!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
Kaido and Luffy clash
with their beliefs on the line.
What awaits the Land of Wano,
light or darkness?
The all-out punch closes in
on a throne drenched in blood.
The people who wish for smiles
and a power sustained by laughter
will blow away the long-lasting sorrow!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The World That Luffy Wants!"
I'm gonna become the King of Pirates!