With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
I soar higher than anybody else
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
At times when you're lost somewhere
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
If my heart is also adrift
mitsukete agerarenainda
I won't be able to find you
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
Your kindness, nor your strength
wakatterunda
I already know
yoake no toki sa
It's the break of dawn
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
To the highest point of reach
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
mahi shite waratterundarou
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
With the world as my enemy
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
I stand my ground on quivering legs
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
Go!
Let's fight it out!
Straw Hat!
Is he going to destroy Onigashima?!
Create Flame Clouds!
--Or we'll all...
--Take this!
...be swept up!
I haven't had enough fighting yet!
"The World That Luffy Wants!"
Kaido-san.
Where did you go, Kaido?!
A person's worth is determined
only by war.
You're an embodiment of the force of arms!
I took it all with my own hands...
...and rose to be the Emperor of the Sea.
You're the man, Kaido!
AT AGE 10, KAIDO...
...IS ALREADY THE STRONGEST!
You're making us even stronger!
No one in this world...
...can beat me!
You don't know anything, do you?
Our country can't stop fighting wars...
46 YEARS AGO, VODKA KINGDOM
We must win and steal money
to pay for Heavenly Tribute...
Otherwise,
we'll lose our rights in the world!
We're just tools of this country!
Why does everyone bow down
to those "Celestial Dragons"?
Unchain me!
Why should I receive such treatment?!
You got drafted.
You will become a Navy soldier.
Why would I wanna be
the Government's dog?!
You're more than this country can handle.
Shut up! Don't tell me what to do!
Don't mess with me!
I'll make you pay!
If you turn over Kaido to us...
this country will be granted
the right to participate in the Reverie...
Don't use me for politics!
You'll be betrayed because you're weak.
I'll form the strongest group in the world,
and turn this boring world
into a world of violence.
I'm the strongest!
The way you unified those samurai
with the help of your crew was impressive.
You're a star of hope that
the cowards of the Land of Wano seized upon!
They entrusted their future to you
but what's your goal?
Straw Hat!
You did great.
Well done fighting to this point!
But...
...you can't change the world!
Navy Headquarters! Kaido escaped!
He beat our soldiers
and destroyed the ship!
I repeat! Kaido escaped!
Many are seriously wounded!
This monster is too much to handle!
S-Stay away! Stop!
We caught Kaido!
Kaido escaped!
He did it again?!
That bastard!
He gets caught every time he gets hungry!
Our prison ship isn't a cafeteria!
44 YEARS AGO,
PIRATE ISLAND OF FULLALEAD
--So strong!
--Who is he?!
Hey! This says he's still 15!
This bounty is too high for a kid!
He's a monster!
Hey, shitty brat.
Do you wanna become a pirate?
Rocks said he wanted to see you.
What do you wanna do?
Kaido joined the Rocks Pirates!
They're invincible now!
Kaido, something big happened!
Come on! Let's go to God Valley!
What?!
The Rocks Pirates fell?!
I'll make him pay!
What kind of joke is that?!
They had all those monsters!
I heard the Navy soldier named Garp
defeated them!
They must've had a falling out!
They didn't know how to work as a team at all!
Where did Kaido go?!
Screw that bastard!
It's been 10 years since that incident...
You're an embodiment of the force of arms!
Kaido!
Throughout human history,
resorting to armed conflict has solved
all kinds of problems in the world.
No wonder.
Because humans are animals!
It's only natural for the weak
to fall victim to the strong!
You're totally right.
The remnants of the Rocks Pirates
will come into power!
Weapons will talk!
I got something good for you...
Those "peace-loving" authorities...
...who were merely born as nobles...
Drag them down to the battlefield!
That's what fairness and freedom are!
A person's worth is determined
only by war!
Of course, I'm gonna win!
I don't know where he got it from,
but Yamato mentioned Joyboy's name.
Oden wanted to open the borders
to welcome Joyboy...
If he is the same guy
you're waiting for, King,
then I know exactly who Joyboy is.
Go, Luffy!
Get out of the Land of Wano!
Do not lose heart, Momonosuke!
He will win! Luffy will win!
He will...
...surely defeat Kaido!
I can do it!
That's the spirit!
You'll save the people of the Land of Wano!
Create them, Momonosuke-kun!
Come out, Flame Clouds!
Heed my call!
Hurry up!
Onigashima's gonna fall at any minute!
Please, Luffy!
Finish this battle as soon as possible!
Don't give up!
Fight until the very last minute!
No one in this world...
...can beat me!
You really...
You really have endured a lot.
For such a long time...
Hiyori-sama.
Head to the Performance Floor!
It's hot...
It's coming!
What's this noise?
What is it this time?!
This doesn't look good!
Robin-sa...
Don't give up, everyone!
I'll make it reach you!
Bring the fire under control!
Help!
Save everyone!
Zou's water!
Water!
Everyone's raining down!
Look! Is that...
We'll make it back alive!
--Usopp?!
--Kin'emon!
Okiku-chan!
No!
I'm sorry, Zoro...
Hey, don't get washed away, guys!
Where did this water come from?!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Sanji-san!
Osome-chan!
What is happening on Onigashima?!
The Flame Clouds are disappearing!
Too late! Onigashima's gonna fall!
Help!
Momonosuke-kun!
We gotta stop Onigashima!
You wanna save the Flower Capital, right?!
I will stop it!
I will not allow people to suffer anymore!
Come out, Flame Clouds!
That's amazing!
That's great, Momonosuke-kun!
Stop Onigashima!
Got it! Count on me!
Go!
Violence will dominate the world!
You're gonna fall victim to it!
Shut up!
Straw Hat!
If you lose, you'll pay for it!
Go, Straw Hat-ya!
The strong will live
and the weak will die!
I'm gonna bury you along with your friends!
Shut up!
Starting with the Land of Wano,
I'll take over the world!
DEFEAT THAT SCARY DRAGON
What kind of world can you create?!
Straw Hat!
Tama!
Don't set the bar too low!
I'll make it your everyday life!
By the time we leave this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
Big Bro!
I want...
Luffy!
Charge!
...to create...
...to create the world...
...where my friends can eat...
...as much as they want!
Kaido!
DEFEAT THAT SCARY DRAGON
King.
I know exactly who Joyboy is.
Who is it?
The one who will defeat me!
Then I don't think he'll appear.
"jikan gire sa"
"Time's up"
dareka ga mata waratta
Someone laughed again
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
All right, now hide-and-seek
owari
Is over
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
(1-2-3)
Be tough, there's still time
kakage you
Let's raise it
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
We're young, so we're free
baka na yume
A foolish dream
ikiru
We live it
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
jibun no ashi de Try
Get on our feet and try
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Let's see the ends of the world together
issho nara ikeru Fly
Together we can go and fly
Kaido falls into the abyss.
The citizens continued to light
lamps of hope despite abuse.
The samurai sacrificed their lives
for a new era.
Luffy's strike backed by
the wishes of the Land of Wano
restores their lost freedom and dignity!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Curtain Falls! The Winner, Straw Hat Luffy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!