<i>With weakness as my ally</i>
<i>yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa</i>
<i>I soar higher than anybody else</i>
<i>dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara</i>
<i>It's a pity to linger in a place like this</i>
<i>konna tokoro de tomatte tara</i>
<i>For the things that's been lost will lose their spark</i>
<i>nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru</i>
<i>At times when you're lost somewhere</i>
<i>kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini</i>
<i>If my heart is also adrift</i>
<i>boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara</i>
<i>I won't be able to find you</i>
<i>mitsukete agerarenainda</i>
<i>Your kindness, nor your strength</i>
<i>yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo</i>
<i>I already know</i>
<i>wakatterunda</i>
<i>It's the break of dawn</i>
<i>yoake no toki sa</i>
<i>To the highest point of reach</i>
<i>saikou toutatsu ten ni made</i>
<i>I'll dash through all the way, yeah</i>
<i>ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah</i>
<i>I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all</i>
<i>mahi shite waratterundarou</i>
<i>For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps</i>
<i>ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun</i>
<i>With the world as my enemy</i>
<i>sekai wo teki ni shinagara</i>
<i>I stand my ground on quivering legs</i>
<i>kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru</i>
<i>Keep moving, just a bit more for me</i>
<i>ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure</i>
<i>The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now</i>
<i>saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima</i>
<i>The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now</i>
<i>saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima</i>
<i>Finally, the curtain falls on
20 years of revenge by the Kozuki Clan...</i>
<i>...in the battle above the Land of Wano.</i>
Luffy!
<i>The winner...</i>
<i>Straw Hat Luffy.</i>
<i>"He Returns!
The Shogun of the Land of Wano, Kozuki Momonosuke"</i>
How is it possible?
Run!
No... You're all mistaken...
They're not Kaido!
Kaido is gone!
Stop!
You don't need to run...
I don't think that dragon we saw was Kaido!
If so, there are two dragons?!
I don't understand!
If that wasn't Kaido-sama,
who was that dragon?
Boss Kyoshiro!
Komurasaki-sama?!
Why is she here?!
What's going on in front of the castle?
What's this all about, Boss Kyoshiro?!
You two are famous.
But I wonder if everyone remembers us...
K-K-Kin!
K-Kin'emon-dono!
Foxfire Kin'emon?!
Why?! I thought he died!
In the burning castle that day!
Why is he here?!
Am I dreaming just as I thought?!
Are we in the other world?
Did we die at some point?
Well, I don't care
if I'm dreaming or not...
Seems like something big
is about to happen!
Yokozuna!
Kawamatsu-sama, the Kappa!
Dogstorm-dono!
Raizo of the Mist is here, too?!
Cat Viper-dono and...
Kikunojo-sama of the Fallen Snow!
Boss Kyoshiro, what is this all about?!
Well, Napping Kyoshiro is
an alternate identity to hide my origin!
In actuality, I am...
...a member of the Akazaya Nine,
Denjiro!
No doubt! They're the Akazaya Nine!
They're alive!
Akazaya came back!
I thought all of them died 20 years ago!
What Toki-sama said was true!
It's quite something!
Somebody! Set up a Light-Scroll!
Let the whole country know! Hurry up!
KURI
An image from the capital!
Everyone, go to Bakura Town!
What? What?
RINGO
Something has happened at the capital!
HAKUMAI
Is this about the earthquake earlier?
KIBI
I thought that
the whole region was gonna collapse!
UDON
Hey! Forget about the broadcast!
EBISU TOWN
What? What? What happened?
What is it?!
We're receiving a transmission
from the Flower Capital!
We'll play the Light-Scroll!
--Huh?!
--What?!
Kaido's son?!
Yes, good to see you!
You wanna fight?!
Stop resisting!
Because... What?!
The battle isn't over yet?!
No, no! I'm not your enemy!
I've always read about you guys
in newspapers.
Well, I had my doubts
as to whether many of you were humans,
but actually...
You have horns!
Did you say Kaido's son?!
Nami-san! I'm coming now!
Anyway, I'm gonna join your crew
from now on!
I'm Yamato A.K.A. Kozuki Oden!
It's good to meet you!
What?!
You're gonna join us?!
Mm-hm!
I like that!
I really like that!
What a funny boy.
But we can't accept that
until we hear it from our captain.
I know.
I wonder if Luffy will be alright.
But that battle gave me chills!
The way he fought!
It was like, whack, bam, ka-boom!
It was awesome!
I wish you were there to see it!
Hey, let's get out of here!
Yeah, we shouldn't be here!
They'll do to us what we did to them!
Hey, stop!
Who said you could leave?!
We don't wanna be slaves,
Young Master Yamato!
Stop, or I'll kick your ass!
An escape?!
That's unbecoming of a soldier!
Shut up and stay there, you guys!
--I'll punish you!
--Don't move!
Seems like he's not our enemy.
Oh yeah, what will happen to those two?
My power will be undone
when the same moon rises.
You mean, in a month?
That's right.
Some animals will turn back to normal
after a month...
...but some will stay tamed.
--I see.
--Maybe it depends on their character?
I think they'll choose
whichever is more comfortable.
Neigh!
Master-sama!
I'm happier staying as I am...
Horselina-chan...
I wish for you to stay, too.
But not as a servant.
I want you to stay with me forever
like a mother!
Horselina-chan?!
Master-sama... Thank you very much.
I'm so happy...
Horselina-chan!
You're holding me a little too tight!
Tama and Horselina...
I'm happy for them...
Yeah.
L-Look!
Komurasaki, Kin-san, and the others
knelt down!
Who is that?
It has been...
...twenty years
since my father Kozuki Oden died!
"Father"?!
D-Don't tell me...
I am glad that you lived through...
...the long, hard years!
It has been...
...twenty years
since my father Kozuki Oden died!
"Father"?!
D-Don't tell me...
I am glad that you lived through...
...the long, hard years!
--What?
--I'm confused...
The Fire Festival will not end!
Starting tomorrow,
you can start whatever business you want!
What?! But Orochi will...
You can drink all you want, too!
What?!
Well water will be free of charge!
The factories will not be allowed
to release poison that ruins the land!
The Land of Wano is no place for slavery!
Momo... <i>kun</i>?
You do not need to suffer anymore...
Four more died at the factory today...
Maybe that will be me tomorrow...
Someone has to tell Otama-chan...
Otama-chan, I hate to tell you, but...
...your father and mother are already...
Dad... Mom...
Rest in peace.
I'm going to be okay!
That tickles!
Woven hats for sale!
Does anybody need a hat?!
They're tough and durable!
It's a great deal!
Do you want a hat?!
Sorry, I don't have money.
Hats for sale!
Does anybody need a hat?!
Komachiyo, I'm sorry.
I couldn't sell any hats...
Does anybody need a hat?!
Hats for sale!
A hat! Does anybody need a hat?!
May I have a hat?
T-Tengu-sama?!
Are you an orphan?
Stay strong.
Just a few years more...
When the strong samurai group
named Kozuki returns,
it'll signal the downfall of the demons!
Kozuki?
I will believe!
Kozuki will take down the demons for us!
I will stay strong!
I'm going to be okay!
Otama?
Master-sama?
<i>Tama!</i>
<i>I'll make it your everyday life!</i>
By the time we leave this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
Orochi's tyranny...
...and the days of
being threatened by Kaido are over!
The dependable friends I made
across the sea!
With the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance,
we raided Onigashima!
Kaido, Orochi,
and the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
All the evils
that threatened this country...
We have punished them!
What?!
D-Did you take down those monsters?!
That hateful Orochi is gone?!
What alliance?
I don't need to be afraid anymore?
Yeah...
I can drink clean water!
The hellish days are over...
Finally... Finally...
We will never forget those
who helped us accomplish the raid...
Ever!
Kin'emon, what should I do?
What else should I say?
Just show off a little!
<i>Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!</i>
Is there anything left in the world
that can scare you?!
Th...
The name my father gave me...
...means "peerless"!
If I lead this country,
even the ruined land will turn into Xanadu!
I need you to work
and help me make it happen!
Transcending 20 years of time,
I am here to save you all!
From now on,
I, Kozuki Momonosuke,
will rule the Land of Wano!
Momonosuke-sama!
<i>Mother!</i>
<i>I will keep my promise to you!</i>
<i>Father!</i>
<i>I will follow in your footsteps!</i>
Momonosuke-sama!
The real Shogun family came back!
We were waiting for you!
Momonosuke-sama!
<i>In the skies of the future,
as a warrior sheathes his sword,</i>
<i>flower petals flutter.</i>
<i>This is the famous samurai country.</i>
<i>The 8-year-old handsome man
gazes up to the cherry blossoms at night.</i>
<i>He is more loyal and empathic
than anyone else.</i>
<i>He is not a man of great strength.</i>
<i>The great Shogun of the Land of Wano,
Kozuki Momonosuke,</i>
<i>who will earn his place in history,
now rises!</i>
<i>"Time's up"</i>
<i>"jikan gire sa"</i>
<i>Someone laughed again</i>
<i>dareka ga mata waratta</i>
<i>All right, now hide-and-seek</i>
<i>joutou saa kakurenbo wa</i>
<i>Is over</i>
<i>owari</i>
<i>Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)</i>
<i>ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)</i>
<i>Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)</i>
<i>kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)</i>
<i>Something will change
(We can see it soon)</i>
<i>nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)</i>
<i>Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)</i>
<i>chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
<i>Let's raise it</i>
<i>kakage you</i>
<i>We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness</i>
<i>kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai</i>
<i>We're young, so we're free</i>
<i>osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana</i>
<i>A foolish dream</i>
<i>baka na yume</i>
<i>We live it</i>
<i>ikiru</i>
<i>We'll illuminate the dark path ahead</i>
<i>mienai saki wo terashite yuku</i>
<i>Get on our feet and try</i>
<i>jibun no ashi de Try</i>
<i>Let's see the ends of the world together</i>
<i>sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou</i>
<i>Together we can go and fly</i>
<i>issho nara ikeru Fly</i>
We will tell you all about the bravery
of Luffy-senpai in the battle against Kaido!
Be ready to carve his freewheeling rampage
into your memory!
Big Bro Luffy is having a lot of fun!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy-senpai Support Project! Barto's Secret Room 4!"
Luffy-senpai's gonna become the King of the Pirates!