With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
"The Morning Comes!
Luffy and the Others Rest!"
So Nika...
...finally emerged.
I can't believe two Emperors of the Sea
fell at the same time...
We can't cover this up.
The news will spread around the world
in no time.
The timing couldn't be any worse!
What should we do?
Zou...
Is it true that Zou disappeared?
Yes. Slowly into fog.
What does that suggest?
Then they won't open the borders!
The Land of Wano will stay
as an iron-tight fortress!
I guess they changed the plan accordingly.
Seems like someone smart is in charge.
So it's impossible to take control of them
by sending a big army!
Can you at least...
...bring back Nico Robin?
I will!
CP-0! CP-0!
A jamming signal?
You guys...
Who are you?!
Wait there!
I'm heading your way!
The Kozuki Clan...
The real Shogun family is back!
The Land of Wano is freed
from 20 years of tyranny,
and is going wild
over the Kozuki Clan's victory.
Drake...
Are you...
...a Navy soldier?
I won't tell you!
Did you come to ask that?
You look miserable...
I thought you predicted
that you'd be okay...
...as long as you didn't betray Kaido...
I...
When I saw the monster,
I knew I was gonna die,
so I became Kaido's subordinate.
Kid and Killer, on the other hand,
continued resisting...
...despite certain death!
Even if I foresaw their victory...
how could I...
how could I suck up to Kid
after all this time?
So it wasn't me?
That one-percent thing?
The certain man you predicted was...
That was me...
SEVEN DAYS AFTER THE BATTLE
ABOVE THE LAND OF WANO
Both of them are beat up.
Frankly, there is a possibility
they'll never wake up...
Don't worry.
If we let them sleep for a while,
they'll wake up noisy and full of energy!
Come on! Take all you want!
The safe products from the Paradise Farm
are all ours now!
Take it! Take it!
I'm hungry...
No, I'm not!
Samurai don't get hungry!
Everyone! Don't put away
the Fire Festival decorations yet!
By Momonosuke-sama...
I mean, Shogun-sama's order,
we'll have another festival!
Okay!
Yay!
Starting today,
I'll be teaching this class.
Is Miss Sarahebi gone?!
Why?!
I'm sorry, but I need you to forget
everything that she taught you.
I will teach the history of the heroes
from scratch!
--What?!
--No!
First, let's talk about a fine fellow,
Kozuki Oden!
He was a bad guy, right?!
Truth be told,
that's a false story made up
by a traitor, Kurozumi Orochi!
What?!
I'm gonna talk about
the life of the true hero...
...Kozuki Oden!
This man was very simple and innocent,
and the one-and-only hero!
Shortly after he was born, at the age of zero,
he sent his nanny flying!
Of course, I was surprised!
Komurasaki-sama, the most beautiful woman
in the Land of Wano, is Oden-sama's daughter!
That Kawamatsu-dono the Kappa
saved her from the burning castle!
It's a beautiful story of loyalty!
The samurai who protected her by disguising
themself as a yakuza named Kyoshiro...
...is a member of the Akazaya Nine,
Denjiro!
PARADISE FARM
Do you know who took down Kaido?
TREASURE
Yeah, I heard that
the warrior's name was Joyboy!
Seems like he already left the country...
I wish I could have seen him!
He's a hero just like the God of the Blade!
ETERNAL GRAVES, RINGO
Build temples?
Mm-hm.
Just like Ryuma the God of the Blade,
I want to build one dedicated to Oden-sama
on a hill overlooking the Flower Capital!
Surrounding it,
we will build temples dedicated to Yasuie-dono
and the other Daimyo who fought for the country.
And...
...temples for Ashura and Izo...
Onimaru!
Onimaru! That tickles!
To think, you're alive!
This brings back memories.
You're our comrade too,
since you fought for this country.
Do you want me to ask them to bury us
in the same grave as Ashura and Izo?
Is that okay, Marco-dono?
Of course-yoi.
One's home soil is the best.
That's probably what Izo would want.
I survived again...
So did we...
If we survived
while something happened to our heroes,
it would be too much...
Let's hope they are okay.
I'm hungry...
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not.
Big brother-sama!
Yamato-kun, where are you?!
Luffytaro-san and Zorojuro-san have...
Big brother-sama!
...woken up!
You are still a tomboy...
It does not hurt though...
Booze!
Meat!
Thank you for waiting!
Grilled fish!
More to come!
Luffy! Zoro!
Luffy! Zoro! You are up!
Luffy! You woke up!
Good morning, Luffy!
I'm glad that you woke up!
You shouldn't drink that much yet!
Oh, this is something to celebrate!
Let's get this party going!
Whoa! You two!
Do not eat too much yet!
The whole country was going to
have a banquet when you woke up!
Let us have it today!
Hey, I am Momonosuke!
Momonosuke!
What?!
So you became an adult!
Your body looks strong!
Because of Oden's blood?
Let me punch you.
Do not!
Do not do it!
I won't go full-out!
Your body looks tough!
Onami!
They are bullying me!
Onami, help me!
Stop it!
I-I am still eight years old!
It does not hurt though...
Oh, you're right.
He's tough as I thought.
This is the world of adults, Momo!
You can't hide behind
the privilege of youth anymore!
Here.
You're a child inside,
but you look like Oden outside!
Stop putting a tray on my head
every time you see me!
Your body's very tough!
You have to thank your parents!
You're gonna be the strongest samurai
in this country!
I will work hard on that!
Let's eat! Let's eat!
Oh yeah, Yamato!
Let's take a bath before the banquet!
Your prayer is answered, right?
"Prayer"?
I heard there is a custom in the Land of Wano
to pray to the gods and Buddha,
holding something back
until your wish comes true.
Until you two got better,
I gave up eating and taking a bath!
Oh, really?!
Thank you, Yamao!
I got better thanks to you!
He's such a good guy!
We aren't dirty though.
I wiped your body clean.
Are you happy?
Mosshead! I need to talk to you!
Oh yeah, you...
After the battle,
if I lose my mind,
you must kill me.
Yeah... I...
I came back from hell to kill you!
No, forget about it.
It's good now.
You can't be sane with that silly face!
What did you say?!
Any way you look at it, I look sane!
Die gracefully!
You die, Mosshead!
You told me to kill you!
Gee...
Let's go take a bath.
Oh, Nami.
There's no mixed bath in the castle.
Is it okay if I come with you?
ROCK BATHING TUB, INSIDE THE CASTLE
MEN'S BATH
All right! Let's bathe!
Yeah!
Ya-hoo!
Bathing is the best!
What?! Am I dreaming?!
Y-Yamato! You...
It feels good!
It's great to take a bath together!
We'll have a banquet after this!
That's great!
WOMEN'S BATH
The men's bath is so noisy!
I want to be bewitching like you!
Feels good!
Remember? We used to take a bath
together with Oden-sama and the others.
Though it's uncomfortable for me
to bathe with other men.
Okiku-chan, you haven't changed at all!
I'm older than you now!
Feels good!
It feels really good!
Hey, did you hear?!
They said the banquet is today!
Let's celebrate again!
The revival of the Kozuki Clan!
Let all the regions know!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Now it's fixed.
Yeah, we can set sail.
General Franky is fixed, too!
That one is so cool!
Don't get cozy with the others, guys!
Don't drop your guard
until we sail out safely!
Information must have leaked from somewhere
and reached journalists by now.
We'll be targeted as replacements
for the Emperors of the Sea!
He's right. This is an isolated country,
so people can't see us from outside,
but we can't see
our enemies' actions, either.
Maybe the bounties for our captains
are higher than we've ever seen!
Yes! I don't know where information
leaked from and how...
Apoo!
I know you're the source!
How annoying you are!
The bounties that everyone cares about
have been released!
Do you wanna see them?
It's all there!
Your new bounties and...
...the names of the ones
who'll be called the new emperors of the sea!
I asked, "Where are you now"!
I told you, Sakazuki-san, I'm in the air.
In the air, where?!
Oh, I can see the Land of Wano now.
Don't do anything unnecessary!
Okay?! Ryokugyu!
I understand!
JUSTICE
I really do.
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
The long-awaited dawn excites the people
and toast-making cheers are heard
throughout the Land of Wano.
As the winds of the times blow violently,
news of the defeat of the Emperors of the Sea
sweeps across the sea.
The names of Luffy and the other captains
gain prominence in the world along with some new stars!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Celebration Banquet! The New Emperors of the Sea!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!