yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
With weakness as my ally
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
I soar higher than anybody else
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
At times when you're lost somewhere
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
If my heart is also adrift
mitsukete agerarenainda
I won't be able to find you
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
Your kindness, nor your strength
wakatterunda
I already know
yoake no toki sa
It's the break of dawn
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
To the highest point of reach
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
mahi shite waratterundarou
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
With the world as my enemy
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
I stand my ground on quivering legs
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
"The World That Moves On!
A New Organization, Cross Guild"
FLOWER CAPITAL AFTER THE BANQUET
I cannot believe such a thing happened
while I was away!
Raizo!
Shinobu-san! Don't die!
Stay with us!
Don't worry.
Dr. Chopper has already given them
excellent care.
He said that they'll be fine
if they rest like this.
I see.
That's good...
I cannot believe Raizo and Shinobu
wasted away like this...
It's terrifying sorcery.
Even though we attacked him together,
we ended up like this...
Oh yeah, he said
he was a Navy Admiral-meow...
Water is important for
both the natural world and humans.
You know?
Let go of me!
Mere humans are
no match for Mother Nature!
Can't you get it?
If Kaido were here, I wouldn't be here!
It's sad but Kaido's domination...
...deterred the enemies of this nation!
I don't want to admit it,
but what he said was true.
Kaido was a deterrent
against the enemies of this nation...
It is a shame!
I am sorry!
I was in Kuri
and I did not know that this was happening!
It's not your fault...
The damage was minimal.
Because of Momonosuke-sama's
tremendous efforts!
So don't worry.
By the way, how was Otsuru-san?
Well, Okobore Town caught fire,
and she was badly burned,
but she survived...
Oh, Otsuru-san!
I heard Kin-san came back.
Yes, he did.
He already went back to the capital though.
You're from the capital, too.
You have to go back for him.
Yes. I want to stay with him, too...
Boy... Even after 20 years,
Tsuru has not changed and is still beautiful...
Hey! Such boastful talk about your love life
is not worth even a dog's attention!
Purr-meow-meow-meow!
That's lovely, Kin-sama.
What is wrong, Raizo?!
Do you want something?
I want...
What?
...to be popular, too.
You need to get better first, Raizo!
I want to make kunoichi
pay attention to me...
Oden in the Land of Wano is so good!
This is big-saru!
There you are!
Do you want some oden?
Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper
are calling for you!
There you are, Carrot.
What is it?! Did you call me?
Duke-sama! Master Cat Viper!
We were waiting for you.
DOGSTORM THREE MUSKETEERS
Why don't you-gara become
the ruler of the Mokomo Dukedom?
The ruler?!
Yay!
Okay!
What?!
The ruler?!
I don't want to!
There's no way I can do it!
Please! I'll do anything so forgive me!
The thing is...
...Cat and I decided to stay in the Land of Wano
and as samurai of the Kozuki Clan,
we'll protect Momonosuke-sama.
Purr-meow-meow-meow!
You-gara traveled abroad with Luffy's group,
something few have done,
so I'm sure you have
what it takes for the next generation.
Wait, wait!
There are so many
who are stronger than me!
Of course, there are!
It's our job to guard the country!
I'll support you, too.
It's Duke-sama and Master-sama's decision.
Carrot! Most of all, you-teia carry...
...Pedro's will in your heart.
Pedro...
It doesn't matter how you fight.
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
Everyone has their own turn.
Carrot...
You-gara'll have your turn, too.
So this is my turn?
Pedro...
We're counting on you.
We'll leave Zou
to you-gara youngsters!
Really?
You're our grandfather?
Mm-hm...
I'm Oden's father.
So you really were alive!
I'm sorry.
I was too ashamed to face you guys.
I couldn't save Oden...
And on top of that,
I couldn't save this country.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I wanted to meet you.
Me, too.
Thank you.
You look exactly like Oden, Momonosuke.
Grandfather-sama!
For us who have lost our parents,
just having relatives is so encouraging!
I feel the same.
So please don't apologize!
I am so surprised!
So he was Sukiyaki-sama!
It never crossed my mind!
My heart leaped into my throat.
I am so glad that he is alive!
I knew you guys had noticed.
Who would wear a tengu mask
when there is no festival?
We did not think
you were just another swordsmith.
We thought it would be rude
to refer to it...
Right, Kin-sama?
That is right!
I'm sorry I put you through that...
I can tell you about this country's history,
seeing as I am an old geezer,
but that's about it.
So please don't tell the nation.
Let me go into retirement.
From here on,
the new era is yours to create.
Just the fact that you are alive
gives us strength!
The era...
...we create.
Okay!
Yes, sir!
What?! Pluton is in this country?!
Yes. I didn't get to see it...
But it's here for sure!
That thing really exists?
Is that the one
Franky burned the blueprints for?
Back in Enies Lobby?
That's right.
It's the Ancient Weapon
that has the name of a god.
Pluton.
Pluton?
That's a dangerous thing.
What was this country up to?
Do you want it, Luffy?
No, I don't.
I bet you don't.
But Oden tried to unleash it.
Why?
What? What? An enemy?!
What?
Are you saying that mature women...
...are like weapons?
Who the hell are you?!
Who am I? Don't you recognize me?
Something happened
and I wasted away a little bit...
It's me, Shinobu!
What?!
I like the way you wasted away!
You're looking so good,
it knocked the bones out of me!
I only had bones to start though!
Really?!
Big Bro! Big Bro!
I became an apprentice of Shinobu-chan!
I'll become stronger,
so the next time we meet,
let me join your crew!
Yeah, if you can use ninjutsu!
Okay!
Yay!
I'll work hard
to become a bewitching kunoichi!
Nin, nin!
Wow! Otama, you're so cute!
Gee! You're the best!
I can't believe it...
Pluton is in the Land of Wano?!
First, Poseidon, and now this...
I have to let that person know about this!
A FEW DAYS LATER
Shogun!
There you are.
Reconstruction plans
for each region have been submitted.
Good.
That's the funding estimate.
Mm-hm, thanks.
Shogun!
Proposals to repurpose
the weapon factory sites have come in.
Mm-hm... Let's go.
Shogun! Please give me your opinion
on the reservoir later.
We need to talk about
the meeting with the Daimyo of all regions.
Mm-hm.
Shogun-sama!
Momo!
Hey! Zoro!
Can you teach me sword techniques...
...a little bit?
Luffy? Zoro?
Onami! Usopp!
Sanji!
Chopperemon!
Robin! Franky!
Bonekichi! Jimbei!
Yamato!
Where are you?!
Everyone!
Hiyori! Did you see Luffy and the others?!
They have gone
after saying goodbye to everyone...
I'm sad!
Saying goodbye?
They did not say anything to me...
Momonosuke-sama!
K-Kin'emon! Luffy and the others have...
I just found out!
What?! You, too?!
I checked, and Denjiro and the others
all said goodbye to them!
Why did they not say anything to us?!
That is my question!
I am disappointed in you, Luffy!
I thought we were friends!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Straw Hat-ya. Find another date!
Why?!
Because it's weird!
Setting sail together!
Our alliance is over! We're enemies now!
We've already decided that it's today!
--Us, too!
Trafalgar! You change first!
Right back at you.
I won't change, either!
This is ridiculous.
It can't be helped
that we picked the same day.
Let's choose separate directions!
The Log Pose locked on to three directions!
Northeast, east, and southeast!
Pick one!
--Northeast!
--Middle!
I'm set...
Heading northeast
will get you the farthest ahead.
CALM BELT: NORTHEAST, EAST, SOUTHEAST
LAND OF WANO
Use your brain a little bit! You idiots!
"Middle"?
What are you, kids?
My direction is set.
Why don't you guys
decide the rest yourselves?
Straw Hat, pick one!
One of them says "East."
This one!
It's "East"!
EAST
I lost!
Sorry, guys!
It's dangerous in all directions!
We don't care!
Just help us load, Luffy!
EAST
Damn!
I'm an Emperor of the Sea,
but I lost the raffle!
Look at you go on!
But...
...the one who annoys me the most
for being an Emperor of the Sea...
...is this guy!
Buggy the Genius Jester!
What?! What's this?!
That's Crocodile and Hawkeye!
Why are they displayed
like they're Buggy's subordinates?!
There's no way
that Hawkeye works under him...
If he really has these two men
under his control,
he should certainly be called an emperor.
But he's an idiot! What happened?
It seems like this company
called Cross Guild...
...began to assign bounties to Navy soldiers.
The Navy which was always the hunter...
...now have to worry about
being hunted by civilians.
While we were in this isolated country,
the world has changed quite a bit.
You don't have any complaints
about the direction, right?
As soon as we sail out of here,
we'll be at each other's throats again!
What's this, Trafalgar?
It's a copy of a Road Ponegliff.
You guys have the right to have it, too.
Cheating takes all the fun out of it...
So Kaido had it as I thought...
It's the thing that we made
one of Big Mom's Generals steal...
We must get serious about this too, Kid!
To participate in the battle
for the One Piece...
We need to find
a Man with the Burn Scar, right?
We have almost no leads.
"Burn Scar"?
What's that?
Don't you know?!
That works in our favor!
What?! Tell me!
Hey! Yamato!
Where are you?!
Hey!
Yamato!
Are you not here, either?!
Momonosuke-kun!
I'm here!
Where?
On top of the roof as always?
Okay! I've made up my mind!
Let's go see Luffy and the others!
I...
...will live like Kozuki Oden did!
"jikan gire sa"
"Time's up"
dareka ga mata waratta
Someone laughed again
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
All right, now hide-and-seek
owari
Is over
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
(1-2-3)
Be tough, there's still time
kakage you
Let's raise it
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
We're young, so we're free
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
An as-yet untold story
from before the Straw Hats' departure!
The extermination of Kaido, which started
with one bowl of rice, came to an end,
and Luffy and Otama
eat warm, but sad, red-bean soup together.
What will be their last words to each other?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Time to Depart - The Land of Wano and the Straw Hats"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!