yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
With weakness as my ally
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
I soar higher than anybody else
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
At times when you're lost somewhere
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
If my heart is also adrift
mitsukete agerarenainda
I won't be able to find you
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
Your kindness, nor your strength
wakatterunda
I already know
yoake no toki sa
It's the break of dawn
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
To the highest point of reach
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
mahi shite waratterundarou
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
With the world as my enemy
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
I stand my ground on quivering legs
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
"Time to Depart -
The Land of Wano and the Straw Hats"
These rice dumplings are yummy!
This red-bean soup is so good!
Fish, meat, and vegetables!
They are all good! You gotta try them!
A little while ago...
RUINS OF ODEN CASTLE, KURI
This is the place where Kozuki Oden,
Kin'emon, and the others' graves once were.
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KANJURO     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KIN'EMON     VASSAL RAIZO
The ruins of Oden Castle, Kuri.
ODEN
It was blown away without a trace
by Kaido's Blast Breath...
That's where Oden built his first castle
after he became the Daimyo of Kuri.
Daimyo!
Luffy!
Hey!
Luffytaro-san!
Hi! What brought you all here?
We're here to tell Oden-sama we won.
There are other things
that we want to tell him, too.
Why are you-gara here?
I'm here to see Oden!
I'm sure Oden-sama would be happy
to see the man who saved the Land of Wano!
You think so?
Oden-sama.
Thanks to Luffytaro-dono and the others here,
we were able to bring down Orochi and Kaido,
and take back the Land of Wano.
Along with Momonosuke-sama
who became the Shogun,
we promise you that we will
return this country to what it once was,
where everyone can live in peace.
I wish Ashura and Izo were here, too...
They're here.
In our hearts, along with Oden-sama.
Mm-hm, that's right.
I bet they're having a banquet
in the afterlife now.
Purr-meow-meow-meow!
Oden cooked by Oden-sama
was the most delicious thing in the world!
I remember the taste of oden
that we had together.
Yeah. It tasted even better
after we trained with Oden-sama.
Nice! I wish I could eat it!
Me, too!
Let's ask Sanji-kun
to cook it for us sometime!
We should stock up on
ingredients for it then!
Yeah, please! Buy lots of them!
Luffy-dono.
Are you leaving?
Yeah.
Once again,
we all would like to...
thank you!
What?!
Stop it. We're friends.
Luffy!
Carrot.
Are we saying goodbye already? No, no, no!
I don't wanna say goodbye to Nami!
No, no, no!
--Carrot...
--What's the matter?
We're gonna go home.
To the Mokomo Dukedom!
I'll protect our home
with Wanda and the others!
Miyagi! Tristan!
Thank you both!
Thank you for teaching me
medicine and stuff!
Dr. Chopper, take care of yourself!
As I recall, Carrot-san,
you snuck onto the Sunny
because you wanted to see the sea.
How was it?
It was great!
I was able to see islands
I didn't know about and meet nice people.
There were a lot of scary moments,
but I feel a little stronger than before.
So the adventure I had with you guys...
...is something I'll treasure
for the rest of my life!
Let me do one last Garchu!
Garchu!
It was fun chatting and having a good time
with you in the women's quarters!
Yeah, it was the best!
You too, Chobro!
That tickles!
It makes me happy, Carrot!
Garchu!
Oh yeah. I saw Zoro on my way here.
You did?
YASUIE     PEDRO
PEDRO
YASUIE
Have a drink.
What are you doing?
I wanted to have a drink with him.
I'll pour it for you!
Did you lay the flowers?
What? Mm-hm!
Big Sis helped me.
Zorojuro-san, you are here.
Yeah.
YASUIE
Rest in peace.
Once the nice temple is built,
I'll come to see you every day, Dad!
Then, you're not gonna be lonely, right?
Right? Right?
YASUIE
You're here. Does that mean
the time has come for you to depart?
Yeah.
I'll miss you.
That means I have to say goodbye
to my father's beloved Enma, right?
I guess.
You can't have it back.
Of course not.
Oh yeah, when I fought Kaido with this...
Three-Sword Style!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
I see...
Just as I thought, that sword...
Oden Two-Sword Style!
...is Oden's sword, isn't it?!
I see...
Kaido must have sensed my father.
Maybe...
"Enma that can even cut through
the bottom of hell..." Huh?
I'm impressed with Oden.
Because he had
completely mastered this thing.
But you saved the Land of Wano...
...by skillfully wielding Enma.
No, it's not good enough.
To me, it looks as if Enma is rejoicing...
...to have a new master.
I'll get stronger.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What the hell's this, Kid Fra?!
Boss! Is there something wrong?
Yes, there is!
Huh?! No way!
You bastard!
You asked me if I could check on
the places where you repaired,
so I decided to help you out,
you dumb shit!
It's perr-fect! You thankless pupil!
You should have left me
at least one spot to fix!
You damn fool!
Oh, I'm sorry for that!
So you repaired it perfectly.
That's what I'd expected from
the Straw Hats' shipwright!
Bye! You simpleton!
Take care! You idiot!
What're you talkin' about?!
FLOWER CAPITAL
DRAPER
Hey! What's taking you so long?
Yes! Yes, yes! I'm on my way!
Okay. Thank you for waiting.
Yeah.
How's this?
--What?
--It really looks good on you.
Usohachi-san, you're cool!
He's the most handsome man
in the Land of Wano!
Look this way!
Young lady, do you want something from me?
That's great!
No, I mean...
Oh, you don't need to tell me.
I know. I know.
--This color looks good on you, too!
--What?
--Usohachi-san!
--Hey! Lady killer!
He's a man
who was made to wear the color red!
So hot!
Be careful, don't fall in love with me.
--I mean, no, no!
--What?
I just need plain black cloth!
Lots and lots of it!
What?! Black cloth?
What are you going to use that for?
What? Well, that's...
Don't tell anyone.
What?! Is that so?!
I will provide you with the finest!
Yeah! Thanks!
All right!
That's it for today!
Thank you for the lesson.
Sangoro's Special Soba!
SPECIAL SOBA
--It's good!
--I love the Special Soba!
--Thank you for the meal.
--Thank you!
How is it?
It's great!
That's good.
Oh, Chuji!
How are you doing, you little thing?
Huh? Huh?
What's wrong?
What? Nothing!
Oh yeah...
I still haven't properly thanked you yet
for saving me at Onigashima.
Don't mention it.
I just did what I had to do.
Um, will you come back here again?
Because Sangoro-san's soba
makes me want to work hard tomorrow.
That makes me so happy!
But I'm leaving soon.
What?!
Sangoro-san, I...
Mister.
Love, love, love!
Can I have one?
Robin-chan! Thank you for coming!
I want a hot one.
I got it, Robin-chan!
Um, can I have one, too?
Okay.
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI
Thank you, everyone.
Now take a break
and have some red-bean soup!
Thank you always
for the refreshments, Otsuru-san!
Let's have it!
RED-BEAN SOUP
It looks good!
It's red-bean soup!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all!
Let's dig in!
Yum!
Yum, yum!
Thank you for the food.
Otsuru-san's red-bean soup is the best!
Good! Eat the rice cake, too!
Okay!
It's good!
Tama, eat as much as you want!
Mm-hm!
Tama, what's wrong?
When I think that
I have to say goodbye to you here,
I feel a lump in my throat...
Ace, then Big Bro...
All the people I love leave me...
Tama.
You gave me your precious rice.
I will never forget it!
I will never forget about
Big Bro and the others, too!
Okay!
I gotta go now.
Tama! See you again!
Big Bro! Thank you!
Like you and Ace,
I will get stronger!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Back to the present...
You really made it for me!
But I can't guarantee it'll work.
That's okay. Thanks, Dr. Chopper!
Luffy! We're ready to set sail!
Yeah!
But are you really sure
about leaving like this?
We didn't say goodbye
to Momo-chan and Kin'emon.
Oh yeah, you're right.
We don't need to.
You're so cold, Mosshead.
Shut up, Twirly Eyebrows.
But of all the people in the Land of Wano,
they shared the most adventures with us.
Yeah, maybe it's a little sad
to just leave like this.
Luffy, what do you wanna do?
Don't worry. He'll come!
"jikan gire sa"
"Time's up"
dareka ga mata waratta
Someone laughed again
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
All right, now hide-and-seek
owari
Is over
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
(1-2-3)
Be tough, there's still time
kakage you
Let's raise it
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
We're young, so we're free
baka na yume
A foolish dream
ikiru
We live it
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
jibun no ashi de Try
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
After running wild like a strong wind
and a raging wave,
and granting the Land of Wano its wish,
Luffy departs the capital silently.
Momonosuke can't contain his anger
at the irreverent behavior
that tramples on their long-standing bond.
As the time to depart looms,
what is going through Luffy's mind?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Last Curtain! Luffy and Momonosuke's Vow"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!