"Entering a New Chapter!
Luffy and Sabo's Paths!"
Since I'm on board this ship now,
it's no longer someone else's affair!
I came to follow
such a troublesome captain!
Luffy!
I love it! I love your dream!
Yeah?
It's great!
Whoa-whoa, calm down, Chopper!
When even our doctor's like this,
we're in trouble!
Stop it!
Well, that's so you...
You have to be the King of the Pirates
to make it happen!
But we can get to Laugh Tale
with just one more Road Ponegliff!
Don't say it like it's easy, Franky.
That last Road Ponegliff will be
the most difficult one to find.
Because...
...unlike the others,
no one has found the last one
in all this time...
There are no clues at all.
Will it be hard?
Idiot!
We should just find it!
Our captain's dream is on the line!
That's right!
Let's find it! The last Ponegliff!
Yeah!
NAVY HEADQUARTERS, NEW WORLD
It's me...
Sabo!
Kamabakka Queendom received a call
from Flame Emperor Sabo!
Good!
Where is he?! Find it out at any cost!
No White Transponder Snail
is being used to jam!
He has no measures in place
to block eavesdropping?
It's an emergency call!
He's gonna hang up soon!
We finally got a lead on his whereabouts!
Don't miss this chance!
Things are heating up!
In the Land of Wano,
some of the Worst Generation joined hands,
and brought down
the infamous Kaido and Big Mom!
As a result, the new Four Emperors of the Sea
were declared,
and things started to change significantly
in the New World.
The abolition of the Seven Warlords system...
...led to the foundation of Cross Guild!
The Navy raided Amazon Lily,
KUJA
but Blackbeard came in,
making it a three-way struggle!
On top of all that,
the Revolutionary Army is active these days.
They declared war on the Celestial Dragons!
Their Chief of Staff, Sabo,
assassinated King Cobra of Alabasta!
In addition, Princess Vivi disappeared!
What's gonna happen to this sea?!
Come on! Show us the entertainment
that lies ahead!
HALL OF POWER, PANGAEA CASTLE
SACRED MARIJOA
The trace was successful!
Where is it from?!
The Kingdom of Lulusia!
Lulusia...
Unbelievable...
It's one of the countries...
...where the simultaneous Eight-Nation Revolution
took place after the Reverie!
After returning home from the Reverie,
PRINCESS COMANE     KING SEKI
OF THE KINGDOM OF LULUSIA
its ruler, King Seki, and Princess Comane...
...were captured by rebels and
are still being held under house arrest at their castle!
There was also information...
...that a Revolution Army officer arrived
in the kingdom a few days before the Reverie!
It's a perfect place for Sabo to hide!
I see...
He is an unlucky man...
No...
This is his destiny...
KAMABAKKA QUEENDOM
Sabo?!
Oh, whoa... Whoa!
Be quiet!
Are you really Sabo-kun?!
Yeah!
It's great that I got through to you!
Sabo-kun!
Sabo!
Why didn't you call us for a while?!
I was really worried about you!
Sorry, everyone!
No! That's okay!
Love!
Enough rejoicing.
You didn't just call us to say you're okay,
did you?
No...
I guess everyone read the article already.
SABO MURDERS KING COBRA
Dragon-san!
King Cobra's assassin...
...isn't me!
Uh-huh!
I believed you!
I didn't need to hear it! I knew it!
But...
...I saw something unbelievable...
...at Marijoa!
Something unbelievable?
KINGDOM OF LULUSIA, NEW WORLD
Hey.
Look.
--What's going on?
--It's creepy...
It looks like...
...some kind of a giant object
is in the sky...
You fools will all regret this!
Once the Navy Headquarters hears about this,
you'll all be impaled!
Dad, let me do it, too!
You vermin, I'll make you pay for this!
King... I mean, Seki-sama!
If you had thought of your citizens
even a little bit,
we wouldn't have revolted.
What?!
Why should a king think about
his lowly citizens?!
Know your place! Don't be rude!
Please admit your guilt!
We're not willing to kill you...
Shut up and just get me out of here!
The Pangaea Castle
where the Reverie took place...
On the Empty Throne there...
Communications Department...
Cut off your Transponder Snail.
What?
Didn't you hear me?
Y-Yes, sir!
No one should be sitting on it
since there's no king of the world, but...
Communications Department.
Listen carefully...
You guys didn't trace any calls...
Dad, I'm scared.
You guys didn't eavesdrop on anything...
Kingdom of Lulusia?
There was...
...no such country in the first place...
What happened?!
Sabo-kun?
Sabo-kun?!
A seaquake occurred off the southeast coast!
Look out for a tsunami!
I repeat!
A seaquake occurred off the southeast coast!
Look out for a tsunami!
A FEW DAYS LATER
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
Another one!
Hold on!
It's cold!
I'm scared!
--We're dead!
--Help!
A Neptunian!
This is messed up!
Aren't you cold?!
It's all a matter of perception.
It's good to be moss, huh?
You're too dull to feel cold.
Do you wanna become fish food?!
Try it!
What are you doing at a time like this?!
Jimbei!
Watch out for icebergs!
Yeah!
Furl the sails! The winds are too strong!
All right!
Strong Right!
Move faster, Mosshead!
Can't you work quietly?
Are we at an island yet, Nami?!
I don't think it's that far away!
I think we're in the climate range of
an island...
Maybe it's a harsh Winter Island!
Seems like they're all having a hard time,
so I'm gonna go help!
Oh, you look good, Chopper.
With this woven hat Otama gave me,
snow is not a problem for me!
Right?!
Hey, Nami!
What's that?!
What's what?
That's a big Warm Eddy!
Really?! That?!
What the hell is that?!
You've got to be kidding!
Why is it in the air?!
A mass of warm water that was heated up
must have been forced upwards.
How large is the temperature difference?!
It's like an Afro!
Whoa-whoa! This doesn't look good!
Get away, Jimbei! We'll get swept up by it!
Leave it to me!
Wait!
Someone's in the water!
What?! No way!
A mermaid?!
Somebody!
No, it's no mistake!
I heard a lady screaming!
From the water?!
Are you serious?!
Even if there is someone, what can we do?!
We can just cut it...
If you give the lady even a scratch,
I'll fillet you!
Shut up!
One-Sword Style...
Bird Dance!
It's cut!
Hey, guys! What's all the fuss about?!
Don't worry!
Woven-Hat Chopperemon is here, so...
The winds are strong!
Chopper, what did you come out for?!
Help!
Chopper!
Luffy!
Not you too!
--What are you doing?!
--That fool!
"GLUTTON" JEWELRY BONNEY, WORST GENERATION
BOUNTY: 320 MILLION BERRIES
A child flew out!
Who's that?!
Who are you?!
Thank good...
Where's the monster?!
Oh, good! Seems like she's alive...
--But...
--Down!
--Where are they going?!
--It's there!
--That little one is yelling something!
--It's still there!
Down!
Look down!
She said, "Look down"...
Oh, no...
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run!
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Now, Robin, what are we doing today?
World affairs are in shambles now, right?
So I wanted to review
a variety of information with everyone.
Oh, that's great!
Let's do it.
First, it's him. Sabo!
He was born on March 20th
and his favorite food is ramen.
He is Luffy's brother,
though not by blood.
He is from a noble family of Goa Kingdom!
But he ran away looking to be free
and met Luffy and Ace!
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
Sabo was thought to be dead,
but he reunited with Luffy in Dressrosa.
Fire Fist!
SABO - CHIEF OF STAFF OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
HACK, KOALA - THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
He became the number 2 of
the Revolutionary Army, the Chief of Staff!
Sabo ate the Flame-Flame Fruit.
The Logia type Devil Fruit
allows its user to transform into fire.
He took over his brother Ace's fruit.
What is happening to Sabo right now?
Oh, we're running out of time!
See you next time!
The Straw Hats are thrown out into the snowy sea
in the face of a powerful force!
A new shadow closes in on the sinking Sunny,
one threat after another looms.
Does the place where the stray Luffy
and the others have washed up on
offer hope or despair?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A New Island! Future Island Egghead"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!