(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
I saw something unbelievable...
...at Marijoa!
The Pangaea Castle
where the Reverie took place...
On the Empty Throne there...
No one should be sitting on it
since there's no king of the world, but...
Sabo tried to contact the Revolutionary Army
from the Kingdom of Lulusia, however...
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others
set out on a new quest,
and ran into a mysterious girl on the sea.
It's still there!
Down!
Look down!
"A New Island!
Future Island Egghead"
What's going on?!
Go away!
--Oh god! Oh god! Oh god!
--What's going on?!
Help!
This area isn't safe!
Get us out of here!
Is this it for us?!
Jimbei! Hurry up!
Jimbei! Get us out of here!
Hold on!
Hurry!
What's that?!
It's not an ordinary shark!
It's too big and made of iron?!
Hold on tight! We'll land on the water!
Oh, no!
Luffy and the others fell into the sea!
This is no good!
Franky!
Take the helm!
Bring the ship around to us!
All right! Count on me!
Luffy!
Chopper!
Where are you?!
There they are!
I said "Count on me"...
...but how can I find them
in this rough sea?!
Well, I've just gotta find a way!
Let's go, Sunny!
Ship's Bottom...
...Rabbit...
...Screw!
SHIP'S BOTTOM, RABBIT SCREW
All right!
Let's save Luffy and the others!
Luffy! Chopper!
Where are you?!
Franky! Get us out of here!
Torpedoes!
Robin-chan! Nami-san!
Oh, no!
It's gonna capsize!
What was that explosion?
Luffy! Chopper!
I'm here! You'll be fine!
Hey, you three! Stay with me!
We'll surface!
The current is strong! It's not navigable!
Is the Sunny okay?!
Thank you, Jimbei...
Oh, Luffy! You're okay!
I'm still alive...
I think I saw heaven...
I'm glad that all of you are okay!
The Sunny will be here soon!
That's...
What's the matter, Jimbei?
Hold on tight!
We'll escape to the sea bottom!
Take a deep breath, guys!
Let's go!
Oh, no... The current is too fast!
We can't surface!
Somebody, help!
Why am I in the water?! What's going on?!
Hang in there, Robin-chan!
Nami-san!
Gee... If nothing is done, we'll all...
...die...
NAVAL BRANCH G-14
All right, everyone!
TASHIGI, NAVY HQ CAPTAIN
It's time for your medication!
One cup each! You can drink it!
I'm drinking it for you, Tashigi-chan!
Mm-hm! Thank you!
--Guys, drink it all up!
--It tastes strange!
I don't want it
because it's tastes terrible!
But let's try to drink it!
Do I have to drink it all?
Yeah, to return to your original size.
I wanna return faster, so I'll drink two!
Tashigi-chan!
I think I have shrunk quite a bit!
Mm-hm! You've changed a lot, Mocha!
I can't wait to go home!
Yeah, be patient just a little longer.
Mm-hm!
Then I'll go see those big brothers
and sisters!
These slightly larger children were once...
...kidnapped by Caesar Clown,
an infamous scientist,
and were experimentally giganticized
at a lab on Punk Hazard.
Luffy allied with Trafalgar Law
who happened to be there,
and beat Caesar.
The rescued children...
...were taken care of by the Navy
under Tashigi's watch,
and are currently undergoing treatment here
in order to return to their original size.
I wonder how they are doing.
Like Chopper-chan!
Mm-hm. I hope you can see them soon.
Everyone, let's hang tough!
Tashigi!
Vice Admiral Doll!
Can I steal you for a sec?
VICE ADMIRAL DOLL
NAVAL BRANCH G-14 BASE COMMANDER
Could you do something about
that annoying brat, Helmeppo?
There's...
...nothing I can do.
His best friend's fate is unknown.
I understand that, but...
Captain Koby is a dear junior colleague
to me, too...
I'm begging you guys!
We're comrades! Please!
HIBARI - NAVY HQ COMMANDER
HELMEPPO - NAVY HQ LIEUTENANT COMMANDER
I'm beggin' you, too!
Koby-senpai has been so good to me!
PRINCE GRUS - NAVY HQ REAR ADMIRAL
Please come with us to the Pirate Island!
"Prince"!
Please! We alone can't...
We alone can't possibly...
...save him!
CAPTAIN KOBY
Please, "Prince"!
I'm begging you!
Stop that and raise your head.
Please! I won't move an inch
until you help us!
It's the Pirate Island
where Koby had been taken!
The Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard's
home turf!
You know that, right?!
If you poke that island even a little,
bloodthirsty pirates will swarm out
and shoot you up like bees!
PIRATE ISLAND OF FULLALEAD
That's why it's also known as the Beehive!
It's not a place we can screw with
that easily.
I know!
That's why I'm asking for your help!
Please!
You guys...
Egghead is close to here!
Let's take the Seraphim!
The Seraphim?! Are you out of your mind?!
Calm down a little!
We can't contact Drake now, either...
There's nothing we can do!
You must understand.
Koby!
What?!
LUFFY'S GROUP
Don't you know who I am?!
Yeah, I don't know.
I've been called the Worst Generation
along with you and the others!
Oh, you're one of the worst, too?!
You damn fool!
I was there at Sabaody too, two years ago!
I'm Bonney!
I'm your enemy! Don't forget!
But you saved me...
Thanks for that.
Don't mention it, Bogey!
It's Bonney!
What the...
That's cold!
I'm invincible with my woven hat!
I won't lose either, Chopper!
He's an Emperor of the Sea?
I don't get it.
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
is really with them, too...
Oh yeah,
what's wrong with that wanted poster?
I thought your hair turned white.
The newspapers were making a fuss about it.
Oh, that's...
...just how I look when I'm free!
What the hell?
What happened to your friends?
They should be fine.
What happened to your ship and friends?
I came here alone.
That iron monster ate my ship.
Screw that thing!
That's terrible...
Yeah! I'm getting hungry.
I'm hungry, too!
Let's find a restaurant.
But, Luffy, do you have any money?
Hey, you ignorant fools!
There's no restaurant here!
This island belongs to the Government.
I'll fill you in.
The name of this island is Egghead!
It houses Dr. Vegapunk's lab
and it is said to be "500 years in the future"!
Vegapunk! I know that name!
I have business with...
...that guy!
Everyone! Are you all right?!
Is the Sunny okay?
A... A...
A giant robot!
Who is operating this?
Someone's coming out!
It's no good...
I failed again.
Why can't I control
living things' primal urges?!
Boy, it troubles me...
I don't know who you are but thank you!
You saved us!
I only ordered the Mecha-Shark...
...to scout, report, and fire.
If it eats them,
their money and goods will be gone too.
It must be a programming glitch.
Now...
Who said anything about rescuing you pirates?!
I'm only a genius scientist
working for the Government!
I'm Dr. Vegapunk!
What?!
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
Jewelry Bonney!
Her bounty is 320 million berries.
She is the captain of the Bonney Pirates
and her nickname is Glutton.
She sure is eating a lot there!
She was born on September 1st
and her favorite food is pizza.
She is a rookie pirate who made her name
around the same time as us.
At that time, those pirates were called Supernovas,
now called the Worst Generation.
So she is in the same generation
as us and Tra-guy!
After the Paramount War,
she was defeated by the Blackbeard Pirates
and detained by the Navy at one point,
but she escaped
and snuck into Sacred Marijoa.
I'll never forgive them!
Ever!
And she met us this time on Egghead!
Looks like she has an ability to manipulate
the ages of herself and others.
Seems like she knows Vegapunk,
but what exactly is their relationship?
That's it for this week! See you next time!
Bye!
They finally reached Egghead,
an island housing Vegapunk.
Fish fly in the sky
and a giant monster and robot fight!
Urban landscapes with
the best of technology abound!
An unknown world full of dreams
attracts the excited Luffy.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Brimming with the Future!
An Adventure on the Island of Science!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!