(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Are your dreams still pure?
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
All of us tabibito e tsugu
All of us, I tell you travelers
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
No such thing as a pointless fight
barabara no bunmyaku ga
When random contexts
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
Start to make sense on their own
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
Luffy and the others met Vegapunk,
the world's greatest scientist,
and learned about astounding
scientific technology from 900 years ago.
There was some power in the past that defies
the common knowledge of the world today.
Even with our scientific technology,
we can't replicate that iron giant perfectly.
It's shameful...
I feel it was fate
that brought you here today.
I need you to take me away
from Egghead-Quasar!
Around the same time, Cipher Pol "Aigis" Zero
was approaching Egghead.
Sea Beast Weapons...
They're like the gate keepers of Egghead.
Fire!
They want us to let them enter the port!
It's not good to have pirates here!
Pythagoras, tell the ship...
...to leave the Seraphim and go.
What?!
Prepare to intercept! We'll deny
the World Government's request to enter!
It's rare that you're willing to fight.
"Preparations for Interception!
Rob Lucci Strikes!"
Please leave!
Okay. I got it.
Clank.
Nothing you say seems to help.
What should we do, Lucci?
We have no choice...
Everyone, get ready to abandon ship!
Using the Seraphim S-Bear's power,
we'll fly to Egghead.
As soon as we invade, this ship...
...will fall prey to the Sea Beast Weapons.
Yes, sir!
That's quite a risky move.
People won't like you
if you're so impatient.
If you wanna be swallowed by the sea,
do what you want.
Oh, how scary.
Do it!
What was that?!
It came from the city...
Maybe Kuma is on a rampage again.
No, that explosion was outside the island...
Seems like CP-0 is causing the commotion.
Zero?
They're those who work
only on the orders of the Celestial Dragons.
What's CP-0? It's not CP9?!
They're superior to CP9.
When they move,
it's said to be an omen of
a major historical event.
It's amazing!
What a futuristic city!
I can't help getting excited!
Are they Cipher Pol?!
Usually, they're all in black suits.
Why didn't they come from the port as usual?
Hey!
I heard two of the Sea Beast Weapons
were beaten up at the shore!
Don't tell me...
...they're intruders!
Shaka! CP-0 is on the island!
They're here!
That bastard is as annoying as always!
I hate him! Go away, Rob Lucci!
I can't move!
Set us free already!
I won't let them touch Robin-chan!
How did they come ashore?
Their ship has been
destroyed by the Beasts at the shore!
We asked them to leave,
but obviously they didn't comply.
In anticipation of our attack, they probably
flew in by Paw-Paw Fruit power!
They used S-Bear.
They're willing to sacrifice
their ship to fight.
If that's what they want,
it can't be helped...
Tell all researchers and workers
to evacuate!
Okay!
Tell Atlas to get back to the lab!
Get the Seraphim ready to launch!
Let Sentomaru lead them!
Energy-fill, start!
96!
97!
98!
99!
Signals all green!
I'm going to open the confining walls.
Seraphim, number one, three, and four.
Seraphim, number one.
S-Hawk!
Seraphim, number three.
S-Snake!
Seraphim, number four.
S-Shark!
Launch!
If the World Government targets me,
it's only a matter of time
before they kill me.
And now, CP-0 is here
and I'm gonna pack up my stuff so...
...take me out to sea-Quasar!
Don't say it like it's
a field trip or something, old man!
If you disappear,
it would be big news worldwide.
Your head is funny, so why not!
Is that the reason?!
I knew you would say yes!
Then, let's go up!
This place will be a battlefield.
I want you to bring Bonney
to the Labophase above the clouds.
Yeah, okay!
You guys, take the Vacuum Rocket
from the Fabriophase!
--Vacuum Rocket?!
--Sounds like fun!
Okay, see you up there.
Meet me as soon as possible!
What?!
He vanished!
Old Man Apple!
The future confuses me...
Hey, look at that!
There's a monster!
It's no use!
Guns don't work on it!
Of course not!
Peashooters like those are powerless
against a creature beyond our imagination!
I've always wanted to
fight something like you.
You look not of this world.
You're...
...a space monster, aren't you?!
All right! Let's fight!
Tempest Kick!
What?!
This one is quite tough!
It's no use.
What should I do?!
It's a hologram.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
You know a lot about this place, Stussy.
Yeah, this place is nostalgic...
When it comes to this,
I'm gonna see what's above the clouds
while I'm in the air!
I'm sure Vegapunk will be there!
Do you see those two lines
on the clouds, Lucci?
Yeah.
Once their enemy
crosses past those lines...
Laser beams are activated.
Kaku-san!
It's called the Frontier Dome.
It's a defense system
encircling the Labophase.
So you better not underestimate
the world's greatest scientist.
Why didn't you tell him sooner?
Hey! You're so mean, Stussy!
Are you warmed up now?
Who is it?!
Who is acting more violently...
...than me on Egghead?!
I'm...
...gonna kick your ass!
Who is that giant girl?!
Is that a hologram, too?
No...
That's Atlas.
One of the Vegapunks.
Atlas-sama!
Beat them up!
Please!
Yeah, leave it to me!
I see...
So she's my prey.
I'm gonna defend the peace of Egghead!
Hey! Stop that cutie now!
Rob Lucci is a crazy guy!
I know!
Atlas! Wait!
You're no match for them! Retreat!
Shut up!
I'm gonna teach
these evil intruders a lesson!
Ultra...
I can't believe this idiot
is a Vegapunk clone...
We're not here to play!
...Mighty...
...Pu...
...n...
...ch!
Six King Pistol!
Atlas-sama!
He has no mercy.
Atlas-sama got knocked out
by the intruder!
Why does Cipher Pol behave so violently?!
They're supposed to be
on the Government's side! Why?!
Everyone on the Fabriophase! Evacuate!
--I repeat! Evacuate now!
--It's an evacuation order!
--Everyone, run into the factory!
--This is an enemy attack!
I repeat! Evacuate now!
This is an enemy attack!
She's still alive...
Let's eliminate her first.
Rocket! Rocket!
Where is the rocket?!
Come to think of it, we don't even know
where to get on the rocket.
How long will we continue to run?!
I wish we could have asked him
more specifically where it was!
If we keep running, we'll find it! Rocket!
Well, we've already done a lot of running!
Hurry up! Let's go up!
Via the Vacuum Rocket!
Straw Hat.
The pigeon guy!
Luffy!
Rob Lucci!
Did they really come to
get rid of Vegapunk?!
Why are you here?! Pigeon guy!
This is the Government's island.
You're right! We're the ones
who weren't supposed to be here!
That doesn't matter now!
Let's escape to the upper level
in a hurry, Luffy!
How annoying! The Straw Hats?!
There's Jewelry Bonney, too.
It's nice if we can get rid of them
all at once...
But don't do anything, Lucci!
Since Straw Hat is an Emperor of the Sea,
we can't fight him without permission from the top.
He's right.
The Four Emperors often have allies.
A skirmish could lead to a war.
Report to the Navy now.
Yes, ma'am!
I know I shouldn't fight him...
Take Bonney, Jimbei!
You...
What's the matter?
How awful!
This girl...
We just saw her!
Oh, if you're hungry...
It's an Automated Cooking Machine!
The leftover ingredients auto mode
is particularly handy!
You aren't listening!
Gee...
Chopper, check on her!
Okay!
I think this is more of
Franky's specialty...
Hey.
Did you do this to her?
Stay out of it.
This is the Government's business.
I don't know what you came here for...
But she gave us food to eat!
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
Still looking for the future
hontou no yakusoku wa
The real promise
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Lies much deeper in my heart
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
A dream that no one can catch up with
tada hitotsu dakishimete
That's all I hold on to
taiyou no youni warau anata e
To you who smiles like the sun
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
I'll sing the same song as that day
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
kono negai ga todoku made
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Kaku!
He was the foreman of Dock One of
the Galley-La Company, a company of shipwrights!
But that was only his cover.
He was actually an agent of CP9,
the World Government's secret agency.
He was born on August 7th
and likes bananas and sponge cake!
He hid his true identity and
successfully captured Robin, the survivor of Ohara,
and Franky who had the blueprints
for the Ancient Weapon Pluton.
After returning to Enies Lobby,
the Island of Justice, from Water Seven,
he ate a Devil Fruit.
The Ox-Ox Fruit, Giraffe Model!
It allows him to transform into a giraffe.
Both its power and appearance are shocking!
I've become square with no blind spots.
Using the power, he fought against Zoro
of the Straw Hats who came to rescue Robin,
but got taken down and
gave Zoro the key to Robin's handcuffs.
I heard he went through a lot after that,
but now he's a member of CP-0.
CP-0 has a not-so-shallow connection
with the Straw Hats.
There could be more turmoil.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
The Drums of Liberation
echo throughout Egghead!
Facing Luffy's freewheeling Gear Five,
Lucci awakens the madness of a wild beast.
The clash between creation and destruction!
The fateful confrontation sends
the Future Island into a whirlpool of chaos!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Powers on a Different Level! Luffy vs. Lucci!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!