(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
"A Beautiful Act of Treason!
The Spy, Stussy!"
What?!
Wait a minute! What's going on?!
Why did a CP-0 knock out another CP-0?
It's not my place to say something, but...
...is it okay for you to do that?
You're Roronoa Zoro, aren't you?
You don't need to worry.
I can't understand
the ways of the Government.
And that skeleton right there
is Soul King, right?
How long are you going to stay there?
Are you scared of me?
Thump!
Yes, in many ways...
Now, what's going on?
Did you have a falling out?
No, I did it for a purpose.
Don't worry. I won't harm you guys.
I don't trust someone
who betrays their friends.
This is Stussy.
I put both of them to sleep.
Sorry for the trouble.
She did it!
She didn't have to...
I would have brought down
the Government's people!
Who is it from?! Your ally?!
Rob Lucci has been taken down?!
What's going on?!
Even that shrewd Lucci didn't see it coming.
Are Zoro and Brook okay?
Yeah.
I'm as good as new!
Good!
Stay on your guard!
Oh, great! Stussy did it!
York, where are you?
Help...
York, are you all right?!
Stay with me! York!
I feel sick...
I can't eat anymore.
She's just talking in her sleep.
Wake up now! Something big is happening!
Now, who is Stussy?
She took down those two.
She must be dangerous.
For an undercover operation
lasting over 20 years,
she has been our ally.
What?! You sent a spy
into an intelligence agency?!
And for more than 20 years?
That's not what we planned...
But it ended up that way.
But, Doctor...
My authority is the same as Lucci's.
I can't override his orders
to the Seraphim.
I can't stop them!
You did enough! Stussy!
We're on our way!
We'll stop them at any cost!
Anyhow, we gotta stop those brats or
our friends will all end up being buried!
You're right!
But those kids...
Don't they look familiar?
They do!
Especially...
...him!
How dare you do that, you brats?!
Damn!
You messed up the lab!
But that made it easier to get out!
I'll go first!
No! That'll cause trouble!
Okay! I got out!
Hey!
Seraphim!
Here is an order!
When I look closely...
you're more of a human than he is.
Who are you?!
That scared me!
Are you okay, Lilith?!
All right! Leave it to me!
Seraphim!
Stop...
...fighting!
Edison!
Just in time!
You're...
Edison!
Hey... Don't tell me...
Lilith-chan.
Are you worrying about...
...this guy?
Edison!
--That was close!
--Thank goodness!
--I thought that was really it!
--Edison! You scared me!
Those look-alikes, they stopped.
Hey! Who the hell are they?!
Explain it to me!
Don't worry!
They're my warriors who I'm quite proud of!
They're not gonna attack us anymore!
Our rank of authority is higher than CP-0
and we commanded them directly,
so the order to the Seraphim
has been overwritten.
Oh...
It's too hard for you to understand,
Mosshead.
Stop being annoying, you stupid cook!
Stop it, Zoro-phim!
Don't treat me like the Seraphim!
--Stop, Green-phim!
--Shut up, Twirly-phim!
--What should we do now?
--I'll kill you, Directionally-challenged-phim!
We've been entrusted with an important mission.
Let's work as one
and help Vegapunk off the island!
Oh! You're full of energy!
Super!
Now we can breathe a little easier.
Those Seraphim are threatening
when they're our enemies...
But it's great to have them on our side.
We have some quite dependable allies now.
Shaka.
I put Sea Prism Stone Cuffs
on Lucci and Kaku.
So even if they wake up,
they can't use their Devil Fruit powers.
Thank you, Stussy.
We're going to get off of the island
by ship with the Straw Hats!
Come with us.
Roger.
Hey! You just invited one more person
to come aboard the Sunny!
Clank.
Stussy-sama is coming with us, too...
That's wonderful!
Now, let's join everyone else!
Okay!
Hey!
Bonney! Old Man Punk!
Where are you?!
Luffy!
Chopper!
Did you find them?
I don't see them anywhere.
That's strange! Where are they?
I'm gonna go check this way!
Thanks.
Yeah!
Oh boy...
Hey!
Old Man Punk!
We can't set sail without you!
Saving Bonney led the Straw Hats
to the Future Island Egghead.
They met Dr. Vegapunk
and his six Satellites
and learned about the advanced civilization
from 900 years ago
and the truth about the ones
who inherited Ohara's will.
After being asked to by Vegapunk Stella,
Luffy decided to take them all to sea.
I need you to take me away
from Egghead-Quasar!
However, they got into a battle...
...against CP-0 led by Rob Lucci
who came to the island to kill Vegapunk.
After subduing Lucci and Kaku,
Luffy and the others
wanted to leave Egghead immediately...
But an incident occurred.
Old man!
Dr. Vegapunk Stella disappeared!
This is Sphinx in the New World.
The pirate Whitebeard's hometown.
Welcome home, Marco!
Hey, Marco. I was really scared!
I wasn't scared!
All of a sudden, the Navy came surging!
I'm really...
...sorry-yoi
that I wasn't there to protect you.
I was not scared!
Then what happened?
Listen, listen!
The Navy guys were horrible!
They said they would seize
Whitebeard's treasure!
They're no different from pirates!
SEVERAL DAYS AGO
Gather all the villagers.
Yes, sir!
I won't do you any harm
as long as you cooperate.
This island is not affiliated
with the World Government!
You people aren't protected by the law!
I believe Whitebeard's vast treasure
is somewhere on the island.
Tell me where it is!
B-But we've never heard of his treasure!
Don't lie!
It's not a lie!
We can't tell you what we don't know!
Oh...
I see...
W-We really...
If you don't tell us,
we'll consider it an act of treason!
Or...
...if I shoot you guys one by one,
will you tell me?
Th-There is no such thing!
Don't point a gun at my little brother!
Stop it!
If we can't pay money to the Government,
we're not even to be treated as humans?!
You brutes!
Aren't you scared?
Marco isn't here to protect you now.
Restrain her.
What are you doing?!
Grandma!
Stop it! I said stop!
Don't do it! She's an elder!
No! Stop it! Grandma!
No! Let go of me!
Don't do it!
Don't mess with...
...my daddy's hometown!
It's Edward Weevil!
W-We gotta run!
--Yeah!
--H-Hey!
I'm sure they sent troops to arrest him
when the Seven Warlords system was abolished!
But we can't contact those troops now!
They must've been beaten! All of them!
So he is as strong as a monster!
Retreat to the ship!
We'll wait for reinforcements!
This is Sphinx!
We were attacked by a former Warlord Weevil!
We need backup!
And the Navy soldiers
who came raiding the village left the island!
If it weren't for that huge man,
we would have been done for.
--Right?
--Yeah!
So he's a hero.
I'm really glad that you're all okay-yoi.
But, Marco!
Who do you think came after that?!
Navy Admiral Ryokugyu came...
And though Weevil resisted,
they took him away!
Weevil!
Mommy!
Give me back my son! And...
MISS BUCKIN, FREELOADER AT MADS,
SELF-PROCLAIMED SCIENTIST,
EX-ROCKS PIRATES MEMBER
...give us
"Whitebeard" Edward Newgate's heritage!
REAL NAME
BUCKINGHAM STUSSY
Is that what you really came here for-yoi?
Gulp!
He went to jail defending his father's village!
What an admirable boy!
Me and Newgate's son!
I really appreciate him
for defending the village-yoi...
Marco!
You also don't believe Weevil is
Whitebeard's real son, do you?!
There is someone who can prove it!
It's Dr. Vegapunk!
Kizaru-san! We brought some teacakes.
JUSTICE
Have you tested them for poison?
Of course!
I'll take them. You can go.
Yes, sir!
May I come in?
I brought you a little something...
Be my guest.
Have you ever met Dr. Vegapunk before?
Mm-hm.
Just once, a long time ago.
I can't believe...
...he betrayed you people.
ST. JAYGARCIA SATURN OF THE FIVE ELDERS
HIGHEST AUTHORITIES OF THE WORLD
I truly feel what has happened is a shame.
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Marco!
He is the former 1st division commander
and ship's doctor of the Whitebeard Pirates
who uses the Tweet-Tweet Fruit,
Mythical Type, Phoenix Model.
He was born on October 5th
and likes pineapples!
In the Paramount War,
he fought against Navy Admirals
to defend Ace and Luffy.
You can't reach...
...the king...
...so easily-yoi!
He lost Whitebeard,
and ever since the Whitebeard Pirates
were scattered in the Grudge War,
he has been defending Sphinx,
Whitebeard's hometown.
But when the Straw Hats set out
to defeat Kaido,
he went to the Land of Wano
and helped them.
If my captain gives the order, I'll just follow.
I'm counting on Straw Hat, too.
No...
On you guys from the Worst Generation.
For the Straw Hats,
he is someone who can always be counted on.
Let's look forward to seeing more of him
in the future.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
On the brink of escaping Egghead,
Dr. Vegapunk, the key figure in the mission,
suddenly and inexplicably disappears!
Where in the closed laboratory did he go?
The Straw Hats, who have been left behind,
begin their search for the genius scientist!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Trouble Occurs! Seek Dr. Vegapunk!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!