(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
"Trouble Occurs!
Seek Dr. Vegapunk!"
We've taken control of the Fabriophase.
All right. Listen.
Look. That tube is
where the Vacuum Rocket goes through.
It runs all over the city
and is designed to reach the Labophase.
Destroy it all.
Thoroughly eliminate anything
that might aid Vegapunk's escape!
Shoot!
What?!
Is it an enemy?!
We're under attack by someone!
Fire back!
Retreat for now! Retreat for now!
What's going on?
That's...
A Pacifista?!
Wait! You're a Navy soldier, right?!
You're supposed to be on the Government's side.
Don't get in our way!
Hey! What are you doing?!
How dare you do that to my colleagues?!
That's...
Stop! Don't shoot!
What?
What kind of ability is that?!
That's a Bubble Shield!
Is that the world's strongest shield
I heard Vegapunk invented?!
That's the one that far surpasses
the prototypes used in the Paramount War...
Pacifista Mk. III!
Stop fighting and move to Factory B.
COMBAT WEAPON OF NAVY'S SCIENCE GROUP
Confirmed hostile activity.
Everyone, surrender! Or we'll all die!
Hurry up!
I'll take you in.
Why?!
The Pacifistas don't move on their own!
Who is giving him commands?!
Don't move! It's bad for your wounds.
What a day off...
Is the Pacifista performing well?
Yes. I was able to take shelter here
thanks to him.
Everyone else is evacuating, too.
That's good.
Sentomaru-san, thank you!
Thanks to you,
we were able to evacuate safely.
Thank you!
I'm gonna put a bandage
on your right arm, too.
Something is happening above.
This is Sentomaru. Respond!
Hey! Old Man Punk!
No response.
And the Frontier Dome is closed.
I can't reach Old Man Punk...
Straw Hat!
I trust you with Old Man Punk!
Okay! Leave it to me!
Straw Hat!
What's disturbing is that the Navy is
continuously communicating...
...but we've been cut out of the loop.
Old Man Punk... I'm already a traitor.
So I'll do as I please.
Pacifista Mk. III, activate!
All fifty of you, go!
Straw Hat Luffy will let Dr. Vegapunk
aboard his ship!
Your mission is to let it depart safely!
Roger.
JUSTICE
The Navy is acting strange!
Watch the shore!
Something will happen on the island.
Make sure your creator...
...gets off this island!
Stop! Don't touch it!
Shut up! Get out!
Bonney!
Dad...
Dad's memories...
What... What happened?!
Tell me, Dad!
Dad!
Where am I?
Hey! Is somebody there?!
I can't take it anymore...
I can't...
What's the matter? Hey.
What happened?
I can't take it anymore...
I really can't...
I can't... take it...
Help, somebody!
I don't wanna go back!
Dad?
What?! What do you mean Vegapunk is missing?
Where did he go?!
Did you look carefully?
He must be here, right? In the lab!
Well, I really...
...ran all over the place.
But I couldn't find him.
Did you really?
Yes, he did! He broke his shoes' flying function
so he was running the whole time!
Don't tell them that!
I have no money to pay damages!
This is not the time for that!
Where did Vegapunk go?!
Usopp, relax!
How can I relax?!
We gotta go soon
or another scary one will come!
I guess we can't set sail yet.
Where did Old Man Apple go?
And Bonney...
I wonder if she's okay.
She's a mess too,
but we can't leave her alone.
I'm worried about her.
Well, I see Bonney.
What?
The monitor shows everything in the lab.
Why only say so now?
--I could see her all along.
--Why now?!
Hey.
Jeez...
Zoro!
What's taking you so long?
Aren't we gonna set sail?
We have some problems!
Anyway, this place is amazing in many ways!
It's so futuristic!
So futuristic!
There's a hat that fits you!
Is that what you find so amazing
about the future?
This place is in worse shape than I thought.
Stussy-sama!
You got ahead of the times and
dressed in futuristic outfits! So... So...
Beautiful!
You're good at flattery.
I'm a man who loves all ladies of all time!
Shaka, how's Atlas?
Edison. Lilith.
Don't summon us
like you're our boss, Shaka!
We're not your subordinates!
Move aside.
I've just finished it. Take a look.
Don't say it like you did it by yourself!
I repaired her with you!
Hi! Sorry to keep you waiting!
I am now fully recovered!
Stop it!
I'm fine!
Okay, okay!
This much energy right after we repaired her?
Give me a break!
Good morning, Atlas.
Hey!
Were you sleeping again?
How long have you been sleeping?
Do you want me to wake you up completely?
Don't do anything unnecessary!
Cutie! Pretty! Lovely!
A beauty! A beauty! A beauty!
A vision of the future!
Beauties in all directions!
To the future!
The future is full of beauties!
The future is the best!
--What's with him?
--Forget about him.
So her face is repaired.
We have replacement parts.
It's you!
You saved my life, didn't you?!
Thanks!
Yeah, because you gave us food to eat.
I'm glad that you're okay now.
Yeah!
How dare they hurt that cute girl!
These jerks haven't changed
since Water Seven!
If you're gonna come after Robin again,
I'll kick your ass!
Nami...
They can't do anything now.
But...
Thank you for caring about me.
It's the thought that counts.
Robin...
All of it was done to hide my true identity,
but it was heartbreaking.
No, you made the right call there.
We were able to neutralize CP-0 because you were
able to keep your true identity hidden.
You're so kind.
Now, I want to see Stella,
but what happened?
There are two unusual things happening.
Listen, but don't get upset.
First...
Stella has disappeared.
Second...
We have lost control of the Frontier Dome.
What? What do you mean?
That means we can no longer
get out of the Labophase.
If you try to get out,
laser beams will burn you to death.
Wait, wait! We're setting out to sea
with Vegapunk, right?!
Yes, but the target of the rescue
disappeared.
What should we do?!
What we can do is look for Stella.
I'll try to fix the Dome somehow.
But if Vegapunk is not on the monitor
that shows everything,
what's the point in going out to look for him?
Normally, it shows everything in the lab,
but due to the shock of
the Seraphim's earlier rampage,
the Cam-snails have either left their posts
or passed out.
I keep sending the Satellites and workers
to check those areas in turn.
He could be passed out
in the Cam-snails' blind spots.
Shaka. This is Pythagoras.
Seems like no one is on the third floor
in Building C.
I see.
Then check the building next to it, too.
We should go look for him, too.
We have to find him and set sail ASAP.
I'm interested
in the treasure of the future, too!
Oh, that sounds like fun.
I'll come with you!
Wait, wait, wait! I bet you guys are thinking
things you shouldn't!
No, we are not. Right, Nami-san?
I don't know.
See! You're up to something.
I'm going to go look, too.
I can't believe he disappeared and I'm worried.
I'll come with you.
Oh, thank you.
Stussy-sama!
Take me with you, too!
I have no choice.
I should go look, too.
Wait, Mosshead!
What? I gotta just find an old man
whose head is cut off, right?
You?! Go look for someone?!
Shut up! Let go of me, Shitty Cook!
Then who's gonna look for you?!
Well...
He's right, Zoro! Stay here!
You too?!
Please. Stay here quietly.
All right...
Wait for me, Vegapunk!
Now, where should we go?!
I don't know!
The hallways were like a maze!
I fear we might get lost.
Pirates are so high-maintenance.
Follow me!
Yeah! Thanks!
Are you sleeping again?
You're sleeping too much. Let's go.
Okay.
Gee, I don't know
what they were talking about...
Well, I guess finding someone
isn't too hard even for them.
I can't believe you ran with all your might.
I always do things with all my might...
Anyway...
I never thought I'd see these guys again.
It takes me back to Water Seven.
I wonder how Ice pops is doing.
Clank.
See! I got some serious information!
The World Government is now in the process
of assassinating the famous Dr. Vegapunk!
Killing the world's greatest genius?!
This is the Ohara Incident all over again!
But the Government's odds aren't good!
Vegapunk is the world's favorite.
He lit up towns around the world
with various energy developments.
The one who happens to be there...
...is him!
Then, here is our World Economic Journal's
next headline!
"Emperor of the Sea Straw Hat Luffy
holds Vegapunk hostage on Egghead!
Gets into an all-out war with the Navy!"
If a pirate is framed as the perpetrator,
Vegapunk's death won't bring
bad publicity to the Government!
The Government will thank me!
--Go get a reward from them!
--Yes, sir!
What a silly article.
Did you say something?
I did!
How dare you make up some random story?
Luffy-san wouldn't do such a thing!
NEFELTARI VIVI
PRINCESS OF KINGDOM OF ALABASTA
That's why I hate WEJ!
Hey!
Keep your voice down!
WAPOL
KING OF EVIL BLACK DRUM KINGDOM
If a Transponder Snail bug is around
and the Government finds out that we're here,
they'll erase us instantly!
Besides, Mor-chan is giving us shelter.
Stop talking back to him!
How can I overlook a lie like that?!
Don't twist the truth and write a story!
Have you no sense of decency?!
I lent her some clothes!
I'll never wash them again!
What?! I wanna lend her mine, too!
Vivi-sama!
You had been crying until yesterday!
Don't get all high and mighty
and meddle in my business!
The only one who can shake up the world...
...is me!
It doesn't matter if it's true or not!
Newspapers are entertainment!
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Morgans!
His nickname is Big News and
he is the president of World Economic Journal.
He is also a user of
the Tweet-Tweet Fruit, Albatross Model!
He was born on July 14th
and likes popcorn!
Albatross is ahoudori in Japanese.
He is always in his Man-Beast Form
and there is no data on his real face.
He is a newspaperman at heart
who is obsessed with writing scoops.
He published a story
that might incur Big Mom's wrath,
and ignored the Five Elders' order
to manipulate information.
He is willing to risk anything
for an interesting scoop.
I won't let them manipulate information!
The truth is the most interesting thing
when the times are changing like now!
I love how everything
is happening in real time!
For better or worse,
he always creates sensations in the world.
I can't wait to see
what kind of scoop he will get next!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Mysterious communication interference
divides the Straw Hats.
The Satellites are caught off guard
and their lives are threatened.
Someone must be invading
the closed Labophase!
An inescapable death game with doubt
and fear engulfs Luffy and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece! "A Shudder!
The Evil Hand Creeping Up on the Laboratory"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!