All of us! Dream save us, all of us!
All of us Dream save us All of us
Us! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, us!
Us! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Us
The farthest dreams, the farthest seas
yume no hate umi no hate
Each of us got somewhere we wanna be
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But before we set off
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
We gotta launch a dazzling legend!
densetsu o buchiagete kara da
Crackling! Bursting! No limits! Now it truly begins!
bachibachi No limit koko kara ga
One Piece!
ONE PIECE!
For all of us, I say to the wanderers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
We sure our dreams are still as clear as they always were?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Gonna make your restless cells laugh 'til they burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Even now, all of us're on an adventure!
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
To all of us, I tell the wanderers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
There's no such thing as a meaningless battle
imi no nai tatakai wa nai n da
When the scattered passages combined take on a will of their own
barabara no bunmyaku ga ishi o mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time will be woven back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
As the world changes, so will we
oretachi to tomo ni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
All of us! Dream save us, all of us!
All of us Dream save us All of us
Love-Love...
...Mellow!
York!
Halt, Seraphim!
Why?! This isn’t right!
I’m Vegapunk!
They’re not following my orders...
That means whoever
is commanding them...
...has to be one of
the other Vegapunks.
What if the communication failure...
...and this situation of
being trapped in the barrier...
...were all calculated?
That would mean someone...
...is intent on killing us all!
Hey, Straw Hat, Roronoa.
How about calling a truce...
...and forming a temporary alliance?
A Painful Decision!
Unlikely Alliance on the Battlefront!
Zoro... You ever see that
Devil Fruit ability before?
Yeah. Was a while back, though.
It’s Baroque Works’...
...living blade guy.
So this brat’s got
Baldy’s power, too...
Makes this a huge pain in the ass.
Zoro!
What the hell did
you do with Lucci?!
Left ‘im over there.
Come again?!
Why, ya little...!
Dammit!
See what I’m talking
about, Roronoa?!
Are you seriously going to the trouble of
leaving us cuffed while defending us?!
We’ve got to team up,
and do it now!
So would you kindly
undo these damn chains?!
I said I ain’t doin’ that, so shut up about it!
We’ll drag your ass wherever the hell we want!
Pardon, what?!
Yer already friends, cool!
Not at all!
Hell no!
CP-0.
Might I inquire...
...as to what your objective is?
To track down the seven Vegapunks...
...and eliminate them.
Lucci! Why the hell are you
telling one of our targets?!
And I take it that Stussy,
having betrayed you,
won’t be let off scot-free?
Yeah.
She’ll pay with her life.
Where’s your survival instinct, man?!
Nami!
—2nd Floor, Building B—
Sure is noisy up there...
Hope everyone’s all right.
This is serious...
What’s the matter?
Nami-san’s...
...in big trouble!
Wait for me, Nami-swan!
Wait for us, Sanji!
—3rd Floor, Building A—
W-What?! What’s going on?!
Aren’t they supposed to
do what you tell them?!
Yeah, s’posed ta!
Eh?!
Is there anything you can do?!
You’re a genius, aren’t you?!
With great ideas, right?!
You can say that
all ya want, but...
...this’s somethin’
I wasn’t expectin’!
An’ I’m tryin’ to figure out what ta do, okay?!
Patience is a virtue, ya know!
Please don’t take
too much more time!
‘Course!
C’mon, think, think!
What’s the best approach when
there’s outta control Seraphim?
Says me, but this ain’t
ever happened before!
What do we do,
what do we do?!
What do we dooooo?!
Yes, I got it!
Fer times like these...
Mm-hmm!
Yes?
Jus’ run fer it!
Wha?!
Oh, my!
That’s Nami’s scream...
That means there’s more than
two of these in the lab...
—3rd Floor, Building C—
And all four of ‘em
have gone berserk.
We gotta keep the seven Vegapunks safe.
Plus...
...how many?
That’s...!
See what I’m talking about?!
Take these things off!
Shut it!
You blockhead!
Helmet!
Keys to the cuffs.
I’ll let you two be the judges.
Straw Hat Luffy...
Please, however you can...
...you must focus on protecting Stella!
Sure! Count on me!
Hey!
After we put a stop
to the four bad guys,
ya ain’t gonna go after my crew or the Vegapunks
just ‘cause ya can’t beat me, got that?
Hey, stupid.
If you’re trying to bait them, that’s not gonna...
I’m totally fine with that!
And that’s ‘cause you’re
the first one on my list,
Straw Hat!
Once you’re dead,
it’s then that I’ll murder
all your friends!
Holy crap, that worked!
Good!
This is not the time for that!
Ursus...
...Shock!
Gear 4:
Boundman!
Sorry, Bonney!
Here I go!
Don’t slow me down.
Who do you think you’re talking to?!
Purgatory Demon Slash!
Tempest Kick: White Thunder!
Gum-Gum...
Six Sovereign...
...Kong...
...Gun!
On a certain island in the New World...
We find ourselves in a bar at a small port.
Meanie, meanie, meanie!
I don’t just wanna go for fun!
Take me, take me!
Take me with you, please!
I wanna go on your next voyage!
Not a chance.
I’m not afraid of getting hurt!
Oh, yeah?
Then absolutely no chance.
But I wanna adventure with you!
I got more guts than
anyone on this island!
Duh-mmy.
Taking a hot-headed brat like you
is a no-go for me.
Give it up already.
You’re just making our captains feel bad, you know.
I don’t wanna!
I’m trying to be like him!
I’m even training my body!
I’m sure I’d be your best crewmember!
You’re gonna regret not taking me!
What else do I gotta do
to get you to take me?!
Hey, go easy on the kid, Boss.
Yeah, don’t make fun of the kid
when he’s bein’ serious!
Who knows what
crazy stuff he could do!
And definitely don’t make light of
him puttin’ his heart into it!
Once in a while, it’s troublemakers
like him that stir up the world!
C’mon, say something!
You’re buggin’ me!
You really are a hothead!
Aww, geez!
Dang it!
Sorry to interrupt, gents!
Need your attention,
Big Boss!
Better be sorry!
Yer interruptin’!
Real sorry, but it’s important!
That dumbass actually attacked us!
Sounds like a problem!
He’s a ball o’ energy, ain’t he?
The peanut gallery’s all riled up and
squabblin’ out there over being blindsided...
What’re we gonna do?
Things’re gonna get ugly!
For cryin’ out loud...
Not sure if his timing’s
great or awful...
We were about to set off anyway...
We just got a little
carried away chatting.
I just happened to meet some old friends,
both of us thought the other was dead.
Couldn’t help ourselves.
Oh, I’m sure the opposition’s pissed.
Beck, you can’t say that!
Who d’ya think he’s got it in for?!
We’re shipping out.
We fightin’ then, Boss?!
Are you declaring war, Shanks?!
I’m not about to
turn this island into a battlefield!
Oh, he’s so dreamy!
I don’t want to cause a catastrophe here.
This country is one of proud warriors:
Elbaf.
Mind giving us a hand,
Dorry, Brogy?
No problem, brother!
You fightin’, then, Red-Haired?
Hey, I want to make sure with him
before this goes down...
Uh, with Captain Kid? What about?
Uh-huh. Ask him this:
“Are you sure you want to fight me right now?”
“Or...
“...would you rather leave the
Road Poneglyphs behind and just go away?”
Tell him, “Choose!”
The handful of ships seen shoreside,
and those dumbasses annoyin’ the hell outta us...
...are apparently...
...a buncha pirates under
Emperor Red-Haired’s umbrella.
An’ they’ve made names
for themselves, too.
It’s the Big Boss!
I was hoping you’d show up, Big Boss!
You too, Beckman!
Don’t come any closer to
the boss and his crew!
I’m here to pay your protection fee!
We don’t run that kinda racket!
The last time we ran into them, we didn’t even catch
a glimpse of their head honcho, Red-Haired,
and we still got
our asses handed to us.
You even lost one of your arms.
They ain’t gonna settle for
just an arm this time!
They’re coming for your life!
That only applies...
...if I lose, right?!
How far have you run to get here?
dore dake hashitte kita no ka
Not knowing, you count your scars instead
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
With the treasure map that's always in your mind
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
You'll keep seeking the future
mirai o sagashi tsuzuketeru
True promises dwell deeper than the bottom of your heart
hontou no yakusoku wa mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Everyone has a dream they can't catch
dare mo minna oitsukenai yume
A lone dream they hold dear
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you, with your smile like the sun
taiyou no you ni warau anata e
I sing, just like I did that day
ano hi to onaji uta o utau yo
Even if I grow up, I never want to forget
otona ni natte mo wasuretaku nai
Until the day my wish reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
Diving Into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!
Diving Into the Sea of Information！
The Punk Records Library！
Yo! I’m one of the humble genius scientist
Dr. Vegapunk’s Satellites, Lilith!
Ah’m one of the Vegapunks too!
Edison’s the name!
Today we’re introducin’
this ‘un here: Daz Bones!
He was a member of Baroque Works,
Member of secret crime syndicate Baroque Works
a criminal syndicate once led by Crocodile.
His codename: Mr. 1!
Codename: Mr. 1
He was the highest ranking commander.
Dice-Dice Fruit
Allows the user to turn
any body part into blades
He ate the Dice-Dice Fruit,
an’ can transform any o’
his body parts into blades!
He was born on January 1st
an’ likes yerba mate ‘n dry-cured prosciutto!
He tried to kill Princess Vivi
of the Alabasta Kingdom,
but went down to Zoro.
He was imprisoned on Level Four
of the Great Prison, Impel Down,
but took advantage of all the havoc caused by Luffy
and his pals, and escaped along with Crocodile!
Sure, I’ll tag along...
Because it’s you asking.
You got to me right as
boredom was starting to hit.
Durin’ the Paramount War, he protected Luffy
from Mihawk’s attacks on Crocodile’s orders.
By the way, we replicated
his Dice-Dice Fruit ability usin’ our tech,
and made it so S-Hawk can use it!
That’s all for today!
Since you watched it all,
you owe us a research fund donation!
See y’all next time!
CP-0 and the Straw Hats, unable to compete...
...with the overwhelming force of the Seraphim!
Their non-stop, relentless onslaught gradually pushes Luffy and his allies into a corner!
Can they find a path to victory
in the face of these flawless enemies?
Next time, on One Piece:
Survive!
Deathmatch with Humanity’s Ultimate Form
Deathmatch with Humanity's Ultimate Form
I’m gonna be the Pirate King!