(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The Straw Hats were looking for Vegapunk,
but were cornered
by some unknown operative's trickery.
The video feeds...
...are going off one by one.
Someone else is...
...in the lab.
What?
No way!
They're not listening to you!
That was close!
This is a really troubling situation.
What if the communication failure...
...and this situation of
being trapped in the barrier...
GOOD
...were all calculated?
That means somebody...
...wants to kill us all!
Stella!
You're here!
Who did this to you?
Shaka.
The hands of evil closed in
on Shaka who found Vegapunk.
I'm glad that you're okay!
I'll unlock the door now!
Hey...
Shaka... Who are you here with?
What?
Shaka!
"The Second Ohara!
The Mastermind's Ambition!"
It's getting quite cold.
How much longer will it take?
We'll soon arrive at Egghead!
Soon, huh?
Maybe I should get some food.
Let the Vice Admirals know, too.
Yes, sir.
How is he doing?
JUSTICE
He is about to have a meal.
ST. JAYGARCIA SATURN OF THE ELDERS
Keep your guard up.
Yes, sir!
FUTURE ISLAND EGGHEAD
LABORATORY, FUTURE ISLAND EGGHEAD
BUILDING C, A, B
LABORATORY, 2ND FLOOR, BUILDING B
What?! Uncle Kizaru?!
Yes...
He is on his way here with a fleet of
over a hundred vessels, large and small.
Over a hundred?!
CP-0's mission is to kill Doctor
and wait for Kizaru's arrival.
FABIRIOPHASE FACTORY
They're sending a Navy Admiral...
The Government's stance
is out of the ordinary...
Yes, they must be taking the situation
more seriously than they did with Ohara.
Why?
Reason one. Doctor has inherited
Ohara's forbidden research,
and is making progress with it.
Reason two.
Egghead has battle capabilities
which Ohara didn't have!
You mean the Seraphim
and all of the Pacifistas?
Yeah, those are good enough reasons
for enormous forces to be deployed.
Contact me when anything happens!
All communication devices in the Labophase
are inoperative.
Got it.
Clank.
Did you hear that?!
Learn from history
what the Navy is gonna do here!
Are we, and this research facility,
going to suffer the same fate as Ohara?!
That's right! There's no time to think!
Hurry up and get off of Egghead!
Go!
Get the ship ready!
We'll leave the island!
Before the Navy gets here!
Just as Sentomaru-san told us!
Okay... There is no turning back now...
How are you going to settle this?
Old Man Punk...
Usopp! Lilith!
LABORATORY, 3RD FLOOR, BUILDING C
You shitty brat! Unpetrify me!
I lowered my guard on my right side,
but I still got my left side!
Do you want a taste of my Weapons Left?!
But if you surrender now,
maybe I'll forgive...
No... I just...
Hey, are you listening?!
I'll shoot you if you don't stop!
Why?! S-Snake!
Whose...
Whose orders are you working under?!
Please don't do it!
Stop!
Pythagoras!
Wait! Hey!
Wait!
LABORATORY, 2ND FLOOR, BUILDING A
I wonder if everyone's okay...
I've been hearing huge explosions
and screams.
We know that the Seraphim are rampaging.
It's incomprehensible!
I thought the Seraphim were on our side...
Perhaps someone
overrode the command again.
Who would do that?
Someone inside the lab...
I'm worried about Nami and the others...
They'll be okay.
There's a person who instantly rushes to her
when he hears her scream.
Oh, you're right!
Teams in combat can't go anywhere.
While everyone's fighting, there's the risk of
something happening to Vegapunk.
We should continue searching.
Yeah! Let's find him ASAP!
Oh, there is a room
that was once used and is now sealed off.
What?!
I don't think
anyone would go there though...
Let's go check.
Maybe we'll find some trace of a clue.
Show us the way, Atlas!
Yeah!
LABORATORY, 3RD FLOOR, BUILDING A
Hey, Little Jinbe.
I don't know if you're
the pinnacle of science or whatever...
I won't let you even touch Nami-san.
Edison, stay with me!
Edison!
Nami-san! I'll lighten myself up
and go find Vegapunk!
Uh-huh!
Oh no!
Sanji-san! You're awesome!
Little Jinbe...
Do you know... the power of love?!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Damn! The flames on their backs
haven't gone out yet!
Yeah.
They're quite tough.
When the flames on their backs go out,
that's the only chance that our attacks will work,
and that's only for a moment.
That's how fast they switch
from offense to defense.
Hey! While we were focused on their flames,
the Hawkeye look-alike is gone!
Where did he go?!
They must've changed
their target priority.
They'll save the troublesome ones for later
and eliminate the weak ones first.
That way, they could also upset
the tough ones by killing their friends.
That's so aggravating!
This is exactly the kind of ruthless tactic that
inhumane bastards like them would come up with.
Luffy, leave him to me! I'll chase him!
I'm counting on you, Zoro!
Oh no!
Hey, Usopp! Go with him!
He can get lost easily!
He's so high-maintenance!
Wait, Roronoa!
Hey, did you call me "Usopp"?!
You're fighting me right now!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
Go out, fire!
You fool. Wait, Straw Hat! Think!
You'll never beat him that way!
This is everything that happened
the day before the famous Egghead Incident.
But it all started three months earlier.
SACRED MARIJOA, THREE MONTHS AGO
Sacred Marijoa, three months ago.
...is... ...g... ...d...
This is E... ...d...
I can't hear you!
This is Egghe... ...d...
I need to talk to... ...igher-ups.
What do you want from them?!
...need to talk to the higher-ups...
I said "What do you want?!"
Dr. Vegapunk is...
...researching the 100-Year Void.
Upon receiving that tip,
CP5 was dispatched to Egghead
to verify the truth,
but found no evidence.
After completing the investigation, the ship
mysteriously disappeared on its way back.
To investigate the disappearance,
first CP7, then CP8 headed to Egghead,
but no one returned to the Government.
This is Egghead...
Put me through to the higher-ups...
Later, there was a meeting
between the Five Elders and another figure,
and the betrayal of the genius scientist
researching the 100-Year Void...
...became clear.
Clank.
The Five Elders decided on
Dr. Vegapunk's assassination.
Cipher Pol "Aigis" Zero,
tasked with that mission, set sail.
However, one of the Five Elders
decided to go in person,
in anticipation of
Vegapunk's counterattack.
He assigned Admiral Kizaru as his escort.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
In addition, reinforcements were requested
to various Navy branches.
The deployment was on the scale of a war.
However, another ship came calling...
That of the Emperor of the Sea,
Straw Hat Luffy.
The Government was not content
with the unexpected intruders' landing.
See?!
Things are getting complicated again!
It's them again!
In any case, the incident will come to an end
the next day,
and the outcome will shock the world
in an unexpected way.
OLD DEVIL FRUIT RESEARCH LABORATORY
UNDERGROUND
Hey!
Is this all your doing?!
Answer me!
W-Why did you do this?
York!
Hey, Stella!
I'm going to become a Celestial Dragon!
What are you talking about, York?!
You've been to Marijoa, right?!
Do you want to be as filthy as they are?!
That's something Shaka would say.
But he's dead now!
It's confusing. We're all Vegapunk.
Wouldn't one Dr. Vegapunk be...
...enough in this world?
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Sakazuki!
He is the Admiral of the Fleet for the Navy
and a Logia type Mag-Mag Fruit user.
He can turn his body into magma
and manipulate it at will!
He was born on August 16th
and likes white rice and hot pepper!
Sakazuki believes in thorough justice,
and during the Buster Call at Ohara, he even
sank a refugee ship full of ordinary islanders.
In the Paramount War,
he beat pirate after pirate...
...as one of the Navy's greatest powers,
the Three Admirals.
He eventually pierced Ace's belly
with magma, taking his life.
As long as you're a Navy soldier,
you can't forgive those thugs, the pirates!
Later, he fought Kuzan for the position of
the Admiral of the Fleet after Sengoku had retired.
After a fierce battle, Sakazuki won
and became the new Admiral of the Fleet.
He has a rugged face and personality.
He is always hostile to the Straw Hats.
He'll continue to be a major threat
to Luffy and his team.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Emperor Red-Haired
continues to reign over the seas!
Fearlessly confronting him is a man
with a bounty of 3 billion berries
from the Worst Generation!
Both holding fast to their beliefs,
the two captains in a deep historical rivalry
face off in distant Elbaph!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Clash! Shanks vs. Eustass Kid"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!