(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
"Run, Koby!
A Desperate Escape Strategy!"
I'm sorry!
I won again!
You guys sure have a lot of free time.
Give me the keys to the cells.
Who the hell are you?
Hey.
Hold your tongue, you fools.
PERONA, HOLLOW-HOLLOW FRUIT,
GHOST PRINCESS
What did you say?!
You have a lot of nerve, young lady.
Is "Shut up" easier for you to understand?
Kneel down.
Negative...
...Hollow!
Negative! Negative!
I'm sorry that
I have less courage than a water flea.
I wanna quit pirating
and live quietly in a prison.
I got them.
Let's go, guys.
They're all out of spirit...
Hey! You!
What?
Ouch. Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, you.
What?
You are...
Are you the one they call Koby the hero?!
KOBY, NAVY HQ CAPTAIN (SWORD)
You got captured!
For a supposed hero,
you're below expectations.
Hey!
I'll help you out,
so free Moria-sama who is being held
in a cell further in from here!
Moria?
Gecko Moria is here?
Are you telling me to collaborate
with pirates?
Yeah, that's right!
Moria-sama's life is at risk!
I'm a Navy soldier...
Gecko Moria is a pirate...
Free him, you say?
I have big news!
Captain Koby has escaped!
PIRATE ISLAND OF BEEHIVE, NEW WORLD
Are you serious?!
Ya-hoo!
Now that he's escaped,
he's no longer Commodore's quarry, right?!
How much will we get if we capture him?!
Yeehaw!
Well, we don't need to put a bounty on him!
Cross Guild will pay for us!
I bought odds on him with a Win ticket!
The payout is gonna be big!
How much will we get if we kill him?!
You're gonna be surprised!
His bounty is five stars!
That means five treasure chests!
That's about 500 million berries!
His bounty is five stars?!
A captain's bounty is usually one star!
All right! Let's hit the jackpot!
The hunting begins now!
Everyone! We're almost there.
Hang in there!
Koby-san,
thank you for saving slaves like us...
Hold on. Don't call yourself a slave!
You're all unfortunate victims
who were captured by pirates.
I'm a Navy soldier,
and I'll save you all at any cost.
Pizarro-san! What's the matter?!
I feel a tickle
on the left side of my chest-meow.
That's where slaves are held
before the sale...
Are they breaking out?!
The slaves escaped?!
Can we hunt them all, Pizarro-san?!
Don't be silly! You guys are so savage!
Bring them all back! Don't even kill Koby!
Or I'll tell Teach!
Why does that rock talk?!
He knows that we're here!
Let's hurry up!
What?
This is it for us...
Just run away before we slow you down.
Everyone, cheer up.
Don't give up hope.
I'll be the bait,
so make sure you all get away!
Well then...
We'll meet again!
Thanks!
Thank you, Captain Koby...
You're a saint!
PRISON
SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
CLEAR-CLEAR FRUIT, INVISIBLE MAN
Why don't you capture them yourself,
Pizarro?
Then Teach will get mad at me later!
"THE CORRUPT KING" AVALO PIZARRO
ISLE-ISLE FRUIT, ISLAND-MAN
Because whenever I move,
I end up breaking things-meow.
Can I go?
Vasco Shot. What are you gonna do-meow?
If I set the town on fire,
they'll have nowhere to run.
"HEAVY DRINKER" VASCO SHOT
GLUG-GLUG FRUIT, BOOZE-MAN
Hey, don't do that!
That would be a huge fire-meow!
Teach would get pissed-meow!
No problem. Leave it to me.
No-meow!
We just finished repairing Rocky Port!
Would you rather leave it to Wolf?
Wolf?
"THE GIANT BATTLESHIP" SANJUAN WOLF
HUGE-HUGE FRUIT, GIGANTIFICATION-MAN
That's out of the question-meow!
The whole town will be gone-meow!
I need...
I need to buy more time!
Where did that bastard go?!
I can't go that way, either!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, you look cute and docile,
but you're surprisingly bold...
I... I'm sorry!
No, you don't have to be.
Because I'll get a lot of money.
Mr. Five Star!
I found him! Right here!
Oh no! They found me!
Damn! I guess I can't outrun them!
I have to...
I have to somehow keep luring them
until everyone else goes out to sea!
Hey!
Koby the hero!
Koby the hero,
I want to turn this island...
...this Pirate Island...
...into a full-fledged nation!
A World Government-affiliated nation!
I'm gonna be the king!
Blackbeard Kingdom!
What do you think?!
That's ridiculous.
There's no way it'd be accepted!
It's a country of criminals!
Hey, don't ruin someone else's dream!
I'll negotiate with them
using you as a bargaining chip.
If the Government and the Navy start negotiating
with terrorists, we're doomed!
JUSTICE
And you're wasting your time.
Because...
...I'm a member of SWORD!
Sword? What the hell is that?
Oh, I see...
This isn't gonna go well.
Give up on the trade, Teach.
SWORD...
That means...
...he's a Navy soldier but also not.
He surrendered his Navy Code.
SWORD is a group of...
...Navy soldiers
who have submitted their resignations.
So they can pick a fight with the Four Emperors
without permission from above.
They can also do whatever they like
and disregard any orders.
They're wild-card commandoes!
In exchange,
the Navy is in no way responsible
for their actions
and can fire them anytime.
I see!
That's the difference between the half-wits
who are waiting for permission to fight us
and the ones who just charge in
without a care in the world!
I like that style. I get it now!
But...
...I'm not gonna change my plan!
I'll try anyway!
Even if you're a SWORD member,
people call you a hero,
so I wonder if the Navy
can stick to the decision of abandoning you.
I'll ask the public!
Then the Government
can't remain unblemished!
Until then, lock him up!
I can't wait!
Don't let him escape!
Get back here! Koby!
I cooperated with a pirate...
But necessity knows no law!
Instead of keeping guard,
I wanna hunt a Five Star, too.
What's that?
I hope those who escaped are all fine...
Three Navy soldiers showed up at the port!
What? Navy soldiers?! No way!
Hurry up!
They're strong! Be careful!
Did someone come to rescue me?
No, no! How arrogant I am!
I feel ashamed!
Who are they?! Why are they so strong?!
They're heading towards
the center of the town!
What do they want?!
How would I know?! Stop them!
What? Guns don't work on them!
That's enough!
His head got cut off!
I took one down!
That serves you right!
That hurt...
What?! Logia type?!
What's wrong with him?!
His body's like clay!
Where are you, Koby?!
H-Hey...
Aren't those buildings moving?!
No, stupid! They're not!
You drink too much!
Hey! Be a good little boy!
Move forward!
There is a strange woman. Who is that?
Come on! Brace up!
You look pathetic!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
She's whipping a building...
Why are you staring at me?
What? No, I...
S-She's a Navy soldier?!
How rare is it to see a Navy soldier
when you're a pirate?
KUJAKU, NAVY HQ REAR ADMIRAL (SWORD)
GRANDDAUGHTER OF GREAT ADVISER TSURU
WHIP-WHIP FRUIT, DISCIPLINE-WOMAN
Come here. You're so cute.
I'll discipline you.
You're cornered, Koby!
Oh no! I'm surrounded!
Take aim!
Shoot all at once!
Fire!
This is it for me!
Everyone's in place!
We'll be ready soon!
Wait for me, my beloved pupil!
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Koby!
He is a Navy captain and
a member of SWORD, a Top Secret Special Force.
He is called "Koby the hero"!
He was born on May 13th and
likes buttered potatoes and Rika's onigiri!
Once, while being imprisoned by pirates
and forced to work like a horse, he met Luffy!
He was encouraged by Luffy
and successfully got away from the pirates.
After Captain Morgan's incident,
he enlisted in the Navy, which he had
dreamed of doing since he was a child!
Since he is kind-hearted, he couldn't bear
the loss of so many lives during the Paramount War,
and his desperate action
led to the end of the war.
We're wasting people's lives!
He continued to train himself,
saved civilians in the Rocky Port Incident,
and rose to the rank of captain!
But now he has been abducted by Blackbeard...
Will he be able to escape
from the Pirate Island of Beehive?!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
A huge warship comes flying down from the sky!
The man who is standing on its bow
is the hero of the Navy, Vice Admiral Garp!
To save the cornered Koby, he tightens his fist!
A giant, deeply-felt blow is thrown down
on the chaotic Beehive!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"For the Beloved Pupil -
The Fist of Vice Admiral Garp!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!