(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
Sabo-san!
Everyone!
I'm back!
I heard about Kuma-san.
I'm sorry.
All your efforts have gone to waste.
Sabo. Even the captains can't hear
what you have to say?
Yeah... It might endanger their lives
to know it.
What's it about?
This Reverie was tumultuous...
I'll tell you all about
what really happened...
at the Holy Land Mary Geoise!
"Sabo Returns -
The Shocking Truth to Be Told!"
KAMABAKKA QUEENDOM
We accomplished all our missions.
We had three general objectives.
Declaring war by destroying
the symbol of the Celestial Dragons.
Freeing as many slaves as possible
and rescuing Kuma-san.
And destroying the food reserves
in the Land of Gods.
How did it turn out?
Well...
We've caught enough of
the world's attention.
Thanks to you for keeping
most of the Naval forces busy,
the citizens of 12 countries revolted,
encouraged by us,
and eight of them were successful.
They called it the Eight-Nation Revolution,
but one of the countries,
the Kingdom of Lulusia...
...mysteriously vanished.
You witnessed it, right?
Anyway,
you made the world a lot better!
It hasn't been reported in the newspapers,
but seven nations
that brought about revolutions...
...are declining both to pay the Heavenly Offerings
and to export natural resources to the Government.
The Revolutionary Army is attacking
the Government's supply carriers around the world...
...to keep resources
from reaching Mary Geoise!
HOLY LAND MARY GEOISE
Because it's located so high up, people say
Mary Geoise is an unbreakable fortress,
But I bet they can't stand
our starvation tactics!
They must learn what it is like
to live without money and food!
Heehaw!
We can expect some effect, right?
Yes, it's highly likely.
Not all supplies are being cut off,
but I'm sure it's steadily
starting to torment them.
And of course, they're not
the kind of people who will just endure it.
When they dispatch the Holy Knights,
the real battle will start!
The Holy Knights...
Sabo!
I mean, Flame Emperor boy!
You're their number one target now!
That nickname doesn't sit well with me.
But that nickname instantly
made you a household name.
Even if it's not true,
the assassination of King Cobra
made you a hero.
From the perspective of the insurgents
all over the world,
everyone involved with the World Government
is the same.
Of course, there are some kings
who should be blamed for misrule,
but there are also many righteous
and competent kings in the world.
Among such kings,
King Cobra of Alabasta was known
as an excellent and benevolent monarch,
but sometimes,
the truth is not told correctly.
But I'm...
...fine with that.
I feel bad for King Cobra...
But if it'll kindle the flames of revolution!
You're unshakable.
Now, explain to us!
The truth...
KING COBRA ASSASSINATED
...behind this shocking news!
We were all trying to speculate
the reason with tears in our eyes.
Because we wanted to believe you!
What I...
...witnessed on that day...
More than a month ago,
during the Reverie, the world council
held in the Holy Land Mary Geoise.
It's an emergency! Someone trespassed
into the Land of the Gods!
Please evacuate immediately!
The food storage exploded-eh!
Do something, bureaucrats!
There are intruders-eh!
Four Revolutionary Army captains
have been identified on the premises!
Catch them now!
What are you doing?! Keep walking-eh!
Damn!
Not only the symbol of the World Nobles,
but they even targeted
our luxurious food reserves!
The poor are jealous of us-eh!
Make sure you catch and behead them!
Everyone!
It's dangerous so please evacuate!
We should execute all the guards
after that-amasu!
You can't let this happen to us
and get away with it-amasu!
I told you to hurry up! You sluggish dog!
What if something happens to me!
Go faster-eh!
Ouch!
You useless bastard!
Forget it! I'll walk myself-eh!
You're fired-eh.
You piece of trash!
My gun!
Who are you-eh?
How could you...
...take other people's lives so lightly?!
Karasoot!
Run to the east side of town.
What?
O-Okay!
St. Pluming! Please evacuate quickly!
Cipher Pol! What took you so long-eh?!
Get rid of that vermin now-eh!
The Revolutionary Army?! Take him down!
We got him!
Let's fill him with bullets!
Wipe him out completely-eh!
What?!
H-He really got wiped out!
Just who is he?
Did we kill him?
Obelisoots!
You piece of trash.
KARASU (SOOT-SOOT FRUIT POWER USER)
CAPTAIN OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
NORTHERN FORCES
I feel two tremendous surges of Haki!
I can't believe they attacked Mary Geoise...
They're such reckless bastards!
Help me already-eh!
No!
Sir! Ma'am! I'm begging you!
Please let us escape, too!
Help!
There you are!
I'm here to help you all!
None of you move!
Laser Shooter!
Hurry up! Wait at the east side of town!
We'll get out of here together!
Th...
--Thank you!
You can thank me later!
Make sure you get there!
Look at that!
LINDBERGH, CAPTAIN OF
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY SOUTHERN FORCES
Lindbergh!
The enemies are coming this way!
Hurry up freeing the slaves!
Got it!
Something is coming...
Something strong!
JUSTICE
Crow...
...Soul Lotus!
Come back!
You slaves should not defy me-eh!
What's this-eh? The ground!
What's going on-eh?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
A Giant?!
That's not nice!
You have to stop shooting people like that!
You guys, get out of here now!
Go to the east side of town!
My friends are expecting you!
MORLEY, CAPTAIN OF
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY WESTERN FORCES
Be careful!
Thank you!
You damn punks of the Revolutionary Army!
You do understand exactly
what it means...
...to go against the Celestial Dragons,
don't you?!
Gee!
What's wrong with this boy?!
He gets mad so easily!
Because you guys...
...are destroying the town!
Where did your leader go?!
Why are you asking me questions?!
You're so naughty!
You pervert!
Look who's talking!
What are you wearing?!
Hey, my eyes are up here!
Whoa. Why are you staring at me?
Do you...
...like me?!
What?!
Shut up!
Hey! Ryokugyu!
Ryokugyu!
If any of us gets hurt,
you'll be sentenced to death-eh!
It's hard to fight! Just go away already!
What?
Hey, Fujitora! What are you doing?!
I'll bring down...
...a meteor.
You can't do that! Stop it, you fool!
Two admirals...
If this were not the Land of the Gods,
they could easily obliterate the landscape.
Yet they're fighting so roughly.
I guess there's no room for us to step in.
Do they wanna destroy Mary Geoise?!
Even though they have the disadvantage,
the Revolutionary Army is sticking with it.
Their captains must be quite strong...
So intense!
Well...
We should get going.
Sabo!
Have you found the keys to the collars?!
It won't take much longer!
I found out where they are.
Lindbergh!
What is it?
Kuma-san came to Pangaea Castle!
What?!
I saw Saint Rosward and his son Charlos...
SABO, CHIEF OF STAFF OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
I think they're on their way to finish
what they attempted at the Mingling Courtyard.
What?!
What are you...?!
Please stop!
I found one-eh! I found a giant Mermaid-eh!
I'll make her my pet this time for sure.
With this one's strength...
I guess they can't give up on
Princess Shirahoshi...
How dare they use Kuma-san for that!
Of course, I won't let them do that!
Morley, get ready!
Okay!
I will save... Kuma-san at any cost!
Dad!
Where are you going all by yourself?
Princess Vivi.
You're... from CP-0.
Please go back to your room.
Can you leave me alone?!
I'm going to go to
Vice Admiral Garp for help!
We will protect you all.
You guys didn't protect Shirahoshi earlier,
did you?!
I bet you know!
They'll come after her again!
Your Majesty.
You'd better not to push yourself...
No, I'm okay.
Chaka, Pell.
I finally get to meet the Five Elders.
I may never have
an opportunity like this again.
Let's go.
Stop!
Only King Cobra is permitted
an audience with the Five Elders.
But...
...Cobra-sama is not in good health.
Stand back.
Cobra-sama...
This won't take long,
but I think it'll be boring to
just wait outside.
I need you to guard Vivi.
She's still so mischievous,
and I can't stop worrying about her.
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Morley!
He is a Giant and the captain of
the Revolutionary Army Western Forces.
He uses the Push-Push Fruit power
which enables him to push anything away!
His bounty is 290 million berries.
He was born on September 11
and likes bagna cauda!
He was once an ill-famed pirate
and imprisoned at Impel Down.
But he successfully escaped the prison
with his Push-Push Fruit power.
The tunnels he carved to escape
later became New Kama Land.
He's serving as a captain
in the Revolutionary Army,
and defeated Blackbeard's subordinate Peachbeard
who was attacking the Kingdom of Lulusia.
Shoot him to death!
What?!
Stop it, boys!
At the Holy Land Mary Geoise,
he declared war on the Celestial Dragons
along with Sabo and the other captains,
and they successfully rescued
Bartholomew Kuma.
I should be careful
because he can push me away, too.
Anyway, I really wanna know
what happened at the Holy Land Mary Geoise!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
The Celestial Dragons take advantage
of their authority and do whatever they like.
While even the royal families
turn a blind eye to their unruly behavior,
two pirates stand up to them!
They, who pledged to serve Luffy,
bring down the hammer of wrath!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Holy Land in Tumult!
Sai and Leo's Full-Power Blow!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!