Excuse me, thank you!
This is what everyone's
talking about in the capital!
I got excited!
Will the decisive battle start soon?!
He knocked him back!
If this is something that you want to do,...
...maybe I can help you a little bit.
Tonoyasu!
The Star of Ebisu Town!
Teach me! That's exactly it!
That Grandpa did this?!
Grandpa! That was awesome!
How did you use Haki?!
It's too much for an old body...
You bastards!
Go! Madilloman!
Hold on, Grandpa!
流桜 Ryuo, Flowing Sakura
You call it Haki,
but we call it Ryuo in the Wano Country.
Ryuo?
It has the meaning of "flow."
I'm sure your Haki flows in your body, too.
First, feel it.
All right!
Flowing Haki...
Don't press too hard!
Damn! That's not it!
Don't strain yourself!
Allow the unused Haki in your body
to flow to your fist!
All right!
Bring in more!
Don't push your luck!
Go to hell, Straw Hat!
Kick the Grandpa's ass, too!
Push them against the
wall already, you fools!
I'm starving to death...
How long will it take to
get there, Okiku-chan?
I think we will enter Udon sometime tonight.
It's taking so long...
I wanna eat it...
お汁粉 Oshiruko, Red-Bean Soup
The sweet, sweet Oshiruko!
The Oshiruko...
Stop!
Don't look at me!
Stop laughing!
Go away!
I see, I see...
By seeing this flyer,
we learned about the great battle.
Two birds on fire...
That means twilight on the day of the Fire Festival!
The rendezvous point for the raid
is Habu Port!
Oh, Kin'emon-kun must've given
a lot of thought to it!
Kin'emon... kun?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Shinobu-chan!
Well, I understand.
It's no wonder that you have a glum look.
The plan is ruined.
Even the enemies know about it.
Mm-hm... That is right...
Our allies with the Reversed
Crescent Moon tattoo...
...signifying rebellion are getting
caught one after another...
It'd be nice to take it back
and say, "It was all fake,"...
...but then it'll mislead your allies, too...
Before this, however, I didn't know about
the crescent moon ankle tattoo.
You were able to secure allies like me.
I'm sure there are tons of people
who got motivated by seeing this!
Please tell Kin'emon-kun and the others!
That we'll fight along with you at any cost!
Kin'emon... kun?
I'm glad to see you two, too...
Now, it's getting busy!
Hey, wait!
There are tons of people
who won't last the week before the great battle!
So if you'll excuse me!
A handsome man,...
...a beautiful woman,...
...and a town girl!
Well, good to see you all!
Now, who's that Grandpa?
I was listening, but I couldn't tell
how you guys are connected to him.
Me, neither!
Well, he was quite cheerful!
Who is that Tonoyasu-san?
Yasu-san! Play with us!
All right!
Well, I must say...
We have no idea!
What do you mean?!
You were talking to him
not knowing who he was?!
Well, he just went on and on, so...
How could you forget someone like him?!
Well, since he addressed
us with "kun" and "chan"...
I thought if he had been someone important in the past,
it would be rude to ask him!
He was addressing you casually,
so could he be your childhood friend...
Or an instructor of some kind?
Or an older friend?
Who is he?!
What?!
Gramps, Gramps, how's the abdominal pain?
Oh, Yasu-san!
Straw Hat!
Disappear!
This isn't it!
This isn't it, either!
Damn!
No! No!
Dammit! Where is it?!
My Haki!
It's not flowing to my fist!
Whoa-whoa, he took down too many, that idiot.
Damn!
Haki won't flow to an angry fist!
Who's next?!
Bring it on!
Thank you as always.
My body feels heavy.
It's not that much,
but I brought you some millet and water!
They'll give you energy!
You're such a nice person, Yasu-san...
You're good at praising!
I'm so happy to be called a nice person!
I'll give you two more millet grains!
I'll leave them here, so don't forget to eat!
Thank you very much, Yasu-san.
See you, Gramps!
Hey! Seaweed Shop Granny!
Do you have enough medicine?!
No, but just seeing you cheers me up.
You're such a man-killer!
Oh, mister, how's your knee?!
Yasu-san! Let's play!
Hanko! How's your sick mother doing?
Osaki-san, how's your baby?
Up, up!
Yasu-san!
Come see us, too!
Here, everyone! Take these!
Thank you as always!
Tonoyasu must be making a lot of money.
No one else can give out food.
No, he is not...
He only gets paid peanuts.
What?
His only daughter named Toko-chan
was sold to the capital and has been working there,...
...but she sends most of her
earnings to Yasu-san.
Toko?
I'm not otoko (male)!
It must be her!
He said Toko-chan took the trouble
to send it,...
...so he shouldn't have it all to himself.
He gives out food to those who can't work
every day.
He doesn't eat much himself.
His facial expressions and body movements are so goofy,
but everyone's always loved him.
He's a saint.
Daddy...
Daddy!
It's bedtime! Go to sleep!
Damn!
Continue this again tomorrow?
Let me fight more!
I'm hungry...
Won't you even let me eat something?!
Stop barking like a dog!
Shut up and go to sleep!
I'm gonna become a mummy by tomorrow!
Can I ask you something, Straw Hat Man?
What is it?
Why would you want to fight Kaido?!
I heard you once lost to him in Kuri.
They're annoying...
Okay, this is good.
Grandpa!
四皇 Yonko, Four Emperors
Do you know the Yonko?
No...
There are four great pirates
called emperors across the world,...
...and Kaido is one of them.
I'm gonna become the King of Pirates,...
...so I have to take them all down!
The King of Pirates?!
You mean a man like Roger?
Do you know Gold Roger?!
He came to this country a long time ago.
Oh, that's what Kin'emon said!
What?! Kin'emon?!
How do you know that name?!
What is that?!
What?!
You're... R-Raizo!
Straw Hat-san...
You...
This is Raizo, right?
I am!
What?!
What's going on with you guys?!
How are you alive?!
Raizo!
Let me explain, Hyogoro-dono!
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
sign: Arrest
There he is! Ushimitsu Kozo!
Surrender!
Catch him!
Is it true, Raizo?!
I... cannot believe...
that you're the famous Hyogoro-dono...
This is hard to take in.
Are you saying that you really crossed through
20 years of time...
...and came from the Wano Country on that fateful day?
Yes! By Toki-sama's power!
I can't believe it!
I can't believe you, Caribou!
Please don't say that, Straw Hat-san!
What do you mean, Raizo?!
You thought it was the key to my cuffs,
but it was to his?!
Don't hate me like that!
I may come in handy.
I'm your subordinate from now on, mister!
But, in exchange,...
...let me get on board when you're leaving!
Oh, so you're stuck here!
I'm sorry for what I did to you in the past!
I have changed now...
Okay, there's no problem if you've changed.
What?!
Thank you... very much!
Is this some kind of trap?!
It scares me how easy that was!
Luffytaro-dono!
This guy has quite an interesting power.
He could be useful!
Without giving up...
greedily...
I held on to life...
I'm glad that I did!
Hyogoro-dono?!
That was close...
I thought I was only gonna
die miserably here...
I was accepting my death.
Had this not happened,
I would've died...
...not knowing anything.
So the Akazaya samurai are alive!
Oden's son, Kozuki Momonosuke, is alive!
The fire of rebellion....
...isn't extinguished!
Raizo! Straw Hat Man!
When it comes to this,
even a dotard like me still can contribute!
Will you please let me join you?!
Oh, we could ask for none better than him!
Luffy-dono! He used to be the greatest yakuza boss
in the Wano Country!
What?! I knew you were a big deal back
in the day, Grandpa!
You said that you were recruiting allies
in the Flower Capital now, didn't you?!
That is right!
It's surely fate that brought you to Udon!
In this Prisoner Mine,...
...there are four other excavation sites
just as large as this one!
There are tens of thousands
of prisoners in Udon!
However, not everyone was imprisoned
for robbery or assault...
Most of the prisoners are here for...
...treason against Orochi!
Oh! Why didn't I think of that?!
Rage from across the country is pooled here!
The yakuza bosses who once supported the Wano Country
behind the scenes are all here, too!
I'll talk to them!
I'm sure they'll be happy to fight for Kozuki!
And Raizo! In that cell...
I know.
I have had a word with Kawamatsu.
I will release him first!
I see!
Then if I break this place down,...
...everyone will ally with us!
Luffy-dono! You are too loud!
It is not that easy...
All right! Our plan has been set!
Bring me something to eat!
I got it!
Mister!
When did you get that?!
Yum-yum!
It's Oshiruko!
Hey, you got to have some, too!
Thank you.
Let me...
...eat...
I'm hungry... and tired...
No Oshiruko yet? Okiku-chan...
Sharkodile-san is exhausted, too.
But we have already entered Udon!
Wait for me...
My Oshiruko...
Is this really a good idea?
Oh, it's good!
Another bowl!
Oshiruko!
I'm gonna stuff myself silly!
News of the Flower Capital's beloved
Ushimitsu Kozo who sides with the weak...
...and crushes the strong...
...spreads like wildfire
across the Wano Country.
Meanwhile, after meeting up with Brook,...
...Zoro and the others learn about
Orochi's despicable plot and a cruel truth.
Next time on One Piece!
Meet Easily!
Identity of Ushimitsu Kozo!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Meet Easily
Identity of Ushimitsu Kozo