Orochi...
...and Kaido...
Let's get them!
We have been waiting for you to say that
all this time!
On that day, five years ago,...
...I made a promise with you two...
That was all a lie, wasn't it, Kaido?!
That's right.
That was all a lie.
We didn't have that many underlings back then...
If you were a crazy man who wouldn't care about the toll of human life just as I heard,...
...it would've been a tough battle for us.
But you believed Orochi's words
and chose the way that no one would be hurt.
I made a good choice that day.
Let's talk about the future now.
The Moment of Conclusion!
Oden VS Kaido!
Wait, wait! Is this how strong samurai are?!
Don't hesitate! We're not outnumbered!
Advance, advance!
Follow Oden-sama!
You're dead!
What's happened?!
Who are you?
I'm taking the liberty of backing you up.
Oden-sama, I'm sure you don't remember me,...
...but back when Sukiyaki-sama was still alive...
Shinobu from the ninja legion?!
Yes! That's me!
Why are you here all by yourself?
What happened to the others?
Kozuki's ninja legion...
Fukurokuju sold out to Orochi.
Those who couldn't trust their silly lord
can't be blamed.
I've always wanted to serve you one day.
I'm still Kozuki's ninja!
A tough journey lies ahead of us, Shinobu!
Yes, I know! I'll accompany you to the end!
Let's go, you guys!
Take this!
How dare you!
Hey, Hiyori! Wait!
No way!
I received a letter from Oden by a messenger.
It says, "My wife and children will be targeted.
Please save them."
Momonosuke...
I mean, Momonosuke-sama is already eight...
Otoki-san, you have to be prepared.
If Oden loses...
...this country is finished.
Oden-san!
This is the first unit. We've been taken down.
Kozuki Oden is way stronger than we imagined!
Tsk! How pathetic!
Why does it take so much time
to finish off 11 samurai?!
We have a thousand troops.
I can't bear to watch.
I'll go!
What the?!
What is about to happen?!
熱息 Bolo Breath,
Heat Breath
Why aren't you giving up already?!
You think just 11 of you
can take down this many troops?
If you wanna fight me,...
...come up here!
Yeah, here I come!
Charge!
Get Oden's head!
Let's stall the underlings!
Yeah!
I won't let you!
I'll fight you guys!
Fine by me!
Kin-san!
華手裏剣 Ninpo Hana Shuriken,
Ninja Art Flower Shuriken
Ninpo Hana Shuriken
Kaido!
All I wanna do...
...is cut off your head!
What a funny man!
桃源とうげん白滝 Togen Shirataki,
Paradise White Waterfall
Oden-sama!
Kozuki Oden!
I've been waiting for a guy like you!
I won't let you have free reign
in the Wano Country anymore!
Interesting.
おでん二刀流 Oden Nitoryu,
Oden Two-Sword Style
桃源とうげん十拳 Togen Totsuka,
Paradise Ten Hands
Oden-sama!
I can't lose now!
I can't lose!
What?!
桃源とうげん十拳 Togen Totsuka,
Paradise Ten Hands
Yes!
Did he wound the invincible Kaido-sama?!
This is it!
Don't ever come back...
...to the Wano Country!
Help!
Father!
Father, help me!
Momo!
It's me!
Oden-sama!
Ashura!
Oden-sama...
Thus, Kozuki Oden and the Akazaya members'
legendary battle came to an end.
The intense battle between the Akazaya samurai
and the Beasts Pirates...
...set a forest in Udon ablaze
which didn't die down until a rainy day five days later.
Mother!
When will Father come home?!
I made a balloon for him!
Oh, look at that!
Mother?
Can't wait to see him, huh?
Uh-huh! I really wanna play with Father!
Kozuki Oden, the Daimyo of Kuri,
and the nine others were held captive,...
...and jailed in the Flower Capital
waiting for the verdict as rebels against the Shogun.
Common people didn't know the reason,
so they treated them with cold contempt...
He already let us down...
It's too late.
We don't get to see his weekly naked dance anymore?
That's a shame!
Hey, that's inappropriate!
Oops. Sorry, sorry.
Oden-sama...
Damn! Let me go!
Be quiet!
Oden-sama!
She's your ally, too, right?!
We'll take her to jail!
Who is she?
She's not my retainer!
I guess she came to kill me!
Oden-sama?
Don't call me that! Stop pretending!
Shut up and go away, you damn kunoichi!
The verdict against the samurai has been passed!
The 10 evil samurai who recently raised a rebellion
against the Shogun Orochi...
...are sentenced to public execution
by boiling three days from now!
Three days later...
It's so rare to see someone getting boiled!
They'll be boiled in oil, so it won't take long!
Then, we must hurry!
No!
Momonosuke,
it hasn't been tested for poison yet.
May I?
Mother...
Why is someone after my life?
Because your father is a great man,...
...and you are the one
who will govern this country someday.
Here you go, Momonosuke-sama, Hiyori-sama.
Let's eat!
Brother?
Mother!
Today, is Father really...
Father...
Father!
All right! It's time for the execution!
Now we begin the public execution of Kozuki Oden
and his nine retainers!
In the end, he couldn't beat Kaido!
Even though he's a silly lord,
I thought he was really strong!
What was he good for anyway?!
Walk.
Get in the pot already!
Give me a chance.
I must live!
Don't be ridiculous!
Stop making me laugh by begging for your life!
Just get in!
Help...
G-Go away!
Cut it out!
Why should I give you a chance?!
Kozuki Oden!
What are you up to?!
We'll get in the pot at once.
What?
Set whatever time limit you like
and if any of us survive that long...
Set us free!
A decisive challenge of fate!
An execution by boiling dooms Oden and his family!
Oden does his utmost to ensure the survival of the country,...
...but Orochi drives his wrath against him!
The truth behind their rivalry shakes the Wano Country!
Next time on One Piece!
Sentenced to Boil!
Oden's Deadly Hour!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Sentenced to Boil
Oden's Deadly Hour