Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Orochi...
...and Kaido...
Let's get them!
We have been waiting for you to say that
all this time!
To take back the Land of Wano,
Oden and the Akazaya members
challenged Orochi and Kaido!
This is it!
Don't ever come back...
...to the Land of Wano!
Oden-sama!
Ashura!
Oden-sama...
Oden and the others got caught
and were sentenced to death by boiling.
All right! It's time for the execution!
Get in the pot already!
Give me a chance.
I must live!
We'll get in the pot at once.
What?
Set whatever time limit you like
and if any of us survive that long...
Set us free!
"Boiled to Death!
Oden's One-hour Struggle!"
You idiot!
It'll kill you instantly!
Are you going nuts, Oden?!
What a sore loser!
He's so pathetic even in his final moments!
Hey, bring me a watch!
Yes, sir!
W-What?! H-Hey! Kaido!
Should be fun!
It'll be a big moment for you!
I'll watch it to the end!
I'll give you an hour!
Try to survive!
That long in even a normal bath would be dangerous!
What a funny man!
You won't go back on your word?
Of course not!
Wait a minute, Oden-sama!
Oden-sama!
We must follow our lord!
Let's go!
See you in the other world, you all!
Yeah!
Stay on the plank, you guys!
What are you trying to do, Oden-sama?!
Don't do it, Oden-sama!
This is like living in disgrace!
We must switch places, Oden-sama!
Let us hold you up instead!
Oden-sama!
Shut up and stay there!
It is our duty to protect you!
That's my order!
What's going on?!
His damn retainers aren't in the oil!
All 10 of them are certainly in the pot!
That's fair enough, Oden!
Now, let's start!
Oden-sama...
Get us down!
What's wrong?
It hasn't been even a minute yet.
How can his skin endure it?!
I feel like I am going to die
just from this heat...
If you whine like a loser one more time,
I'll beat you up, Raizo!
We're just sitting up here!
Don't move, cat! It makes it harder to hold!
Oden-sama...
I heard it wouldn't take long...
This is so boring!
I thought they'd scream more
and die in an entertaining manner.
I'm busy!
I've had enough of the silly lord!
Silly lord?!
Damn you!
Who did you call a silly lord?!
If you say it one more time,
I'm gonna kill you!
Don't...
Who's that woman?!
Watch out! She has a sword!
A kunoichi?!
Captain, that's Shinobu!
Why is she running amok?
How could you insult Oden-sama?!
You don't know anything!
It's you all who are the silly ones!
Who do you think worked hard,
so you can live in peace?!
If we lose Oden-sama...
Everyone will realize!
Exactly how much suffering was prevented!
Orochi is not the Shogun or a dictator!
Becoming a leader wasn't his purpose!
Listen! To me,
every single person in this country...
...is a sinner who mistreated
the Kurozumi Clan!
I don't care if they all die!
I became the Shogun...
...to destroy this country!
And to get my revenge!
Destroy the country?!
Why do you hate the country so much?!
Don't be absurd!
My damn grandfather
aspired to become the Shogun!
That was before you were born.
He killed the Daimyo of each region one by one
and was sentenced to seppuku!
The clan fell from grace!
All of that was tolerable.
The problem came after that!
The nightmare began for the Kurozumi Clan!
The surviving family members were hunted
by unknown "heroes of justice"!
Punched!
Thrown into the river!
And killed!
I couldn't sleep
because I was terrified of those idiots!
Even after the one who committed the crime
was long dead!
Kurozumi! Pay for your crime!
You're from the Daimyo-slaying family!
Don't!
Forgive me!
It seems like even a child would be found guilty
if they were a Kurozumi!
That's why everyone in the Land of Wano...
...deserves my retribution!
Screw you!
W-What the...
What are you gonna do with them?!
It's what you fools asked for!
Orochi! What are you gonna do with them?!
In the other room, there
was a pile of weapons...
...and hundreds of people
who had been kidnapped!
Once they were handed over...
their human lives were over!
They were all...
...tributes for Kaido!
Those people...
...will be sold or toyed with...
...or killed!
Help...!
You're the cause of all of this!
Kaido!
I'm taking the Land of Wano back!
Blast Breath!
Kozuki Oden!
You're the biggest fool in the Land of Wano!
I'm a pirate!
Stop!
This is my castle!
I won't forgive you!
Orochi! Kaido!
Oden-sama got angry!
But that was when Orochi made an offer!
Do you wanna stop the kidnappings, Oden?!
Even if you got in a war against us,
you'd lose so much!
Now, what are you gonna do?!
Help...
I wanna see my family...
Mother!
Orochi!
Just choose already!
A war?
Or the citizens' lives?
We won't stay in this country forever!
Once you've fulfilled your
end of the bargain...
we'll leave here in five years!
You really mean it?!
It's up to you!
You're the silliest lord in the world!
He was just a man seeking vengeance
and had no interest in the
country from the start!
So it's obvious
that the country would be devastated even if we won.
That's why Oden-sama accepted the offer...
If he dances naked to express his apology
to the Kurozumi Clan
every week at the appointed time,
even though he would lose everything,
he could save 100 lives with each dance!
What?!
They said when the ship they
were building was complete,
they'd leave the country,
and he believed their words!
At the same time, he traveled to each region
every week to make sure nothing went wrong!
Oden-sama had...
Oden-sama had always been
protecting this country!
Now, who's the silly lord?!
Say it!
Opening up the Land of Wano!
Believing that the sun will rise,
Kozuki Oden burns with his fighting spirit!
While the irritated Orochi
makes the whole capital scream,
will Oden be able to perform a miracle?!
This legendary hour holds the fate of the future!
How will it end?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Oden Wouldn't Be Oden If It Wasn't Boiled!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!