Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
It'll be a big moment for you!
I'll watch it to the end!
I'll give you an hour!
Damn you!
Who did you call a silly lord?!
Captain, that's Shinobu!
Oden-sama had always been
protecting this country!
Now, who's the silly lord?!
Say it!
"Oden Wouldn't Be Oden If It Wasn't Boiled!"
We were being protected by Oden-sama?!
Even if you tell us now...
It's too hard to swallow!
It's not too late!
You must know the truth about Oden-sama!
Enough, Shinobu!
Fukurokuju!
Truth only creates turmoil!
Let go of me!
"The silly lord who rebelled against the Shogun dies."
That's what people will think,
and the execution will be over soon!
That's what this execution is all about.
How could you interfere?
You knew the consequences, right?!
I'm already sharing the same fate with them!
I'm Oden-sama's retainer!
You guys became Orochi's dogs,
so I'm not gonna obey you!
If anything happens to Oden-sama and the others,
I'll die with them!
No! We'll all survive
and take you guys down!
You're dreaming!
S-Shogun Orochi!
Please stop this execution!
I'm begging you!
--Please!
--I'm begging you!
Th-They need treatment now!
Orochi!
Damn scum!
Not only the Shogun's family,
but all the common people
persecuted the Kurozumi Clan.
The people instantly realized how dreadful
its vengeful descendant Orochi could be.
Meanwhile,
the reason behind Oden's strange behavior
of dancing naked for five years,
spread among the people in no time.
What?!
Then, the person who saved us that day was...
Yet we mocked him so much!
Even though he was enduring
more than anyone else!
Damn! We're a bunch of fools!
Everyone rushed to Oden.
They finally realized that
the protracted execution they were witnessing...
...involving this man who was facing death
in front of their eyes...
...was the only hope for the Land of Wano!
Oden-sama, you must survive!
I'm sorry for cursing you
without knowing anything!
Thank you for protecting us!
It's too late!
They're such brown-nosers!
Oden-sama, never mind...
Thanks! I'll try my best!
So straightforward!
However, Orochi, of course,
wouldn't leave the people's excitement be,
and before they knew it, they were surrounded by
Kaido and Orochi's armed subordinates.
The temperature of the oil surpassed
700 degrees Celsius and kept rising.
I won't concede!
Arrows carried messages
to the castle in each region to publicize the incident.
KURI   KIBI   FLOWER   RINGO
UDON   HAKUMAI
HAKUMAI, LAND OF WANO
The Land of Wano's letter-arrows
can travel a great distance...
Oden-sama!
Guys!
Oden-sama, what is it?!
If I manage to survive this boiling...
I...
...want to open up this country!
They're talking about something...
You were talking about opening up before...
You said that the isolation is deeply tied to Kozuki...
What did you find at sea
where you traveled with Roger and the others?!
Those responsible for isolating this country
from the rest of the world a long time ago...
...were the Kozuki Clan!
To protect the Land of Wano from an enormous force!
The Land of Wano...
I mean, the whole world...
...awaits a certain figure!
When that figure shows up after 800 years,
this country must be welcoming
and cooperative!
Let me be clear!
Today, they'll...
...definitely kill me!
No!
But if you can really survive this boiling...!
One third of the time has already passed!
Kikunojo!
Let's hear what Oden-sama has to say!
On behalf of me...
Open up the Land of Wano!
We can do it with you...
Your dream is our dream!
Well said!
Thirty minutes to go!
This is like hell
where even the heat is lethal.
The boiling oil is cooking Oden.
I-I'm sorry!
Why hasn't he died yet?
Why's he still alive?!
Gah! Raise the temperature!
Let the oil boil more!
Ten minutes to go!
Heat can't kill him?!
We'll set out on a great adventure
beyond your wildest imagination!
My little brother!
Five minutes to go!
One minute to go!
Ten seconds!
Eight! Seven! Six! Five! Four!
Three seconds!
One second!
He did it!
It's a miracle!
He survived the death penalty!
Oden-sama has...
...withstood the boiling!
He did it!
--He really did it!
--Remarkable!
It's Oden-sama's victory!
Oden-sama!
Oden-sama's name has been cleared, too!
And now, the whole country is on our side again!
Get ready for it, Kaido!
Don't tease him, stupid cat!
What?! He surely won!
Shut up! Don't speak so idly!
What's going on?!
You promised to set all of us free
if we survived for an hour!
I conceived of the idea of changing his sentence
from boiling to shooting a minute ago!
And we'll execute not only Oden...
...but also all his family members!
What a childish excuse!
That's not what you said!
Oden-sama did...
Those of you who have a problem,
show yourself!
We'll pump lead into you!
I'm counting on you guys!
Open up the Land of Wano!
Run! To Kuri!
Shinobu!
Don't look back!
Kozuki Oden!
That was an interesting conversation.
Oden-sama!
Kill them all!
Go after them!
Eliminate the name Kozuki!
I know your body is already "dead" anyway...
This is the least I could do for you...
I'll shoot you!
Kozuki's era will end here!
You're all gonna die!
Don't underestimate my samurai retainers!
Oden-sama!
Stop eating, you brats!
I said stop!
Don't give him anymore!
Whoa! I give up! I give up! I give up!
I thought you were a dead person!
Oden-sama!
You fools who grew up pampered in the capital...
...can't understand
what it feels like to live in hell!
Is that what you wanna say?!
Shame on you, you pricks!
How could you bully those little ones?!
I'm hungry...
That's because you lend people money!
Oh, yeah!
Guys, go steal food!
A Daimyo shouldn't say that!
Finish him off already!
Even if you act miserably now,
people will talk about how heroically you died
for generations...
I don't mind...
...being forgotten!
But...
...my spirit will live on!
What?!
Sorry about the old bag!
I killed her...
You did?
That's so upright of you...
Build your strength while you can!
I'm happy...
...if people talk about me over a drink...
I'M HAPPY IF PEOPLE TALK ABOUT ME OVER A DRINK
My samurai retainers!
Toki!
Momonosuke!
Hiyori!
I'm off!
Oden wouldn't be oden...
ODEN WOULDN'T BE ODEN
...if it wasn't boiled!
IF IT WASN'T BOILED
Raided by Kaido, Oden Castle is set alight!
After repeated attacks,
the Kozuki Clan has nowhere left to run.
Even cornered, Toki still struggles to save
Oden's dream and the country's future!
Believing the sun will rise, she makes a fervent wish
and entrusts the fate of the Land of Wano to others.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Castle on Fire! The Fate of the Kozuki Clan!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!