mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Kanjuro was the enemy's spy.
Momonosuke was kidnapped
and Kin'emon and the others' plan seemed to have failed,
but Napping Kyoshiro came along.
My Kyoshiro Family is 200 strong
and we would like to help you with your raid!
Are you Denjiro?!
Adding the 1,200 of us,
it's 5,400 in total!
Now let's go, everyone!
Oh, no! Nothing has changed!
Now, to Onigashima!
Let's avenge Oden-sama's death together!
"A Tearful Promise!
The Kidnapped Momonosuke!"
--Kawamatsu!
--Momonosuke-sama!
Momonosuke-sama!
Somebody!
I am scared! Let me down!
--Wait!
--Momonosuke-sama!
Kanjuro of the Akazaya betrayed us!
--Why?!
Help!
Momonosuke-sama!
Are you okay, Shinobu?
Forget about me, save Momonosuke-sama!
Damn you, Kanjuro!
Kanjuro was a spy, right, Robin-chan?
I think so. We must help Momo-chan!
What?!
Luffy!
Kanjuro was the enemy's spy!
He's taking Momo away!
What?! Are you sure?!
Does that mean he's been fooling us?!
That bastard!
He's flying into the clouds!
I'll shoot him down!
Special Attack!
Green Star Platanus Shuriken!
I'm sorry.
Help!
I don't have time for you fools...
What's this cloud?!
No, Sanji-dono! Get back!
I have a bad feeling about this!
He will use another technique
we have never seen...
Ink Clouds!
Let the Ink Arrows rain down!
Ukiyo Portrait: Evening Shower!
Turn the rudder! Get away from the cloud!
Ouch!
--Chopper, this way!
--Yeah!
What are you doing to my Sunny?!
No!
Nami-san!
The only person who is allowed to shoot an arrow through
Nami-san
and Robin-chan's hearts...
...is me!
Sanji!
Stop already, Kanjuro!
They are all going to die!
That's right...
They're all gonna die...
At last!
I'm counting on you guys!
Open up the Land of Wano!
Your father Oden,
and your mother Toki held out false hope,
and merely let those fools
escape death for 20 years...
Anyway, it's funny that the person
who leads
those tough samurai warriors
seeking revenge...
...is this empty-headed, timid kid
who's scared of heights.
That's so hilarious!
I know...
I am not Kozuki Oden...
I know that better than anyone!
What should I do?! I can't do anything...
Somebody, help...
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
Toki!
Momonosuke!
Hiyori!
I missed you all, too!
Oden wouldn't be oden...
You say it!
I thought you were an important person!
You're a leader of these great men,
aren't you?!
Are you gonna just cry?!
We all share one wish!
Take back the Land of Wano!
I am the heir to the Daimyo
of the Land of the Wano...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
Now is the time to rise up!
E...
What am I trying to say?!
If I say something like that,
no one is going to help me!
But...
Everyone!
Can you hear me?!
Momonosuke-sama!
All of you, stop worrying about me!
That is exactly what they want!
I can escape on my own!
So I want you to bring down Kaido and Orochi,
and save the Land of Wano!
How touching and noble those words are!
Momonosuke-sama!
I can't believe Momo stood up like a man!
That's right, Momo!
You...
...are just a chicken-hearted stupid brat,
but you always boss people around,
you squirt with a funny topknot!
How could he speak so rudely
to Momonosuke-sama?!
Who is that bastard?! Chop him up!
Survive however you can!
I'm gonna come rescue you!
Because you're my friend!
All right...
Let's go to Onigashima!
Yeah!
Luffy!
One of the enemy ships is fleeing!
Let it go!
We're gonna head that direction anyway,
so we can sink it later!
Oh?! I thought there was one more ship.
Yeah, I already sank it.
Let's get going!
Momo's waiting for us!
Kin-sama, I'm sorry!
I was supposed to save him!
I am glad that you are okay.
I do not think
they will kill Momonosuke-sama yet.
I'm so sorry!
Do not be.
Denjiro, I'm happy to see you again!
I can't believe that infamous Kyoshiro was you,
Denjiro-san!
By the way, Denjiro!
What...
...happened to your face?!
Oh this?
Oden-sama! Toki-sama!
It's a long story.
I'm glad to see you all!
Everyone! Are you all right?!
There are some injuries
and wrecked ships!
We're okay! No problem!
Let's go to the island now!
We don't wanna die at sea!
Hey!
This is not a camp for samurai!
Remove your boat, too!
Thank you for taking us in!
I'm not taking you in! Get off!
Guys!
Don't fall behind the Straw Hats!
Yeah!
What?! Where did it come from?!
It's from the ship that fled!
--A long-range cannon?!
--They were trying to keep a good distance!
How can they hit us from that far?!
The weapons from the Land of Wano
are well-made!
Thanks to the weapon factories
in the Land of Wano,
we Animal Kingdom Pirates have
a variety of weapons!
Come flying towards us
like you did before!
Back the ship up! We're too close!
Damn! I thought they escaped too easily...
Full speed ahead!
We've got to move closer!
I don't care how many samurai ships
will sink!
Oh, no! If they keep this distance...
we'll all sink!
It's over now!
They can't do anything!
Shoot! Shoot!
Fish-Man Karate!
Spear Wave!
--There's a hole in the ship!
--Help!
I'm gonna fall!
Fish-Man Karate!
Spear Wave: Murasame!
The long-range cannon...!
Something's happening.
Maybe the ghost of a drowned baby...
...is killing them...
That sounds even more peaceful than this!
What's going on?!
Is anyone there?
Everyone!
Please listen!
I was born...
...in the Fish-Man District,
the Kingdom of Ryugu, the country in the deep sea...
I gave my seniors around the world
so much trouble,
but now, I am going to exchange a cup of sake with
Boss Straw Hat-san...
I am merely a fledgling!
People call me...
..."First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
"FIRST SON OF THE SEA" JIMBEI
You've got to be kidding.
He's gonna join the Straw Hats?!
"FIRST SON OF THE SEA" JIMBEI
HELMSMAN OF THE STRAW HAT PIRATES
BOUNTY: 438 MILLION BERRIES
Please remember my face,
and I request your continued support!
--Jimbei!
--Jimbei-san!
Boss!
Jimbei!
Thank you for indulging me!
Luffy! I came back alive as I promised you!
I'm glad I made it in time for the battle!
Luffy and the others are
excited to see Jimbei.
Now, to Onigashima, a stronghold
that is difficult to infiltrate.
As the samurai formulate a new plan,
guards of a giant torii gate get in their way.
Having a new member and increased manpower,
the Straw Hats fight these enemies
with their formidable teamwork!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A New Member!  'First Son of the Sea' Jimbei!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!