Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
I'm gonna come rescue you!
Because you're my friend!
After letting their enemy's spy Kanjuro
kidnap Momonosuke,
Luffy and the others were facing another crisis
when that long-awaited man finally returned!
Please listen!
I was born...
...in the Fish-Man District,
the Kingdom of Ryugu, the country in the deep sea...
I gave my seniors around the world
so much trouble,
but now, I am going to exchange a cup of sake with
Boss Straw Hat-san...
I am merely a fledgling!
People call me...
..."First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
"FIRST SON OF THE SEA" JIMBEI
HELMSMAN OF THE STRAW HAT PIRATES
BOUNTY: 438 MILLION BERRIES
Please remember my face,
and I request your continued support!
"A New Member!
'First Son of the Sea' Jimbei!"
You're finally here!
Jimbei!
Everyone! I'm a crewmember of the Sunny
from today.
I was worried about you!
I missed you!
Boss!
I'm happy to see you all again, too!
A former Warlord of the Sea, Jimbei,
is our member now!
How reassuring!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Nami-san, you don't need to hug him so hard...
You really made me worried!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I had to take care of
some injured members of the Sun Pirates,
and the farewell party for me was blast,
so I couldn't leave it.
I'm sorry.
But it's really nice to see you again!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Let me bring up...
...the rear!
I'll pull it off and come back alive!
Don't forget, Jimbei!
I'm your captain now!
I'll be waiting for you at the Land of Wano!
Come at any cost!
Thank you!
Jimbei!
Don't die no matter what!
Have mercy on me!
Take me with you!
I can help you for sure!
Hand Dragon's son over to me!
I cannot do that!
Because I've already made up my mind...
...to save his life even if it means death!
I know that it's painful now, Luffy,
but you have to bottle up those feelings!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have...
I still have my friends!
Hey, Jimbei.
Join...
...my crew!
Now, I'm leaving the Big Mom Pirates!
Thank you for all your troubles!
Jimbei, if I don't escape death...
I'm sorry but
could you look after my brother?
I'm sorry to contradict you, Ace-san,
but you can't overrate me.
I'm not as good-natured as you think.
Even if he's your brother,
we're in the pirates' world.
I only help or protect
the ones who I have a high regard for!
--I look to you for your continued support!
--Yeah!
Everyone, once again,
I'm looking forward to traveling with you!
Jimbei's steering skills are really amazing!
He surfed a wave with the Sunny!
I see...
Someone who can tap into the dream ship's potential
finally appeared...
Every time I take this helm, I think...
...this is a great ship!
Thanks.
Okay.
Let's make a toast!
All right!
To celebrate Jimbei's coming aboard,
let's make a toast!
Yeah!
Whoa, wait!
We don't have any booze on this ship now!
No...
I smell booze...
From where?!
From that way!
Onigashima is in that direction...
There's something in front of it...
What's that?
Hey! Luffy-dono!
I want to discuss what we will do
after we reach Onigashima!
Come here immediately, Luffy-dono!
You liar! I only smell the seawater!
I'm not lying!
I can smell food, too!
Luffy-dono!
Stop, Kin.
There's no point in giving them a plan.
Besides, this is my ship. If you're having a strategy meeting,
take it to someone else's ship.
I need to be briefed on your strategy!
FULL-POWER SHISHILIAN
CAPTAIN OF THE DOGSTORM MUSKETEERS
Full-Power Shishilian-dono!
Duke Dogstorm-sama will fight as Kozuki Oden's retainer
in this battle!
So I'll lead the Minks!
Yeah, thanks!
Allow me...
...to take charge of
all the samurai from the Land of Wano!
HYOGORO THE FLOWER
FORMER GREAT UNDERGROUND BOSS OF
THE LAND OF WANO
Boss Hyogoro!
I am sorry for being a stranger
for as long as 20 years.
I am glad to see you looking well.
Kin'emon... No, all of you Akazaya members...
I'm glad that you returned to the Land of Wano
after jumping 20 years.
On top of that, you brought
the straw hat man who is extremely strong.
We did it all to take down Kaido and Orochi
and open the borders of the Land of Wano!
Yeah!
All right. Now, should we quickly discuss
what we'll do after we reach Onigashima?
Okay. Come this way.
Yeah, yeah, sit where you can see the map
in a circle, yes, in a circle.
Are you okay?
Mm-hm! Can you see?
You sit here!
Ah, looks like everyone is here.
All right, let's begin!
Um, first of all...
I told him that this ship
isn't to be used as their camp.
All right!
I am going to explain
the Onigashima raid plan!
As shown on this map, Onigashima is an island...
ONIGASHIMA
...that has mountains along its perimeter.
Even if you try to approach by boat,
the sheer cliffs will bar your way,
so it's impossible!
There is only one way to enter the island!
That is by passing through the front gate!
The skull of the island is embedded in a mountain,
and what's more, there is a castle inside.
But by obtaining the blueprints of the mansion,
we found out that there is a back entrance
on the other side of the island!
BACK ENTRANCE
So we are going to avoid the front gate
which will be heavily guarded,
separate into two groups,
take the mountain paths on the left and right,
BACK ENTRANCE
and sneak into the castle from the back entrance.
We will make a surprise attack on Kaido
who will be drunk after the banquet,
and finish it up quickly!
How impressive...
That's my Kin-san...
It is a good idea, isn't it?
Now, what is your real plan?
What?!
I know that poorly-thought-out plan...
...is what you came up with to deceive Kanjuro...
What?
Now, what's your real plan?
What?!
Here we go, the over-evaluation.
But I know that Kin'emon has...
...no real plan!
Um...
My real plan is...
First,
if the enemies notice our raid,
they'll be most focused on the Akazaya samurai!
In addition, I,
Straw Hat-ya, and Eustass-ya...
We three captains.
Mm-hm! That is true!
No matter what kind of plan you make,
we know there are two idiots
who'll try to charge in through the front door!
IDIOTS
Those idiots will be good decoys for us.
And they're stronger than ordinary decoys.
In order to stop those idiots,
tons of Kaido's underlings will be sent to the front.
I see! Most of Kaido's underlings
will go to the front,
and the mountain paths on both sides
will be lightly guarded!
So, as planned,
we'll all proceed along the mountain paths on both sides.
But...
...those who proceed along the paths are decoys, too!
What?!
Of course, we're prepared to sacrifice ourselves
for a fight...
...to send Kin'emon and the others off
to a decisive battle...
Then, how will the Akazaya members proceed?!
On water is the only option.
But the whirling waves will block our approach!
No problem. It's gonna be fine.
By going underwater in this Polar Tang,
and circling the island,
we can avoid the whirling waves along the way.
And...
...my ability will allow me to
send you all into the island.
Mm-hm! Sounds great!
But Law-dono,
I still have to lead the others.
You're right.
Then, I'll take the mountain path, too,
so that we can lead the groups on each side!
Okay?!
Raizo!
Kawamatsu!
Dogstorm!
Kikunojo!
Ashura!
Got it.
We'll save our energy,
and fight Kaido with all our might!
All right!
As originally planned, let's use that strategy!
That's my Kin-san!
It's a well-laid plan!
Stare...
Would you like to say something, Raizo-kun?
Not particularly.
Let's see...
DEITY
Under the torii gate...
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
What the hell?
That's a fortress!
Looks like the Animal Kingdom Pirates
have quite nice booze...
Hey, Luffy!
Do you really wanna charge?!
That's a fortress!
Even so, I'll destroy whatever's in our way!
I'll have both booze and Kaido's head!
Th-That's an enemy ship!
It's gonna get bumpy!
Hold on!
Let's use the anchor
to force our way ashore there!
Do it!
All right! Let's do it in one go!
I've never seen a ship moving like this!
My bones are sliding!
Th-The ship moved sideways!
All this jerking around means I can't aim!
Your skills are impressive,
but next time, please steer gently.
I'm sorry!
Captain Luffy! Destroy their gun battery first!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
Don't let them approach! Shoot, shoot!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
...Pistol!
GUM-GUM PISTOL
Shoot, shoot!
Two-Sword Style...
Hawk Wave!
TWO-SWORD STYLE HAWK WAVE
I'm surrounded.
Get him!
Soul Solid!
Swallow...
...Banderole!
SOUL SOLID SWALLOW BANDEROLE
Mil Fleurs, Gigantesco Mano!
Stomp!
MIL FLEURS, GIGANTESCO MANO STOMP
Robin-chan...
You're beautiful even when you fight...
Hey, you! Why are you so relaxed?!
Flanchet!
FLANCHET
Franky Boxing!
Super!
FRANKY BOXING
Seems like none of them need our help.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
For the annual Golden Festival,
fearsome warriors gather at Onigashima!
Enjoying the debauched banquet,
Orochi is on cloud nine!
As Luffy and the others approach and Kaido plots a new plan,
extremely dangerous and formidable figures show up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kaido's Trump Card! The Tobi Roppo Appear!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!