Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Hey...
The Straw Hats' ship is missing.
What?!
No way! Luffy-dono!
Gum-Gum...
Is that...
Gee, those fools...
They always do whatever suits them!
Red...
...Hawk!
The guards at the torii gate...
...have been wiped out!
Luffy and the others took
the lead in the raid
by attacking the torii gate
in front of Onigashima,
and they conquered it.
Thank you, Luffy-dono!
--What's that?
--You quickly got past the first barrier...
I appreciate it!
Kozuki's samurai!
You loyal warriors!
Follow us!
All ships, to Onigashima!
Charge!
On the night of the Fire Festival,
the samurai warriors' raid accelerates!
"The Samurai Warriors' Earnestness!
The Straw Hats Land at Onigashima!"
Everyone!
When we kick Kaido's ass,
we'll have a big banquet!
Yeah!
All right! Let's do it!
Let's do it!
Get out of my way, you weaklings!
Jaggy!
I won't let anyone take Kaido's head!
Right, Killer?
Yeah, that's right...
Is that it?! Don't you have
anything else to say?!
No, I don't.
Is that it?!
Kaido, pretty up your face and wait for me!
I'll chop your head off
and display it on the bow of my ship!
He's right!
How could you turn Killer-san into a cheerful character?!
We're gonna become a cheerful
pirate group, then!
Stop it!
Straw Hat! See you later!
Hey, wait, Jaggy! That bastard!
They're in good spirits!
Jimbei! You know what to do!
Keep up with Jaggy's ship!
Sounds fun!
All right! Leave it to me!
I'll catch up to that punk's ship in no time!
About ship!
Wow! Cool!
That's it, Jimbei!
After them!
I'm gonna bring you down!
Wait for me, Kaido!
Raizo!
Explain our plan to everyone again!
Okay!
Here is the plan that Kin'emon created.
While Luffy-dono lures the enemies to the front,
Kin'emon and Denjiro will split up...
...and lead everyone else
along the side mountain paths
to the back entrance of the castle.
Mm-hm! That is exactly right!
To avoid the whirling waves,
we will try to reach the back entrance with this ship.
--Okay, just as we planned...
--See you at the back entrance!
Mm-hm!
Okay, I got it.
Set sail!
Nin, nin!
Law-dono! I am counting on you!
Let's go!
Okay, guys... Prepare to submerge!
Prepare to submerge! Aye-aye, Captain!
Aye-aye, sir!
The Polar Tang, all systems are clear!
Airtight seal confirmed!
Open the vents!
Roger!
Water intake is good!
Guys, maintain your focus
from here on out!
Submerge!
Aye-aye, sir!
Adjust trim, 30 degrees!
Sustain a depth of 100 meters!
Captain! What is our course?!
Full speed ahead to the back
entrance of Onigashima!
Aye-aye, sir!
Onigashima! Onigashima!
Let's take down Kaido! Hunt the ogre!
Hey! Guys!
We're gonna go ahead!
Luffy-dono!
Everyone!
Stay sharp!
Don't let your guard down!
There could be an ambush any minute!
The fate of the Land of Wano
will be determined by this battle!
Kin-san, I'm glad
that I can fight alongside you again!
Haven't you lost your touch, Denjiro?
Why bother surviving the last two decades
if not to improve my skills!
You must have been through a lot!
Let's end this!
Yeah!
There it is...
I can finally avenge myself!
So this is Onigashima!
Oh, it's enormous!
I've never seen it before.
So this is Kaido's stronghold!
Kin-san, look.
Yeah... They are just enjoying a banquet...
They are not on the lookout for
an enemy attack at all.
I guess they have not received
Kanjuro's report yet...
Or maybe they have received it,
but it does not worry them...
Even so, we are lucky...
We can even launch a surprise attack now!
Kaido's castle is deep in the island, right?
Yeah, that's what it looks like!
It's farther from here than we expected.
If they haven't noticed,
we must attack swiftly...
We must buy time for Kin'emon and the others
to reach the back entrance, too...
What should we do?
Hm? What's that?
Is that a guard?!
Oh, no! He's turning this way!
What are those?
Ships?
Huh? You've got to be kidding!
I haven't heard anything about this!
Who are they? Invaders?
Invaders?
Yeah, they've got to be invaders!
Why don't you guys take a nap?!
Special Attack Green Star!
Sleepgrass!
Oh? I thought I saw some people there...
Looks like they're sleeping! Problem solved!
Do you think we can get ashore?
Hold on. I'm checking now.
The enemies will notice us! Hurry up!
Shut up! Just wait!
All enemy guards have been silenced!
There's no one else around!
I'm impressed with Straw Hat-san and the others!
They're fast!
Finally!
Yeah!
Why don't you guys relax?!
Boss Hyogoro!
Gee...
If you're already this nervous now,
you'll be useless when it matters most.
You guys, too!
Don't you dare slow the Akazaya down!
Yes, sir!
In any case, I can't believe
we made it this far!
Letting our main force, the Akazaya members,
charge in from the back entrance, huh?
I see... I've got a rough
understanding of the plan,
but if we moor this many
ships out in the open,
our enemies will definitely be provoked!
Everyone!
Get ready to disembark!
What's going on?
Don't tell me they...
Break them!
What?!
What?! What?! What's all this about?!
What are they doing?!
What decisiveness!
What determination!
All right! Everyone!
Go ashore quickly but quietly!
Listen, fellow warriors!
We will split up into two groups
and take the mountain paths to the back entrance!
Follow me or Denjiro!
Hey, hey, hey!
We all worked so hard
to repair those ships!
You hid the ships by sinking them?!
But you can't sail them anymore!
How are you guys gonna get back?!
You can't escape if you do this!
Luffy-dono, you do not need to worry.
We will let them all sink!
Because we do not need return ships!
Well then, we must go now, so excuse us!
Guys, keep a low profile!
What an incredible display.
We saw how earnest
those samurai warriors really are.
There is no hesitation in them,
only determination...
Win or die...
There is no arrogance
in taking on an Emperor of the Sea!
What if they wanna escape?!
They'll just be swallowed by the sea...
Then...
We have to sink the Sunny, too?!
No way, you fools!
A small number of ships can be hid!
Make your way ashore, too, guys!
All right! I'll do it!
What?! No way!
Oh, no! This is no good!
What is it, Carrot-chan? What's no good?
Look!
How didn't we notice...
There are so many enemies at the shore!
Why's this happening?!
W-What's going on?!
What happened to the samurai?!
Are they...
...Gifters, the power-users
who ate the artificial Devil Fruits?
We've already been found by the enemies?
--No, they're not.
--What?
Look at the other end of the bridge!
Hey! What's this?!
That's what the enemies wear.
Hey! Jaggy!
That looks perfect on you!
It makes you look really strong!
Sh-Shut up!
Do you like it?
That's one of my special techniques!
Garb-Garb "Kin's Clothing Company"!
It seems like...
....you people sure are some mighty pirates.
You can invade this island as you like,
but they are overflowing with talent!
Their forces are
more than five times larger than ours.
So I advise you
to take advantage of those disguises!
This is good.
We just wanna take down Kaido,
we don't have time for any other small fries...
Let's go!
Yeah.
Luffy-dono!
Why don't you guys pass through it, too?!
Yeah! That looks like fun!
I'm gonna do it, too!
Transform!
Hup!
Cool!
Ta-dah!
Chobro! You look amazing!
I'm gonna do it, too!
Nami-san! You're even more tantalizing!
Now let me try it!
How do I look?
So ordinary.
Don't you care enough to even make fun of me?
Robin-chan, you're so cool and beautiful!
We're gonna do it, too!
Yay!
Super!
Oh! You guys all look great!
Kin'emon! That's quite a technique!
Kin's Clothing Company!
I am grateful for your compliment.
Now, since it is only my technique,
once you take them off or tear them,
your clothes will turn back to your original kimono!
My fellow warriors!
This is Onigashima, Kaido's stronghold!
Our enemies are way stronger than us!
But our spirits are high enough!
However,
avoid unnecessary battles whenever possible,
and try to reach the castle
for the final battle!
Good luck!
Kin'emon and his allies charge forth from land and water
to the castle where Kaido is.
The Kidnapped Momonosuke
is lost in underground passages.
Luffy tries to infiltrate,
but incites trouble in front of the Gifters at their banquet
and creates turmoil in Onigashima.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Goes Out of Control?!
Sneaking into Kaido's Banquet!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!