mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Kin'emon's group is invading Onigashima
to take down Kaido and get rid of Orochi.
The Akazaya samurai take the pirate Law's submarine
towards the back of the island.
All right! We should get going, too!
Yeah!
I'm the one who'll take Kaido's head!
And me!
Those fools!
Okay!
I'm gonna go stop them!
Wait, Luffy!
He'll only make things worse.
I'm gonna go stop him!
But...
Hey, Luffy!
Wait!
Jaggy!
Where are you?!
"Thinking of Otama!
Luffy's Furious Strike!"
Where did he go?
Luffy...
Oh, well...
I guess I'll find him once I reach Kaido.
Hey, bro! Are you drinking?
Where the hell are you going?!
Hey, where's Kaido?
Why are you asking me that?
Don't tell me you're gonna drink with him!
Kaido-san is at the back of the Performance Hall
just up there,
but he'd never drink with us...
Hey!
I brought them.
Come in!
Kaido-sama-arinsu! It's been a while-rinsu!
What kind of language is that?
Are you drinking?
There's no point in drinking with small fries.
I wanna drink with you, Kaido-san!
Yeah, all right.
Let's go to the hall later.
No standing on ceremony today.
Later?
Why can't we go now?
I was gonna introduce you guys to Linlin first...
Linlin?
Introduce us to Big Mom?
Yeah...
This rouge and lipstick...
They're good colors.
I like them.
Thank you for waiting!
Here is your red-bean soup.
Red-bean soup!
I've been waiting for it!
I heard she's changing now. Let's see her later.
Later?
In any case, a small incident occurred,
so I had to keep you guys waiting.
You call this planning?!
Hey, stop!
Well, that's true, but I didn't summon you guys
in the first place.
What?!
Then who summoned us?
I did.
I summoned them, Kaido-san.
King... So it was you who needed us?!
How could you trick us?!
I know some of you wouldn't come
if you knew it was me.
Who's-Who! Sasaki!
You're right.
You two who were once captains
of your own pirate groups...
...are aiming to take over our positions
as the Lead Performers.
We're promoted based on merit in this group.
Of course, we're aiming for that!
Know your place.
Whoa, stop!
Why are you fighting on this delightful banquet day?
King! Why did you summon them?
Because I heard about your small incident
before anyone else.
Don't you need them?
I do, indeed...
Bao Huang!
Yes!
WIND
BAO HUANG - A HEADLINER, ANIMAL KINDOM PIRATES
FLYING SQUIRREL SMILE FRUIT
What's my schedule today?
Later at the Golden Festival stage
where Queen-sama is now performing...
the three Lead Performers and Fukurokuju-sama will...
...make a toast!
Following that, Orochi-sama and Kaido-sama will...
...give speeches!
Then, when the Big Mom Pirates' ship arrives...
Kaido-sama and Big Mom-sama
will announce the world's strongest...
...pirate alliance!
After that, Kaido-sama will make...
...an important announcement!
That's it.
An important announcement?!
It's so not like you to keep us hanging.
That's so annoying-arinsu!
Yeah, I know. But if I share it now
it'll cause confusion.
Now, here is what I want you guys to do.
My foolish son Yamato disappeared today,
and I want you to bring him to me!
Whoa... That's quite a task.
That means your announcement
has to do with Young Master Yamato?
That's right.
I see.
What a pain! It's just a family matter!
Hey!
And... what if we bring him home safely?
I'll give you the right to challenge
the Lead Performer of your choice.
How's that?
Seriously? I'll do it!
I'm in, too!
You don't mind, do you?
No, not at all!
Hey! You're all covered in red-bean soup!
You don't eat red-bean soup!
You cover yourself in it!
Bring the soup!
We'll pour it on each other!
Spill it all!
Tama...
I'm all covered in red-bean soup. It stinks...
More! More!
Keep it coming! Here!
Let us through.
We wanna see Kaido.
Get out of our way.
I'm sure Kaido-san will eventually appear
on the stage right there.
Wait until then.
Let's have a drink and
watch him when he comes.
Have a drink.
What are you...?!
Damn you!
Shut your mouth.
Listen!
Kaido-san took good care of me...
So I must see him in person
and thank him properly.
Do you know what I mean?
Okay.
Th-That's very nice...
Y-Yeah...
Say hi to him for me.
This disguise is good.
We can avoid unnecessary fights.
Thanks to that,
we can get to Kaido unharmed.
We can finally take his head...
Yeah...
Yay!
I think I've been here before... or not...
What? You came back again?
Did you guys move?!
Huh? We've been here all along.
No way.
I've walked a lot,
so I must be getting closer to where Kaido is.
--You got drunk and lost your way?
--You're a grown man embarrassing yourself.
Well, don't be so mad and just drink.
You can eat as much as you like.
It's delicious!
The booze and food here are surely good,
but your faces...
...sour it all!
What did you say?!
All right! Do you wanna fight?!
What are you looking at?!
Say something!
--What are you doing?!
--Did you do this?!
Are you messing with us?!
I'm starving...
Mom! I'm hungry!
Just a while longer.
Don't push your luck!
I'm a little frustrated. I'll fight you!
Hey! The meat is covered in red-bean soup!
We've got tons of food. Just dump it!
Only the people of Okobore Town would eat it!
You're right!
Why?!
Why is there plenty of food
for fools like you guys?!
Do you have a problem?!
What is he doing?!
Does red-bean soup taste that good?!
Yeah, it's delicious.
There is nothing else that tastes this good.
--Then why don't you have more?
--Come on and get your fill...
Starting with your head!
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
What?
Is this your first time having it?!
Yes!
How come...
...Tama doesn't get to eat anything?!
It's just red-bean soup,
don't get so bent out of shape!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
--Run!
--Or you'll get dragged in!
That must be where Luffy is.
Captain, look!
Straw Hat! What is that fool doing?!
We're trying to pass through the banquet hall
while keeping a low profile in disguise...
Oh, well...
Kid?!
Let him be!
He's making quite a scene,
so it's easier for us to move.
I have to calm him down now
or I won't be able to face Kin'emon...
I'm counting on you, Enma!
What the?!
Gee...
You created a ruckus!
I walked straight down to where the mess was...
And it's already like this!
Why can't you sneak in quietly?!
Sneak in quietly? Look who's talking...
Does he know what he's talking about?!
Did you forget what the plan was?!
No, I remember!
But these fools...
They intentionally spilled red-bean soup!
Red-bean soup?!
This soup is so delicious!
In that case, I gotta cut them all up!
The Golden Festival site instantly turned into a battlefield!
Scratchmen Apoo stands in
the raging Luffy and Zoro's way!
The fearful tune!
As they struggle in a battle with no way out,
Kid arrives with his own grudge!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fighting Music! An Ability That Harms Luffy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!