Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Go to hell, Apoo!
Kid!
Punk...
...Gibson!
"His Dream Broken?!
The Trap That Lures Sanji!"
Oh, Jaggy!
That fool!
Apoo-san!
Hey! He's not one of us!
Whaaat?!
Don't tell me that's...!
That's Captain Kid!
How come even Kid is here?!
I thought he was locked up in Udon!
What's this all about, Babanuki?!
You were eager to form an alliance with us...
I should've noticed at that time!
That you were an informant for Kaido!
Kaido knew every move that we made...
because you were reporting to him, right?!
You're so naive!
What?!
Did you think our alliance was strong enough
to take down one of the Four Emperors?!
Get real!
To begin with, pirate alliances...
...seldom have a happy ending!
Scratch!
Slash!
SLASH
I thought you were dead...
Huh, Kid?
You scum!
Bop!
BOP
Captain!
Are you okay?
No need to worry!
Queen-san! They're running wild!
They're so full of energy,
it's too hard to catch them alive!
You can kill them.
Repel!
Those who wanna die, bring it on!
I'll kill you!
There he is! I knew it was Killer!
Kid! Let's get out of here!
Fighting them here won't get us anywhere!
You're right!
Hey, stop! Even if you kill them,
you can't be part of the Tobi Roppo!
Whoa-whoa, stop!
You're gonna hurt us!
Go away!
Somebody, stop him!
This doesn't look good...
Let's retreat for now!
Who is that guy?! Is he out of control?!
Is he a Giant?! But he looks way larger!
HACCHA
That's it, Haccha! Crush the Worst Generation!
I'll take Kid's head!
Jaggy! Let's make a dash for the castle!
Our aim now is to take Kaido's head!
We shouldn't waste our time here!
Straw Hat!
You guys!
Captain, go ahead!
We'll handle them!
Alright! We'll leave them to you guys!
Let's go, Jaggy!
Let's go, Zoro!
Yeah!
Gee...
I knew you'd cause a scene, Jaggy!
Look who's talking, Luffy!
You're in no place to talk either, Roronoa!
Listen, Jaggy!
We'll sneak in quietly from here!
Don't tell me what to do!
I don't remember allying with you fools!
What?!
Are you listening, Straw Hat?!
You're always...
Bye, guys! I'm gonna take Kaido's head!
Hey, wait!
--You can't do that!
--I'll go first!
No, I'll go first!
No, I will!
I won't let you!
The plan is all messed up.
They're out of control...
They're hopeless!
Yay!
No one can get away from my Fighting Music!
Get wiped out! Check it out!
Boom!
I guess he's the one who did it!
Damn!
It's him again!
From that far?!
Apoo! That bastard!
Don't lose focus! That's what he wants!
Here we go! One more! Check it out!
Hey! Cover your ears!
Check it out! Boom!
BOOM
Listen up, guys!
Apoo's attacks are only effective within earshot!
Once you hear it, you can't dodge it!
Watch out for his sudden attacks!
What?
What did you say?
Say it once more!
It's very important,
so I'm gonna repeat myself!
Yeah!
I've received word from them!
They said the ship was okay,
so they'll be here soon!
That's good!
But that's strange, Big Mom...
We haven't heard a word from Mogura Port...
If they saw any sign of a ship at the port,
they should've contacted us...
Port?
What is a port?
What?!
Meanwhile, the Eastern Forces led by Kin'emon are
heading towards the back entrance of the castle as planned.
PRESENT LOCATION
Hey, Kin'emon!
We came by tank!
Chopper-dono! You are here!
All right! Let's go!
My fellow warriors!
I would like to modify our plan now!
It seems like they have not heard about
our arrival yet.
Let's split into two again!
The first half will sneak in
from the side of the Skull Dome,
PRESENT LOCATION
and wait for the right moment
pretending to be the enemy.
Meanwhile the other half will sneak in
through the back entrance,
and we will attack Kaido and Orochi
from both sides!
I'm trembling with excitement!
I wonder if Momo'll be there.
Thus, the plan continues to progress smoothly
with a few alterations.
LAW
Meanwhile, Law and the others
are traveling underwater in the submarine...
SOUTHERN FORCES
And Denjiro and the others
are taking the path on the south side of the island.
In disguise, Jimbei and Robin are blending in with the enemies
aiming to infiltrate the castle.
So are Franky and Brook.
While the Animal Kingdom Pirates
are having fun at the banquet,
the samurai are making steady progress to the castle
where Orochi and Kaido are.
What are they doing?
Hey, you guys!
You all!
We've been summoned by Kaido-sama...
...and we're in a hurry! Let us through!
Go ahead!
--Thanks!
--Yay!
Would you like to have some fun with me
after my business with Kaido-sama?
If so, let me through!
What?!
No!
Ninpo: Ball-Crusher!
NINPO: BALL CRUSHER
Being a mature woman is a crime.
That technique was terrifying...
I've yet to experience anything like it...
but I might wanna explore new possibilities...
No, no!
I'm not ready for that!
Stop!
However, there was a miscalculation.
WOMAN TROUBLE
I see. The information on the blueprints
was already old.
It is no surprise that
the building has been expanded.
But it is too out-of-place
for more than 2,000 soldiers to cross that bridge!
WOMAN TROUBLE
WOMAN
Hey, Kin'emon...
Th... Th... Th...
There is a pleasure hall!
This is a pleasure hall...
One of the Tobi Roppo, Black Maria, owns it.
I have a feeling that
there are a bunch of lovely ladies!
Oh, Sanji!
Wait, Sanji-dono!
It's like he's being sucked in!
Forget about Sanji-kun!
That aside, Kin'emon.
We're gonna sneak in, too!
We'll team up to rescue Momonosuke-sama!
You're actually really worried about him,
aren't you?
Leave Momo-chan's rescue to us!
So Kin'emon and everyone else
can focus on the fight!
Nami-dono! Carrot-dono! Shinobu!
Thank you!
To be honest, it has been weighing on me.
I am counting on you!
Someone's come out of the pleasure hall!
That is...
Seems like he couldn't find any women...
After hearing the commotion
that Luffy and the others created,
almost all of Kaido and Orochi's subordinates
have left the pleasure hall...
All right!
No women in the pleasure hall means no men are there, either.
We can cross the bridge now!
Invaders! Catch them!
Take them down!
It's Killer!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Yo! Yo!
Why is it taking you so long to beat that weakling?
Did you guys know?
Killer ate a defective Smile,
and became a Pleasure!
Hey, Killer!
If you eat this,
I'll give you a chance to save your captain!
Now, what are you gonna do?
What's so funny?!
You bastards!
Don't laugh at my friend!
I'll send everyone who laughs at you to hell!
Okay.
Hey, Jaggy!
Don't cause any more trouble!
Like you're ones to talk!
So they broke out of the prison in Udon...
Should we catch them?
We can get credit for that...
Forget it! They're just a handful of rats.
Instead, find Yamato
and let me know where he is.
That'll be a greater feat.
Don't let Sasaki find him first!
Yes, sir!
Why are you struggling with those fools, yo?!
Just kill them already!
Anyway...
I can't believe what Queen said...
I happen to wanna get rid of someone...
...from the Tobi Roppo!
There is someone...
...I want to kill, too.
While the infiltration of Onigashima progresses, Big Mom's
children are tenaciously trying to enter the Land of Wano again.
One man stands in their way!
Wings of flame and sharp claws!
His name is Marco the Phoenix!
Here he comes!
On the next episode of One Piece! "Reinforcements Arrive!
The Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!