mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
After infiltrating Onigashima,
Luffy and the others are now steadily closing in on Kaido.
Kid who found Apoo...
Did you think our alliance was strong enough
to take down one of the Four Emperors?!
Get real!
To begin with, pirate alliances...
...seldom have a happy ending!
Scratch!
Slash!
I thought you were dead...
Huh, Kid?
You scum!
I'll take Kid's head!
Jaggy! Let's make a dash for the castle!
Th... Th... Th...
There is a pleasure hall!
I have a feeling that
there are a bunch of lovely ladies!
Oh, Sanji!
Wait, Sanji-dono!
It's like he's being sucked in!
That is...
Seems like he couldn't find any women...
"Reinforcements Arrive!
The Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates!"
Repel!
Jaggy, what are you doing?!
They know who we are now anyway!
Stick to the plan!
Shove it up your ass!
I'll just do it!
Hey, wait!
It must be tough to have a captain
who is so quick with his fists.
No, it's not.
Kid is great!
Well, my situation's not so different from yours.
Are you feeling like a hero saving us, Straw Hat?!
I didn't save you guys!
That's what someone who feels like a hero
would say!
Cut it! You're annoying me!
Why are you guys fighting?!
We don't need a falling-out now!
You should take down your enemies quietly!
--Should we listen to him?
--We'll do whatever we want.
We're not gonna obey anyone anymore!
No one was there...
I found a pleasure hall, heaven on earth,
but no one was there...
Is this a bad dream?
No women in the pleasure hall
means no men are there, either.
We can cross the bridge now!
Uh-huh!
Infiltration team, good luck!
Yeah!
Nice! That's the spirit guys!
The rest of you, follow me!
Yeah!
We'll go, too!
Brachio Tank 5 will bring up the rear!
Start moving!
Sanji! I don't know what your deal is,
but cheer up!
You must be careful.
There'll probably be tons of enemies in there.
Tons?!
That's right!
They must... They must be in there somewhere!
Somewhere!
Sanji?
Sorry for making you worry...
I'm not gonna give up on finding those women!
Sniper and Driver Usopp,
move Brachio Tank 5 ahead slowly,
matching speed with the infantry!
Roger that, Tank Commander Chopper!
Dead slow ahead!
Keep an eye on the windows of the pleasure hall
just in case!
I got it!
If you see a human figure in the window...
Kin'emon!
It's noisy outside.
Everyone, dive into the water!
What?!
Finally! We've finally made it back up this far again!
Lick!
Mama was with us when we came here...
It's all that bastard's fault!
Dammit!
Mama!
Hmph! Get swallowed up by the sea.
King... I won't forgive him!
We'll make him pay!
Let's go, brothers and sisters!
We'll enter the Land of Wano this time!
Yeah!
Climb all the way to the top!
What I want to know is,
why is this the only kind of entrance?!
It's crazy!
So is the alliance between us Big Mom Pirates
and the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
It's insane! What is Mama thinking?!
That's what she decided!
Forget about the alliance,
remember what we came here for!
Yeah! We must take care of Straw Hat
who disgraced Mama and tarnished our family's name...
...and show his decapitated head to the world!
How savage!
More importantly,
I'll become Kaido-san's favorite!
Screw you, Flampe!
We're here!
The Land of Wano!
We don't know what's out there!
Prepare to fight!
Don't drop your guard!
The last time, at this very place,
that damn King...
That's...!
What?! King?!
That bastard came back...
No, that's not him!
Marco?!
MARCO THE PHOENIX
FORMER 1ST DIVISION COMMANDER
OF THE WHITEBEARD PIRATES
Hmmm...
So the rumor about the Big Mom Pirates
and the Animal Kingdom Pirates' alliance...
...is true-yoi.
Marco from the Whitebeard Pirates?!
Their 1st division commander, Marco the Phoenix?!
Show no mercy! Shoot him down!
Now...
Go away!
Phoenix Brand!
I won't let you do that!
You've got to be kidding!
Again?!
Why is he here?!
The next time you make it to the Land of Wano,
you may find things are slightly!
What the? A big ship is falling-meow!
Look up.
It's been a while.
I'll get you this time for sure!
Straw Hat!
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
We've all seen his limitless tenacity and power
with our own eyes.
He's the one who Ace wanted to save
and who Pops approved of!
We're bound to bring him into the new era!
I thought that you all were better than that!
Not that it matters!
The Whitebeard Pirates!
Akainu!
The degree to which you see him as a risk
makes you wanna kill him.
The degree to which we have high expectations of him
makes us wanna protect him.
They're the same, don't you agree-yoi?
I haven't seen you...
...since the war.
Marco...
Have more.
Black Maria?!
Hey, why aren't you working on your task?
What task are you talking about?
The search for my stupid son!
Well, isn't this better,
Supreme Commander Kaido?
No, it's not.
Those fools will be enough for the search.
Those other insufferably annoying Tobi Roppo members...
That's why I'm here.
All right!
Like every other year, let's not stand on ceremony today!
Right, Orochi?! It's a great day!
That's right, Kaido!
The ghosts of the Kozuki Clan
who have haunted us for 20 years are all gone!
We have to celebrate today!
Kanjuro who deceived them
until the very last minute...
...has ended his 20-year acting career
and will be arriving soon.
Along with the captains of the battleships
who sank the Akazaya members into the sea!
He's an impressive one!
I might've killed him by accident
at that moment.
Blast Breath!
The amazing thing about Kanjuro
is that he can survive...
...even in such a perilous situation.
On top of that, by escaping death together,
Oden's trust in him became unshakable,
and the Akazaya members didn't suspect his betrayal.
But even though he was able to win so much trust,
Oden never opened up to him.
That means even those samurai retainers
haven't been told anything yet.
You mean, about that thing?
Yeah...
The key to the location of Laugh Tale,
the last island that Roger reached.
Akazaya?!
Why are you here?!
I have nothing to talk about
with wannabe actors like you.
--What did you say?!
--Are you out of your mind?!
Who cares! Cut him!
Who are you?!
Pardon me!
I need to speak to Orochi-sama!
Oh! You're here, Kanjuro!
I've never seen him before.
You wanna fight here?!
Calm down, you fools! He's Orochi's man!
It has been a while, Orochi-sama!
The mansion is massive,
so I got a little bit lost.
KUROZUMI KANJURO
SHOGUN OROCHI'S INFORMANT
I had to slice up all those men
who saw me as their enemy and attacked me.
I apologize for that.
Well, that's all right!
Oh-ho! I see you've got something there...
It is Kozuki Momonosuke, just like you asked for.
He is Oden's son.
There's a strong current ahead!
It's a bit risky,
but should we plunge into it?
Yeah...
Don't screw it up!
Aye-aye!
We'll charge at full speed!
Don't panic! Keep it horizontal!
I'll adjust the trim!
Okay! It's looking good!
Aye-aye, Captain!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Can you hear me-meow?
Is it Cat?! You're late! You just arrived?!
CAT
Yeah!
We just climbed up the falls!
GUARDIANS - CAT VIPER'S SUBORDINATES
Do you know what day and what time it is?!
It's the night of the Fire Festival, the day of the great battle,
so we're just in time.
You-gara can't say that yet.
We're already on our way
to the northwestern end of Onigashima.
Okay! Then, see you later!
No, wait! Wait, hey! Cat!
Clank.
He's as hasty as always.
I hope they can make it in time for our raid.
I haven't seen Cat-chan since we got separated,
but just like Dog-chan,
I guess he's quite big now, too.
That damn cat...
He'd better move as fast as he can.
We'll reach the back entrance soon!
I don't think he's gonna make it in time.
Because of the sea current,
normal ships can only approach from the front.
I hope Kin'emon and Denjiro
have reached the back entrance without any problems.
Yeah! I want to fulfill Oden-sama's wish
together with everyone!
Momonosuke-sama...
Please be safe!
It's a dead end.
Maybe.
You lost your way, didn't you, Zoro?
No, we can cut a path ourselves.
Quietly, though.
We shouldn't ruin the plan...
Yeah, okay.
Enma!
Well, there are always obstacles on a path...
Yeah...
You're right!
Big Sis! Please!
I am pleased-arinsu.
That's not what I meant.
Why don't you walk by yourself now?!
No-arinsu! This is more fun-arinsu!
This is no fun at all for me...
Really, Pay-Pay?!
I told you not to call me Pay-Pay!
You're actually having fun, right?
Cut it out...
We can't look for Yamato like this!
I don't give a shit about Kaido's stupid brat!
Don't talk bad about them!
--Pay-Pay, do something!
--Don't call me that!
Damn Luffy... He wandered off.
Where did he go?
I can use it quite well now.
Kaido must be up there.
There he is!
I'll cut off Straw Hat's head!
Ya-hoo!
There he is!
--That's him!
--The one who takes him down will be part of the Tobi Roppo!
Let me practice a little bit more with you guys!
Get him!
Ryuo!
Big Mom's anger cracks the ground!
She delivers a deadly strike
against her most hated Straw Hats from above!
Overcoming their trembling fear,
they challenge the Emperor of the Sea with Brachio Tank!
Go get her, Commander Chopper and Driver Usopp!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Pact Between Men! The Fierce Fighting of Brachio Tank!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!