Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
"The Pact Between Men!
The Fierce Fighting of Brachio Tank!"
Big Mom?! Why is she here?!
Oh, no! Oh, no! She'll eat me!
Oh, no! Oh, no...
Tank Commander Chopper!
Since we're disguising ourselves
as the Animal Kingdom Pirates crew,
I'm sure she thinks we're her allies!
What?!
O-Okay!
I forgot we were disguising ourselves
as the enemy!
Alright, let's do it!
I have a report!
This is Tank Commander Chopper!
He just introduced himself as Chopper!
I'm on security detail for the banquet!
Oh, you're on patrol.
She believed him!
That was close!
He looks awfully familiar...
It's him!
Wait!
You're the raccoon from Straw Hat's group!
Driver Usopp!
Retreat at full speed! Retreat at full speed!
Roger!
I won't let you get away!
I knew it wouldn't work!
Of course not!
Raccoon!
Retreat at full speed!
They're gone!
--Chobro!
--That's one fierce mature woman...
Good luck!
On the way here, he cut the rope and tried to escape
so I knocked him out!
Do not worry. He is alive!
How could you do that to
the heir of Kozuki who was once your lord...
You're so cold and heartless!
I've finished playing the role
so now he is just a brat I do not know.
I'm surprised! I indeed remember.
You're one of the Akazaya Nine
that I faced off against 20 years ago.
Yes... I remember you well, too.
I was disappointed to know you were the son of
that brave Oden 20 years ago and you haven't changed a bit!
Yes, he is just a shitty brat!
He just happens to have such a great lineage...
Oh, poor boy!
How could you punch such a little boy
until he bleeds.
Alright, drink! Let's make a toast first!
You've done well
serving as a spy for so long!
Good job!
No, Orochi-sama!
I failed to intercept the Akazaya's plan...
...due to the Straw Hats and other pirate groups'
surprise attack!
What?! Failed?!
The rebel forces, 5,400 strong,
are advancing towards Onigashima now!
Luffy?!
A-Are they still alive?
S-So are you saying that
th-the Akazaya members are still around?!
Screw you!
You failed to intercept their plan?!
I am deeply sorry!
You're the one who told me
that they'd rendezvous at Tokage Port!
Why didn't you exterminate them?!
K-Kin'emon outsmarted me!
I knew him for a long time,
but I did not know he was that tactical!
Don't make excuses!
Tell me, Kanjuro!
Will the samurai's fleet come to Onigashima?!
Seems like it's still safe here, Orochi-sama.
Fukurokuju!
There are no suspicious ships at the port.
However, three of our warships
haven't returned.
I...
...saw two of those ships
being sunk by the damn pirates.
In that case, it's reasonable to assume that
the other ship was sunk as well.
In fact, on the Performance Floor out there,
we confirmed four pirates.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Eustass "Captain" Kid.
"Murder Machine" Killer.
The members from both of their pirate groups
have very likely entered the island.
If you knew that, why didn't you report it?!
Queen-dono was handling it,
so I thought I'd better not spoil the banquet...
Whether they're here of not,
all our forces are here on Onigashima.
Whatever happens,
this is the safest place in the country!
You're right!
Drink, Orochi!
Here! Have a cup.
Mm... mm-hm...
No... I don't want any consolation!
I'd rather hear a report
that the damn samurai have been killed!
I'm sure it's gonna be fine!
Everyone must be here on Onigashima!
Because Luffy's here!
Survive however you can!
I'm gonna come rescue you!
I have to get away!
I must survive...
...however I can!
Black Maria!
Give him to me!
That's right! We must not forget!
He's the leader of the enemies!
Set the execution stage!
If their iconic Kozuki Family dies out,
their mouldering loyalty will crumble away, too!
And it'll all be over!
Luffy...
Everyone...
Father...
Are they all okay?
Yeah, of course they are!
Izo!
Thank you for everything, Cat.
He said everyone's already entered the island
so I guess the raid is underway!
That lonely island is now called Onigashima, huh?
Kiku...
Anyway, you left before me
but you're arriving at the same time as me.
I didn't need to entrust you
with my message to Straw Hat Luffy-yoi!
You're right! I'll throw this note out!
I'LL BE LATE BUT I'LL BE THERE - MARCO
--You said you're gonna go to the Land of Wano?
--Yeah.
What are you planning to do there?
We'll take down Kaido!
We'll do it! We'll avenge Oden-sama!
The Straw Hats will help us!
Okay...
Then I have even more reason to come with you.
Anyway, I can't believe you came, Marco.
Yeah, because I always liked Oden...
It's my friend's home which he risked his life to save.
How can I not help?
Thank you. I'm indebted to you.
Don't say that.
I should've done something sooner.
I can't believe how much Oden's country
has changed...
Information about the Land of Wano
doesn't cross the sea.
I didn't know the once rich Land of Wano
was in such a state...
It's all because of Kaido.
I guess you're now determined!
Let's hurry to Onigashima!
We must catch up to everyone!
But what should we do?
Their raid has already started.
How do we join them
in the presence of the enemy?
Count on me! I have an idea!
As planned, Denjiro is leading the Southern Forces
toward the back entrance of the castle.
SOUTHERN FORCES - DENJIRO'S GROUP
There's an undocumented gate!
They must've extended the place.
Hide!
Is it a top officer? What a pain!
--Listen! Find him as quickly as possible!
--Yes, sir!
No, not so much of a pain after all.
I know him.
I'll go talk to him...
Who is it?!
Wait, it's me!
You're...
It's been a while...
Sasaki!
SASAKI, TOBI ROPPO, ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Kyoshiro! I heard you weren't coming this year!
Yeah, don't tell anyone about me!
You're here incognito?
What happened to your special faux-pompadour?
It's unusual for you to leave a banquet.
Yeah. Kaido-san's kid went missing.
--Anyway, would you like to drink?
--Yes, I would!
Guys, go back to the Skull Dome!
I'll join you later.
The gate that wasn't on the blueprints.
And one of the Tobi Roppo, Sasaki.
However, for Kyoshiro
who was trusted by the enemy for so long,
they were easy obstacles to overcome.
Sea Prism Stone?!
Hey, what are you doing, Kyoshiro?!
--Tie him up!
--Yes, sir!
What's going on?! Hey!
--Cover his mouth, too!
--Yes, sir!
Answer me, Kyoshiro!
Hey, Sasaki...
Do you know the Land of Wano's history?
Is that...?!
After restraining one of the formidable Tobi Roppo,
Denjiro split his group into two
just as the Eastern Forces did.
--Get inside the dome from here!
--Good luck!
DOME INFILTRATION TEAM
Thus, the Southern Forces are steadily closing in on Kaido!
RAID TEAM
How annoying those fools are!
Where did you go, raccoon?!
You've got to pay for the wedding cake!
Your Majesty!
We heard you want to destroy a tank
so we came in haste!
All right. Then why don't you take up
your positions already to smoke them out?!
Yes, ma'am!
Tank Commander Chopper, what should we do?!
It doesn't look good!
They're each setting up traps with the intent to shoot us!
Oh, no!
We're finished!
Tank Commander Chopper!
Don't you remember our purpose?!
Our purpose?
Our mission is to rejoin Franky and the Black Rhino
at the promised hill,
and combine to become the General Franky!
Oh, yeah...
That combo is our best shot!
Your animal instincts are
the only hope we have to get through this situation!
Driver Usopp...
You're right. I guess I got too frazzled.
If we can't trust this Brachio Tank,
who else will?!
Tank Commander Chopper, your order sir!
Let's go! Charge at full speed!
Roger!
The enemy's lying in ambush at the slit in the wall!
When I give the cue,
turn round by drifting!
Now!
Go, Brachio!
Shoot!
Okay, fire back!
Launch mortar attacks!
Leave it to me!
There are massive cannons ahead!
Charge, don't hesitate!
We'll get them at close range!
Now! Driver Usopp, show them what you've got!
Leave it to me!
They took them all down... Not bad.
But now I know where the raccoon is!
Do you know the weak point of a tank?
It's an attack from right above!
Big Mom Bomber strikes!
She's above us! Let's get away at full speed!
Stop the tank!
Why, Commander?!
Trust the thickness of Brachio Tank's armor!
There must be a way out!
Okay, let's rest our fate on Brachio Tank.
Here you go!
Go to hell!
Driver Usopp, now!
All right! A point-blank shot!
Here's some extra candy! Enjoy!
We won, didn't we, Driver Usopp?
Tank Commander, it's a total victory!
Expertly commanded, Tank Commander Chopper!
No, we survived thanks to your shooting skills!
Anyway, it was a tough battle...
Commander, let's meet up with everyone else!
All right. Let's go back!
You guys, you don't really think
you can bring me down that easily,
do you?!
Screw you!
Commander, w-what is your order...
Y-You know what I would say...
Make a strategic retreat!
I knew it wouldn't work out!
Of course not!
Raccoon!
Even though they were frightened,
they ran in the opposite direction...
Thank you, Commander Chopper, Driver Usopp...
Let's move on!
Yeah!
Everyone! Don't let the sacrifice go to waste!
Hey, shouldn't we do something?!
I think that monstrous mature woman
is too much for those two boys to handle!
She's right! It's Big Mom!
Yes, that's why there's nothing we can do!
Let's just thank them for luring her away!
Anyway, why is it so hot here?
Nami! Look up! We're in trouble!
I found you!
It's the woman who kidnapped Zeus, Mama!
Get him!
Ryuo!
Damn you!
You bastard!
Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay!
Go for it! Pay-Pay!
Hey! Go look elsewhere, you idiot!
What, Pay-Pay?! Did you call me an idiot?!
Shut up! You're an idiot!
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Say that I'm a wonderful Big Sis!
But...
I can't run anymore...
Pay-Pay! I'm tired-arinsu!
I don't care! Let's go!
I have no energy left...
Even my dear brother is taking me for a fool...
Poor me!
Don't bother me!
If you're tired, just sit there!
Why can't you say...
Oh, no!
..."Let me carry you on my back"?!
ULTI AND PAGE ONE
TOBI ROPPO, ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Hey, get off of me! Hey!
Wait! Let go of me! Big Sis!
You little...
Hey! Stop it! I mean it!
Pay-Pay?!
Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay!
Stay, stay, stay with me!
Oh, my Pay-Pay!!
What the?
Pay-Pay!
Pay-Pay sacrificed himself to save me!
Who the hell are you?!
Who are you?!
Acknowledged as a strong enemy!
The Color of the Supreme King, used by the man who aspires
to be King of the Pirates, surprises Ulti and Page One.
When they are about to attack Luffy in their beast forms,
a stranger in a demon mask appears
with the sound of wooden clogs.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Thunder Bagua! Here Comes Kaido's Son!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!