mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
On the way here, he cut the rope and tried to escape
so I knocked him out!
Do not worry. He is alive!
How could you do that to
the heir of Kozuki who was once your lord...
You're so cold and heartless!
I've finished playing the role
so now he is just a brat I do not know.
You've done well
serving as a spy for so long!
Good job!
No, Orochi-sama!
I failed to intercept the Akazaya's plan...
...due to the Straw Hats and other pirate groups'
surprise attack!
What?! Failed?!
The rebel forces, 5,400 strong,
are advancing towards Onigashima now!
Luffy?!
A-Are they still alive?
S-So are you saying that
th-the Akazaya members are still around?!
Screw you!
You failed to intercept their plan?!
Black Maria!
Give him to me!
That's right! We must not forget!
He's the leader of the enemies!
Set the execution stage!
If their iconic Kozuki Family dies out,
their mouldering loyalty will crumble away, too!
And it'll all be over!
Luffy...
Everyone...
Father...
Here you go!
Go to hell!
Driver Usopp, now!
All right! A point-blank shot!
Here's some extra candy! Enjoy!
You guys, you don't really think
you can bring me down that easily,
do you?!
Screw you!
Commander, w-what is your order...
Y-You know what I would say...
Make a strategic retreat!
I knew it wouldn't work out!
Of course not!
Raccoon!
Even though they were frightened,
they ran in the opposite direction...
Thank you, Commander Chopper, Driver Usopp...
Damn you!
You bastard!
What the?
Who the hell are you?!
Who are you?!
"Thunder Bagua!
Here Comes Kaido's Son!"
Finally!
Finally here!
I've been waiting!
I've been waiting all this time!
To see you...
I've been waiting all this time for this moment!
Kid! As I thought,
it's too reckless to break through head-on!
Stop complaining and watch my back!
Together we can make it possible!
You're right!
We got separated from Heat and the others...
...who were fighting along with us,
WIRE     HEAT
KID PIRATES
but they'll make it through somehow.
Repel!
If we kill you guys,
we'll get a chance to be promoted!
If you aim so high...
prepare yourself and bring it on!
--Please stop!
--Kaido-sama is looking for you!
Stop bothering me! Leave me alone!
Young Master! Please stop!
If you let down your guard, you'll die!
Pay-Pay!
Pay-Pay! Are you okay?!
Stay with me-arinsu!
Hey, you!
How could you...
How could you do this to Pay-Pay?!
Don't bully my Pay-Pay!
You're the one who slid down the stairs
using him as skis.
Say that I'm a wonderful Big Sis!
But...
I can't run anymore...
Pay-Pay! I'm tired-arinsu!
I don't care! Let's go!
I have no energy left...
Even my dear brother is taking me for a fool...
Poor me!
Don't bother me!
If you're tired, just sit there!
Why can't you say...
Oh, no!
..."Let me carry you on my back"?!
ULTI AND PAGE ONE
TOBI ROPPO, ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Hey, get off of me! Hey!
Wait! Let go of me! Big Sis!
You little...
Hey! Stop it! I mean it!
Pay-Pay?!
Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay! Pay-Pay!
Stay, stay, stay with me!
Oh, my Pay-Pay!!
What the?
Pay-Pay!
Pay-Pay sacrificed himself to save me!
No! I didn't do anything!
What's your name?! Who do you work for
and which unit do you belong to?!
No, Big Sis...
He's an intruder.
What?!
Hey, you! Who the hell are you?!
I'm Luffy.
The man who'll become the King of the Pirates!
Do you know who's castle this is?
It's certain that
Kaido-sama will become the King of the Pirates!
You uber-idiot!
I'll smash your skull!
A head-butt?!
Ulti-Mortar!
Hey, Big Sis!
I know...
You too, Pay-Pay?
Yeah!
Excuse me, but...
...why did you two transform?!
ULTI
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
PACHYCEPHALOSAURUS MODEL
Ulti-sama!
PAGE ONE
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
SPINOSAURUS MODEL
Page One-sama!
Ulti-sama? Um...
Shut up!
Because we...
...have acknowledged him as a strong enemy!
No, his head got cracked and he's already dead!
Then how do you explain that Haki?!
That hurt!
There are a bunch of tough ones...
I was downplaying it.
I was wrong.
This castle belongs to an Emperor of the Sea!
I will destroy you!
Gum-Gum...
Big Sis!
...Elephant Gun!
Page One-sama! Are you okay?!
Page One-sama...
You bastard!
How dare you do that to Pay-Pay?!
I'll destroy you!
Ulti-sama turned into a dinosaur, too!
Please! The castle can't take it anymore!
Shut up! Don't tell me what to do!
Ulti-Mortar!
How tough your head is!
This won't be over until it's all smashed up!
She's... so strong!
I'm gonna break your head open!
Ulti-Meteor!
Oh, no!
Gear Four!
Thunder Bagua!
Straw Hat Luffy!
It's you, isn't it?!
Yes, it is!
I...
Who are you?!
--He's getting way!
--Yamato-sama!
Catch him!
I'm sorry! I'm not gonna hurt you!
Yeah, you don't seem like you will...
Listen, I gotta go!
I've been waiting for you!
Finally! You're finally here!
All this time!
My name is Yamato!
I'm Kaido's son!
Out of the frying pan into the fire!
Luffy got away from the formidable members of the Tobi Roppo,
but Kaido's son, Yamato, stands in his way!
He hides his ambition and shows his monstrous strength!
What does he want from Luffy?!
When the two collide, another fact will be revealed.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Enemy or Ally? Luffy and Yamato!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!