Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
After infiltrating Kaido's castle,
Luffy was blocked by Ulti and Page One.
You bastard!
How dare you do that to Pay-Pay?!
I'll destroy you!
Ulti-Meteor!
Coming to Luffy's aid was none other than...
THUNDER BAGUA
Thunder Bagua!
I've been waiting for you!
All this time!
My name is Yamato!
I'm Kaido's son!
"Enemy or Ally?
Luffy and Yamato!"
So that's Onigashima.
King...
Marco...
Phoenix Brand!
Again?!
Straw Hat...
They better prepare themselves... Lick!
And, I don't approve of Mama's alliance!
The Big Mom Pirates will have the last laugh!
Shoot!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
I knew it wouldn't work!
Don't give up!
If we can't trust this Brachio Tank,
who else will?!
I won't let go of this
lever even if it kills me!
Usopp...
Targeting Big Mom!
Brachio Tank, High-Explosive Anti-Tank!
Shoot!
Life or...
Don't do it!
Mama!
Zeus and the woman who
kidnapped him are here!
Did she walk away?
Yay! We did it!
That'll teach you, Big Mom!
This is what the Brachio Tank is capable of!
That'll teach you!
What's going on?!
With that punch, it seems like
the transformation switch has been activated.
We've got to combine it with the Black Rhino ASAP.
to form the General Franky!
Uh-huh! To the promised hill!
But what should we do, Usopp?!
Big Mom went after Nami and the others!
I guess she'll try to take back Zeus.
I'm worried about them...
Well, they're gonna be fine...
Sanji's with them, too.
Sanji, huh?
I hope he won't forget about rescuing
Momonosuke and start chasing
women at the pleasure hall...
That's quite possible.
But let's trust Sanji!
Yeah!
Kin'emon and the others were able to move forward,
so we're doing well!
We showed them
what this Brachio Tank is capable of!
Yeah! Commander Chopper!
Sniper and Driver Usopp!
The Brachio Tank 5!
Nothing stands in our way!
Come on!
An old umbrella.
Old clogs and old sandals.
A dirt wall! A candle!
A lantern, too!
I'll give you life!
Follow me.
Mama, this way!
Hey! Don't call her, Sun!
What should I do, Nami?!
If I get caught by her, she'll kill me!
Is that overripe mature
woman really that dangerous?
She's on a whole different level!
Hey, didn't we see Sanji a little while ago?
Uh-huh!
Oh, but...
Sorry for making you worry...
I'm not gonna give up on finding those women!
What did he come here for?!
In any case, we must outrun her
and look for Momonosuke-sama!
Okay!
Mama! This way!
We don't need to rush.
The Performance Floor is ahead.
They can't get away!
Everyone is drunk
and there is virtually no security.
It's like an all-you-can-assassinate buffet.
Is that...
Those samurai have successfully snuck in.
You're quite cute! Which
unit do you belong to?
What's your name? Tell me.
What is it?
I'm sorry, but I don't
have a name to tell you.
You scare me.
Guys!
Shogun Orochi presents!
An impromptu special event starting now!
Is that...
Everyone! The brat that you see...
Lo and behold!
He's Kozuki Oden's son
who was thought to be dead 20 years ago!
Tonight, I'll show this brat mercy,
and send him to meet his father!
Damn Orochi.
How could he start such a stupid thing?
He ruined the mood of my banquet.
Damn! What's going on?!
There are a bunch of power-users...
Call us Gifters.
I can't believe you made it all the way
inside your enemy's territory.
You really don't fear death.
Yeah, I suppose not.
I know you wanna become
the King of the Pirates, too.
We as well were once aiming to be
the King of the Pirates.
But as long as Kaido-sama's alive,
you'll never accomplish it!
I have no interest in that.
It's our captain who'll become
the King of the Pirates.
Hmmm...
You're quite handsome.
Why don't you join us?
What if I say no?
Can you?
This is how powerful Kaido-sama is!
There are almost 500 of us.
If you obey Kaido-sama,
it'll make things easier for you.
Take the easy way.
You can still start over.
No way!
Willing to die?!
What the...
No, I'm not willing to die at all.
But you guys better be.
If I have to die,
I'd rather fall forward than backwards.
You said you were Kaido's son...
What do you want from me?
I have something to tell you.
It's important.
I don't have time now.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna hurt you.
Didn't you hear me say...
I don't have time?!
I said I don't have time!
I have something to tell you.
Big Sis! Stay with me!
Big Sis!
Thunder Bagua!
THUNDER BAGUA
Hey, you dumbasses!
Bring the medical team!
--Hey!
--Yes...
Don't lose those two.
Keep them cornered and let us know where they are.
Damn Yamato!
Page One-san!
You received a pretty hard blow, too.
Elephant Gun!
Oh, no...
Page One-san needs to be treated, too!
Yeah, that was quite a punch...
My jaw is probably dislocated.
Is that it?!
More importantly,
isn't the medical team here yet?
We're here!
How is she?
You're hurting my eyes!
Sob... Sob...
Pay-Pay!
It hurts-arinsu! Poor me!
Why don't you keep quiet then?
What did you say?!
How dare you talk to me like that!
Are you a rebellious teen?
Do you wanna make me cry?!
Anyway, that fool Yamato...
How could he use Kaido-sama's Thunder Bagua
as his own?!
She looks fine.
His is more like Thunder BADua.
It didn't hurt me at all...
Big Sis...
Page One-sama!
Yamato-sama and Straw Hat stopped running!
Okay!
Hey, Pay-Pay!
Don't leave me!
Where are you taking me?!
I've got no time for a stranger!
Wait. I just wanna talk.
Get out of my way!
Listen to what I have to say!
You have five seconds!
People can hear us.
I wanna talk to you in private.
Then, no!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
You're hard-headed!
Red Hawk!
It reminds me of...
...the fight against that man!
Who are you?! Give me your name!
Give me your name!
I'm...
...Ace!
I'm here to take Kaido's head!
Having inherited Oden's will,
the Akazaya members gather at Onigashima!
Momonosuke is sentenced to death!
In a time-sensitive situation,
Yamato passionately shares his determination!
Kaido's son takes his mask off
and shows the confused Luffy his real face.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Desire to be Oden! Yamato's Dream!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!