Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
"The Akazaya Face-off!
Kikunojo vs. Kanjuro!"
Oh, my...
Big Mom?!
Welcome back, Zeus.
Ma... ma...
Mama!
She looks so scary up close!
She's the world's strongest old bag!
Zeus!
Nami?!
They've been caught?!
You're finally here, Linlin!
What took you so long?!
Don't be so stiff, Kaido!
I made it in time.
As Kaido said,
we formed an alliance for a purpose!
A purpose?
If we're at each other's throats,
it's out of our reach,
but if we join hands,
it's already within our grasp!
Okay, guys?!
We'll concentrate on pirating!
We're finally...
...going to go get...
...the great treasure of the One Piece!
The One Piece...
That's something I'm gonna have!
Those bastards!
The presence of the Ancient Weapons...
...will bring about fear and a war in the world!
Prepare yourself!
That's the world of violence that we hope for!
The Ancient Weapons...
It is said that three of them exist
and that they bear the names of gods...
PLUTON
Pluton.
URANUS
Uranus.
POSEIDON
Poseidon.
If they seize those powers,
the world will lose its balance
and hurtle down the path of destruction.
--Isn't that a bit dramatic?
--No, it's true.
That's exciting!
So listen, Orochi's subordinates!
You must choose.
Choose what?
This country...
...is a natural stronghold
surrounded by the falls,
which the Navy and the World Government
can't easily penetrate.
If we build more weapon factories,
and force
even the people of the Flower Capital to work,
this place will become a lawless land,
a paradise for pirates!
Kaido-sama... What do you mean?
I'm sure you heard me.
Hey...
Hey!
Kaido, you bastard!
What are you blabbing about?!
The Flower Capital is my home turf!
Just because I'm Kurozumi,
do you know... do you know how much pain...
...the Kozuki Clan has given me over the years?!
I was persecuted and despised just for being alive,
and they took away everything from me!
A grudge against the Kozuki Clan!
And against the Land of Wano!
An urge for revenge against them all...
That is what has driven me all this way!
In a sense, the Flower Capital is
the symbol of the Kurozumi Clan's retaliation!
Their lands and lives...
...are all mine!
Even you...
...can't mess with it as you please!
Are you listening?!
I'll make the rascals of the Kozuki Clan
who tortured the Kurozumi Clan get on their knees,
and to keep them from rebelling against me,
I'll parade horrors before them!
Forever and ever!
I'm the one who'll destroy the Land of Wano!
This country is mine!
Know your place, Kaido!
You've been here for only a short time!
Who do you think is making it possible
for you to procure weapons?!
The Land of Wano can only exist with me!
I hope you know that!
I see you understand.
What we've got to do now...
...is kill that brat right...
I don't care!
We don't need him anymore!
What nonsense!
To me...
both the Kurozumi Clan...
...and the Kozuki Clan...
...mean nothing!
Momo!
Hey, that's Momo!
Momo, wait for me!
Hey, keep it down!
--Hey, what the hell?!
--What's going on?!
Kaido!
You fool! What are you doing?!
Hey! We gotta get to Momo!
Show me the way!
O-Okay!
Yamato-sama! Please stop!
I'm coming for you, Momo!
BACK ENTRANCE, ONIGASHIMA
What?!
I know the habits in your swordplay,
but you don't know my techniques, right?!
Finish him off, Kiku!
O-Okiku, I'm sorry...
I can only live as a member of the Kurozumi Clan...
So kill me already!
I still remember the days we spent together
like siblings...
Living while deceiving you...
...was always painful.
I really, really think I did horrible things
to Momonosuke-sama, too...
I was born Kurozumi,
and I could only live like this...
Forgive me!
I...
...actually wanted to live
side by side with you guys!
Kiku! Do it!
Kanjuro-san... it's not too late!
Let's take down Kaido!
How can you...
How can you believe in a jerk like me...
You're so...
...naive!
Kiku!
Tell me that it's all a lie.
This Kanjuro-san...
...is a fake!
The Kanjuro-san I'm facing now...
...is nothing but a phony!
Okiku!
Hey!
What are you doing?!
How dare you cut me, who is like a brother to you
in cold blood!
It's so painful to be betrayed!
I'll make you pay for it!
You betrayed me!
What is your true heart?!
Who in the world are you?!
The Kanjuro-san who laughed and cried with us
back in those days...
Give him back to us!
What?! No way!
I thought we were gonna be friends
no matter what...
I never believed that from the start!
This is the real me right here!
My life as an Akazaya member...
...was all an act!
I didn't share any joy or sorrow with you!
I don't give a damn about you!
I did everything for the Kurozumi Clan!
Go to hell!
Look at this!
This spectacular grand stage!
Everything was fake...
Your life is all an act...
You only lived your role...
It wasn't fake!
I've been living to fulfill my role all my life...
If I touched you emotionally,
I feel blessed for being such a good actor!
What?!
I sliced up...
...my own heart
that was trying to believe in you!
The charade is over!
I wish you said your betrayal was an act.
We'll never able to see the Kanjuro-san
that we knew...
The joys and sorrows we shared...
...were all an illusion!
The Kanjuro-san that I knew...
...was just a drawing!
You have no one to say goodbye to.
In that case...
In that case, I have no mercy!
Great! This is an unforeseen twist!
Fallen Snow Blade!
I can predict all your moves!
This is a simple one!
Okiku, you're still as kind as ever!
The guy right here is not Kanjuro!
Kanjuro-san...
...is no longer here!
Why?!
You said everything was all an act!
I thought we were friends!
Tell me, Kanjuro!
Why?!
Excellent...
Excellent! Well done, Okiku!
I've been looking for...
...a place to die!
If...
...I can...
...die on this grand stage,
I'd be very happy!
It's perfect!
Good!
I feel...
...great!
Kin-san...
Yeah. Let's go.
Kin'emon-dono! Denjiro-dono!
Good luck!
Good luck to you too!
It's not fair to attack me from behind!
Hey, Kawamatsu! That's my brush!
Whoa-whoa!
Be nice to each other!
We don't have money, Oden-sama!
What?!
We got nothing to eat for dinner!
No dinner again, Oden-sama?!
Oh, come on!
Okay, you got a job to do!
Beg for food in the town!
Again?!
I've never heard a Daimyo say that!
You're right. Me neither.
My name is Kanjuro.
My name is Kin'emon.
Good to meet you!
We both like Oden-san,
so let's get along.
Yeah, sounds good!
It must have been hard, you guys.
Kin-san...
Let's keep moving forward for now.
Izo...
Is it okay for you to die here?
I don't wanna miss another chance to die.
Okay. Let's go.
Okiku.
Now the fly that was attracted to pirates
is dead.
Decide what to do in five seconds,
Orochi's men!
Do you wanna become pirates and follow me?
Or do you wanna challenge us here and die?!
To prepare for the upcoming world war,
I will turn this country into a pirate empire!
We'll go on more expeditions
for our primary business.
So tonight,
we'll relocate this Onigashima
to the Flower Capital,
and the Land of Wano will fall!
That bastard!
Rename the country New Onigashima.
The new Shogun is my son...
Yamato!
What did he...
...just say?!
You can't force that on me!
You shitty old man!
Hurry up! Momo will be killed!
Let's take a shortcut!
Okay!
After 20 years of despair,
the Akazaya Nine charge, sweeping away the enemies!
The target is their sworn enemy, Kaido!
Momonosuke who trembles
before his execution faces a tough decision.
For the Land of Wano and the Kozuki Clan,
swear by heaven and earth!
Stake your lives on this blow!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Raid! Inheriting Oden's Will"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!