Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Kozuki Oden!
I've been waiting for a guy like you!
I won't let you have free reign
in the Land of Wano anymore!
Interesting.
Now choose! Orochi's samurai!
Do you wanna die alongside your lord Orochi here?!
Or conquer the world with us?!
I know how you samurai are loyal.
I admire even those of you who challenge us!
The Land of Wano will change.
Along with our new allies,
we'll build a new foundation for this world!
What are you gonna do?
The Land of Wano Ninja Force and Oniwabanshu!
5,000 strong!
We'd like to serve you!
Likewise, the Land of Wano Samurai Force,
5,000 strong!
We'll serve you from now on!
We welcome you!
Orochi-sama...
Well, who cares...
Great! I didn't wanna become your enemy suddenly
and try to kill you guys!
Looking forward to working with you!
They don't even deserve to be called samurai!
Hold it in for now, Boss Hyogoro!
I can't believe you recruited
the worthless Shogun's subordinates...
You're pretty good!
Now, the forces are well-organized!
Let go of me!
No! Stop it!
Keep them restrained.
I won't let you guys have your way!
If Shinobu-chan can get away,
we still have a chance!
I'm sorry, Onami!
I'm going ahead!
Hurry to Momo-chan's rescue!
Oden-sama knew it!
That taking down Orochi wouldn't change anything!
For 20 years, Kaido has been the only one
that we've needed to bring down!
Everyone!
To avenge our late lord Oden-sama,
and...
...to rescue Momonosuke-sama,
we are aiming at one thing!
Taking Kaido's head!
Let's go!
"Raid!
Inheriting Oden's Will"
Now in the Land of Wano,
there is no Shogun
or samurai who serve under him!
The foolish citizens of the Flower Capital...
...must be enjoying the festivities too much
to see that this will be their last day.
What do you see in the future you imagine?
Hey, you brat! I've always had doubt.
A coward like you...
...can't be that daring Kozuki Oden's son!
I...
This execution is for bringing an end
to the old Land of Wano.
Looking back at that day 20 years ago,
in the burning castle, you...
...didn't answer my question!
Help...
Your father was a silly lord.
My father was a great samurai...
...and I'm...
...the one
who will govern this country someday!
What's your name?!
Say it!
Mo...
Father!
Somebody, help!
If you're not Kozuki Oden and Toki's son,
I'll cancel your execution immediately.
I'd be ashamed
because it would've been a false accusation.
But if you doggedly say you're their son,
you'll face the same fate as Oden.
Momo-chan!
Let go of me! I can't take it anymore!
Let me ask you one more time, you brat.
What's your name?!
Kaido-sama is so generous!
All that brat has to do is lie
and he can survive!
Come up with a funny name, kid!
Please stay alive even if it means you have to lie!
Momonosuke-sama!
What?! Then that boy...
...is the real Kozuki Momonosuke?!
That's right! Oden's retainers are all alive!
What?!
Intruders!
Get out of my way!
If those Akazaya samurai I saw that day
are all...
If they're all alive, that's wonderful!
That's great!
Unbelievable!
Momonosuke's waiting for you!
Let's hurry! They're here, right?
The Akazaya Nine!
Let me down, Yamao!
Yamao? Why are you calling me that?
Please stop, Yamato-sama!
Stop!
Young Master Yamato and Straw Hat Luffy
are heading to the floor!
To the Performance Floor?
Yes! We'll catch them!
No, don't try. You're no match...
How could they mess with my men!
Yamato!
I'll make you pay!
No, Usopp! Not this way!
It looks dangerous!
You heard the broadcast earlier!
They'll kill Momo!
The Giants!
They'll prey on us!
Let's turn back, Usopp!
Don't be scared, Chopper!
We fought an Emperor of the Sea to a standstill!
Believe in the General Franky's toughness
that endured Big Mom's attacks!
I can't! I can't stand these monsters!
Don't give in! Don't kneel down!
Tank Commander Chopper, what's your order?!
Retreat! Retreat!
Jaki!
How annoying!
What's a remnant of the Whitebeard Pirates like you
doing here?!
I'm trying to exterminate pests!
You guys formed an alliance with Kaido, right?
I'm here to break up that alliance!
We don't need to join sides with that monster!
He's nothing but trouble for us!
You too, Marco!
I won't forgive you!
I wish I could say that, but I'm no fool.
I'm up against one of the Four Emperors...
What are you mumbling about-yoi?!
Kaido is our common enemy, right?
I came up with a good idea.
The Big Mom Pirates will conquer this world!
And Mama will become the King of the Pirates!
We'll kill...
...everyone who gets in our way.
Say it, you squirt!
What's your name?!
It's impossible for me...
...to take down Kaido!
Because your father is a great man,
and you are the one
who will govern this country someday.
Mother...
Are you scared?!
Cut the "samurai" crap!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates someday!
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
Are you gonna just cry?!
The meaning of your name?
Yes!
I want you to be a man who is compassionate,
broad-minded, and admirable.
Momo!
The word "Momo"...
...stands for peerless!
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
I'm the one who'll become...
...the Shogun of the Land of Wano!!
Momonosuke-sama!
You're so brave, Momonosuke!
I'll save you at any cost, Momonosuke-sama!
Well said, Momonosuke!
We're almost there, Luffy!
Let me take these off! I promised you!
Please!
Just in case... to be safe...
throw them far away...
Though I don't think they'll explode...
Are there only idiots in the Land of Wano?!
Father... Mother...
I just wanted to be the man...
...who wouldn't have to be ashamed of himself
when I see you in the afterworld.
Hiyori, I wish I could see you again
even for a little bit...
I don't want to die!
I don't want to cry!
A samurai shouldn't cry in front of others...
It's embarrassing...
They came off!
What the hell is going on?!
It's hot! It's hot! It's hot!
What?!
Luffy?!
Damn!
That cow-gorilla!
He was gonna kill me!
What was that explosion?!
Find out now!
I understand!
He's not my father anymore!
Y-Y-Y-Young Master!
I'll take care of him myself!
Did you do it, you spoiled brat?!
Wait, Yamao!
You damn old man!
Let go of me!
Calm down, Yamao!
My name is Yamato! Don't stop me!
We made it in time...
but it's not supposed to be me or Yamao!
We're not the ones who'll start the great battle!
The Akazaya samurai!
Where did they come from?!
The rulers of the Minks?! They're alive!
You damn ghosts! I'll strike back at you!
Izo!
You fools!
Stop drinking!
Pick up your weapons!
We're getting raided!
Are you...
...Kyoshiro?!
Kaido!
You half-ghost bastards!
Su-rrender your na-me!
Be as a chi-ld!
Your blades...
...can't cut me!
Stake your lives on this blow!
Oden!
Don't ever come back to the Land of Wano!
Sunacchi!!
Oden...
I can't lose!
The Akazaya members finally
deliver Kaido his punishment!
Grievous cries echo all over Onigashima
and the Emperors' alliance starts to crumble!
Luffy challenges the irritated Big Mom to a fight!
The great battle for the future of the Land of Wano
and the title of the King of the Pirates begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Onigashima in Tumult! Luffy's All-Out War Begins!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!