Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Sunacchi!!
Even if it kills you, cling on to Kaido's head!
The Akazaya samurai got into a deadly battle
against Kaido.
Luffy-dono!
Thank you!
Kin'emon! I'll catch up to you later!
I'll show you the world's greatest military power!
Jack is our sworn enemy
who devastated our thousand-year-old kingdom.
I have a score to settle with you, too!
To pay off an old score,
the Minks in their Sulong form
clash with Jack who is leading the Numbers.
"Zeus' Treason?!
The Cornered Nami!"
It has begun.
That bastard Jack went up?
He's considerate, unlike you.
King, do you have a problem with me?!
Hey!
Momonosuke-sama...
I'll save you at any cost!
Straw Hat!
Prepare yourself!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
What do you want?!
This is Point E!
We're in battle with the enemies!
At Point B, there are tons of Udon prisoners!
We can't stop them!
What?!
What happened?! Respond!
Can't you hear me?!
They broke through Point A!
What should we do, Queen-sama?!
--Queen-sama!
Idiots! Don't all speak at once!
Figure it out yourselves!
Shinobu?!
Momonosuke-sama...
Look what they've done to you...
I, Shinobu, will rescue you now.
Ripe-Ripe Enticement Jutsu!
Quietly...
Stop whining like losers!
Ulti! I don't have time for you!
Yamato!
Are you trying to turn your back on me?!
I'm Kozuki Oden, and I've got things to do!
Momo!
If you dare run here,
I'll kill you, you fool!
We have problems here, too!
Damn you!
Shinobu...
Momonosuke-sama...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
--Queen-sama!
--Don't yell!
Stop whining and come to the Performance Floor!
We're short-handed here!
Hurry up!
Clank.
Oh, no!
Shinobu!
The idea wasn't bad.
But...
...the execution was poor!
Shinobu!
Shinobu-chan!
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm ashamed to have been knocked out!
Let's try again!
What the...
What?! He's flying!
Flying!
It's so high! I'm scared!
Momonosuke-sama! What's happening?!
On behalf of Kaido-san,
I'll execute you!
What's that?
Sangoro!
Sanji-kun!
Sanji!
You're the best!
Give me the brat!
He has to be wiped out from this world!
Momonosuke-sama!
Hey, Momo!
Your self-introduction earlier...
...gave me the chills!
Sangoro!
The word "Momo"...
...stands for peerless!
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
I'm the one who'll become...
...the Shogun of the Land of Wano!!
Sangoro!
Shinobu-chan, look after him!
Okay!
Thank you, Sangoro!
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm glad that you're okay!
The Kozuki must die out!
The acceleration device!
Activate stealth!
Shooting Star! Soba Kick!
What an over-the-top technique...
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
This is no good! I'm in danger!
Stop it, you bird brain!
If nothing is done,
I'll get a hole in my stomach and die!
Not just a hole! You'll be broken in half!
If you're so scared,
why not disappear and run!
It's just an optical illusion...
Just let go of me!
This is it!
Sanji!
Just let go of me!
This is it!
Sanji!
Sanji-kun!
Sanji...
San...
That attack was crazy...
Yamao! I'll leave Momo to you!
Protect him and Shinobu!
What?! Is that okay?!
Why are you asking me that?!
You're right. It's only natural.
B-Because he's my son!
Just go!
Yeah, leave it to me!
Fathers help their sons!
Hey, don't ignore me!
Wait for me, Momonosuke!
--Your father is on his way!
--Hey! Wait-arinsu!
I won't let you get away!
Straw Hat!
Even if the others escape,
I'll never let you get away!
Damn! I wanna go help Sanji!
Guys!
Let's kill all the samurai who came to attack us,
and start the banquet over!
You've ruined...
...the wedding, the tea party,
and this big banquet...
You always spoil other people's fun!
I won't forget!
No way!
Run! The cake is collapsing!
Luffy?!
That bastard!
Alright!
It's broken!
I'll kill you in a most befitting manner!
Your final breath will be pathetic!
Ikoku...
Oh, no!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Is that old bag a monster?!
I heard she's a pirate captain
who is as infamous as Kaido overseas!
What?! Then it's like we're facing two Kaidos?!
I wanna go save Momo and Sanji now,
but if she follows me,
I'll only lead the enemy to them!
Straw Hat, I can't believe you dodged that!
Come on, Zeus!
Zeus, what's the matter?!
You're...
She noticed!
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's impossible!
Nami! She'll kill us!
Zeus!
I look away for one moment
and now you're with her?
Bad boy!
Now, come back!
Okay, Mama...
Zeus!
Me or Big Mom, who do you choose?!
I can't stand up to Mama!
If you choose me, you can eat delicious things
like you did earlier.
What?
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yummy!
Is it true?!
I've never lied in my life.
So believe me. Okay?
Uh-huh, uh-huh! I believe you!
Let me eat as much as I like!
Enough already!
Nami!
You damn Cat Burglar!
It's my fault.
Sorry, Mama.
I won't go anywhere now, so forgive me!
Well, well... Now you're changing sides.
How can I trust someone
who would follow an annoying tramp like her?!
What should I do?!
What can I do to win your trust?!
You know what to do.
Take her down!
The watch? I threw it out!
I'm the wind!
Get this straight, Zeus!
If you hold back, I'll wipe you out!
No!
Activate the Soul Sensor!
I'm sorry, Nami!
Rest in peace!
I hate you!
I'm done with you!
Help!
Wings? I'll spread them!
I'm a bird!
I'll flutter my wings and fly away!
In the sky, on the wind!
I'm a free rider!
Franky!
Okay, you've been cut!
What?!
What?
Oops! I think I ran over something!
Who cares!
As long as I didn't run over a flower.
Big Bro!
Franky challenges Big Mom! Robin and Jimbei
come in to help him with a combination attack!
Meanwhile, Yamato has a fateful meeting
with Momonosuke to save him!
The one who inherits Oden's will
and the one who has Oden's blood.
Will this encounter lead them out of difficulty?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I'll Protect You! Yamato Meets Momonosuke!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!