Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
The great battle at Onigashima
is getting intense!
Shinobu, who tried to rescue Momonosuke,
was blocked by King...
But Sanji dashingly appeared.
Momonosuke-sama!
Hey, Momo!
Your self-introduction earlier...
...gave me the chills!
Sangoro!
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's impossible!
Nami! She'll kill us!
Zeus!
I look away for one moment
and now you're with her?
Bad boy!
I'm sorry, Nami!
Rest in peace!
I hate you!
I'm done with you!
Help!
I'm a free rider!
Franky!
Okay, you've been cut!
What?!
What?
Oops! I think I ran over something!
Who cares!
As long as I didn't run over a flower.
"I'll Protect You!
Yamato Meets Momonosuke!"
Mama!
They're doomed!
They're dead men!
He ran over Big Mom with his bike!
Big Bro!
Thank you, Franky!
Nami!
Are you okay?!
Yes! Yes! I'm fine!
If Big Bro's here, it'll
be a tremendous help!
Go! Samurai warriors!
It's already started!
It's a huge messy fight...
Since we're late,
we should work harder than everyone.
Oh, boy... Look what they ran into.
Help me a bit, Nico Robin.
Sure, I'm happy to.
Great!
That's what I expected from Franky and Brook!
Then I'm gonna...
...go help Kin'emon...
...now!
Damn! The drunk Giants!
How could they treat Brachio like a toy!
Get a grip! Let's fight back!
It's fine! Don't worry!
Believe in Brachio!
It got beaten badly,
but there's not a single scratch on its super body!
Super body!
The superalloy Wapometal is
as solid as it looks!
Let's start fighting back!
Change course!
Hurry away!
The targets are behind us!
Turn around and face them!
Aye, sir! Commander Chopper!
Get ready to fire!
Fire!
Ya-hoo!
All the shots hit!
Now you see how strong
Usopp, Brachio, and I are!
You did an excellent job, Gunner Usopp!
And your orders were superb,
Commander Chopper!
This is what we're capable of!
Big Mom, Giants, or whatever,
just bring it on!
High-Explosive...
...Anti-Tank...
...didn't...
...work!
Th-The tank is unbreakable...
But we can't take it
if you shake it so hard...
Please stop!
Y-Yamato, stop!
Damn you!
Yamato!
I'm gonna beat you within
an inch of your life,
and take you to Kaido-sama!
I don't have time for you!
And I won't go back to Kaido!
I have my own mission!
Leave me alone!
How annoying!
I'll kick your ass!
Stop dodging, you little...
Ulti!
I'll force my way through!
Now if you'll excuse me.
Wait for me.
I'm on my way!
Please forgive me...
I'll never ever let you go!
I, Shinobu, will protect you
even if it costs me my life!
I'm counting on you...
They'll see you here.
We should hide in the building.
There you are!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
Who are you?!
Hey, Shinobu!
He's our ally! You can trust him!
What? Our ally?!
It's safer to be with him
than to be by yourselves.
See you!
Are you really our ally?
Yeah!
Okay. I believe you.
What's your name?
What?!
I'm...
I'm Kozuki Oden!
I'll protect you!
Father...
Oden-sama...
Fath... er?
Breasts...
Horns?!
You can't be my father!
You're too suspicious! Definitely our enemy!
What?!
Smoke Escape Technique!
Wait!
Why are you running away?!
We're heavily outnumbered.
This will take forever.
You're right!
It's just a waste of time
to fight these small fries!
The dinosaurs called the Tobi Roppo
that Denjiro was talking about...
Should we go take their heads?
Even if we're no match for them...
We can still stall them!
Now...
I don't think she'll keep
sleeping like a baby forever.
Gee... I didn't see that coming...
Big Mom is about to lose control!
Run!
Finally...
You're up.
You're popping up one after another...
You Straw Hats!
Soul King! It's been a while.
Your group really is made
up of such rare creatures.
I can't wait to add you to my collection.
You have good taste!
You like my iron body?! You old bag!
My name is...
...Franky!
I'm a cyborg!
I'm so rare and strong!
No, you two!
Let's run! She's an Emperor of the Sea!
An Emperor of the Sea?
So we run?
Hey, Nami. Don't you want...
...our captain...
...to become the King of the Pirates?!
Franky...
...Radical...
...Bea...
What... What are those giant things?!
Hey! You were assigned another banquet hall!
Numbers!
No!
They're as big as Oars! What are they?!
They remind me of Thriller Bark...
Are they the failed recreations
of the ancient Giants...
...that Kaido bought from Punk Hazard?!
Nice...
Here we go!
Thanks!
The weather forecast is rain!
I'm cranking it!
Fire!
I can't move.
Be careful.
Gear Three!
Bone Balloon!
Three-Sword Style...
...Secret Arts!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Bazooka!
It took all of us to finally
defeat Oars alone...
Look at that!
What that monster has in his hand is...
...Brachio Tank!
That's Usopp's team!
Let go of it!
You big mole!
Franky...
...Radical...
...Beam!
My laser beam...
...is unstoppable now!
Didn't you wanna shoot this way?
Iron man...
Lend me your arm!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
Mil Fleurs!
...Whirlpool Shoulder Throw!
Delphinium!
Damn you, Jimbei!
I remember what you did to our fleet!
I'll kill you, too!
Bring it on!
How did it go?
Better than I expected!
She'll be back angrier!
You're really a remarkable woman.
Sorry! Thanks!
Jimbei! Robin!
Mm-hm. I'm glad that you're okay!
Now...
It's the moment you've been waiting for...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Come in, Commander Chopper!
Usopp! Wake up! Usopp!
We got a call from Franky!
Hey! You guys are okay, right?!
Brachio Tank is the world's greatest...
Do you remember the promise?!
Promise?
A pirate made of iron, the Iron Pirate!
Let's combine!
Com...
...bine?
Combine!
Wait for me, Kin'emon!
Luffy seeks revenge and
heads to the battlefield
where Kaido awaits amid flying sparks!
Turning adversity into success,
the Straw Hats slice up a
whole bunch of strong enemies!
Overcoming the tidal wave of war,
the New Generation pirates will
pave the way for the future
of the Land of Wano!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Overwhelming Strength! The
Straw Hats Come Together!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!