mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Looking to fight it out against Kaido,
Luffy made a dash to get to the rooftop.
Franky! Jimbei!
They say rearguards are
the true heroes of the battlefield!
Hurry to the castle, Luffy!
Okay! I'll leave them to you!
Sanji! Let's go inside the castle!
Yeah!
On the rooftop, the battle between the Minks and Jack
continued in front of Kaido.
To stop Jack's rampage,
Dogstorm and Cat Viper finally turned into Sulongs, too.
And Queen let loose a new version of the Plague Rounds
aimed at Zoro and Drake!
Don't tell me...
...this bullet is...
"A Heroic Blade!
Akazaya vs. Kaido, Again Once More!"
I'm the best!
Hey! Stay with me!
No...
No... I've finally made it this far...
I don't wanna die here!
Help me...
Help!
What's going on?
They look like...
...ogres!
He finally used...
...the Plague Rounds!
Damn!
Hey, you!
What is this all about?!
What's in those bullets?!
If you're so curious, get shot!
As soon as that happens, you'll know!
Run! Now!
My dear son! Momonosuke!
He's here!
I'm Kozuki Oden!
Listen to your father!
Shinobu...
He looks so desperate...
Why can't we just listen to what he has to say?
Luffy said he's our ally...
Momonosuke-sama,
we're in the enemy's stronghold!
We shouldn't trust someone
who identifies himself as Oden-sama!
I'm Oden!
I wanna protect you!
Father...
--Can't we just listen to him...
--Momonosuke-sama! Don't fall for it!
He can't be Oden-sama!
I'm Oden!
You can't be Oden-sama!
But I...
...want to talk to my father again!
Take this! I'll go all out!
It took all I've got to take him down.
He was quite strong.
Bring it on!
I'll slice through you with all my strength!
One of the Lead Performers of
the Animal Kingdom Pirates...
Jack the Drought!
All the resentment and bitterness from the past...
Let's settle it once and for all...
Jack!
Duke-sama!
You should let us settle the score with him-meow!
He-gara is truly like a disaster...
We Minks will never forget!
The awful poisonous-gas-filled vision
is burned in all Minks' memories!
You don't know how many people writhed in agony
and gave way to despair!
Since I saw you-gara earlier,
my severed left arm has been tingling!
This leg that you-gara cut...
...is itching...
...to chop you up, too!
You damn little Minks...
...will be completely destroyed this time!
Don't let anyone go up!
Don't let them get in Luffy and the others' way!
Stop them all here!
Wanda! No matter how many of them we cut,
they keep coming!
We'll get run down!
Don't stop! Keep moving!
Let's keep running like this!
Carrot!
I'll fight, too!
Carrot, thank you!
Count on me! Let's stop them here!
Lick.
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm sorry, Wanda. I gotta go.
Carrot?!
I need to check something!
I got thrown this far outside...
They caught me off-guard...
Damn Jimbei!
Mama!
Oh, Perospero!
Great, Mama! I need to talk to you!
Well, you came at the right time.
Why don't you help me?
I didn't expect to see you here, Marco.
What brought you here?
I heard Whitebeard's group already fell apart.
Well, I have the same objective as your son...
Ogre extermination-yoi.
That's right, Mama!
I came to bring down Kaido!
We teamed up for that!
What did you say?!
No!
What the hell?
Perhaps, the alliance that everyone's talking about
really was formed?
So you heard about it...
That's right. We formed a pirate alliance!
No...
You've got to be kidding, Mama...
We can't ally with Kaido!
He's not trustworthy!
Perospero.
Are you second-guessing my decision?
To get the One Piece!
We can use him.
Finally!
That's enough, you fools!
Kaido!
Jack is one of our Lead Performers that I handpicked!
There's no reason for me to keep quiet
as my precious subordinate is beaten to death.
I'm... sorry...
Kaido-sama...
I know you're not weak.
It's just that they're...
...too strong!
Due to the Sulongs,
we sustained serious damage...
But you did a good job
cornering those Sulongs as much as you did.
Go get yourself treated.
You've already done enough.
INSIDE THE CASTLE
BANQUET HALL
The island is in tumult.
--Are they gonna come up here?
--I can't believe no one's here in the banquet hall!
Big Sis Maria, will you sing us a song?
All right.
How about something like this?
On the snowy night
Wait!
The two who missed each other
But they didn't get a chance
To see each other for so long
Finally seeing each other!
Under the moonlight
So romantic!
That excitement!
All right, Perospero?
I decided to form an alliance with Kaido.
Even so,
we family members have always wanted
Mama to become the King of the Pirates!
Lick!
I know that, of course.
Can't you guys trust me?
Okay... I'm relieved now.
I see.
Then, we don't share the mutual objective of
ogre extermination anymore.
Perospero.
I accepted your offer but...
Marco! I can't believe you helped those punks.
I thought you were better than that.
I guess the remnants of Whitebeard's group
don't know what to do.
Aren't you misunderstanding
the meaning of the word "remnant"?
You think Pops' voice...
...still binds us?
We who were left behind...
...are free-yoi!
Yeah, the dead can't speak...
Do as you like.
You don't seem to get it...
But I'm free to do whatever I want!
I knew it was him!
I...
...had a feeling that this would be my last journey.
What do you mean, Pedro?
One day, you'll see how important it was...
...to save Luffy and the others here
and let them set sail!
Pedro?!
Goodbye.
Pedro!!
Listen!
You-gara guys must go forward!
Pedro!
Carrot! Where are you going?!
I found Pedro's foe!
Straw Hat-san! Go ahead now!
Thanks!
There they are! Straw Hat and Black-Leg!
How annoying!
Get out of our way!
I know you'll eventually
get tired from running and die!
Can't wait to see how many you can dodge!
I did not even think about it.
Blast Breath!
Foxfire Style!
Flame-Rend!
You thought we were gonna run?
That's funny!
We're sick of running!
Sick of hiding!
Let us die as Oden-sama's samurai!
Clutching your head!
After keeping their passionate, ground-shaking
hearts beating for years
with their love for their lord Oden,
the Akazaya members come together
to save the Land of Wano.
Forged blades! Now is the time!
The legendary secret arts will finish Kaido!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Inherited Technique! Unleashing Oden's Secret Swordplay!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!