As the infection from the Plague Rounds: Ice Oni
spreads around,
Queen came up with another game.
Ice Oni...
...Tag!
Zoro! Grab that antibody from him!
Okay!
- Don't let them have it!
- Our people will die!
Don't let those samurai get well!
Wait, wait, Queen!
You're too crazy!
Start!
Meanwhile, Oden's son Momonosuke was saved by...
W-Who are you?
You identified yourself as my father...
Kozuki Oden!
Also known as...
Yamato!
I...
...can die for you!
A little before that,
Luffy made a declarative statement in front of Ulti.
Hey, you! Who the hell are you?!
I'm Luffy!
The man who'll become the King of the Pirates!
Marco! I can't believe you helped those punks.
I thought you were better than that.
I guess the remnants of Whitebeard's group
don't know what to do.
Aren't you misunderstanding
the meaning of the word "remnant," Big Mom?
You think Pops' voice...
...still binds us?
We who were left behind...
...are free-yoi!
Yeah, the dead can't speak...
Do as you like.
You don't seem to get it...
But I'm free to do whatever I want!
"Nami Surrenders?!
Ulti's Fierce Headbutt!"
Marco!
I don't know what role I'll play in this war yet...
but I know how dangerous you are
better than Straw Hat and the others!
Hey! Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Ready?!
Heavenly Fire!
Big Mom!
There's no ship bound for the new era for you to take-yoi!
Shut up!
Why am I overwhelmed by his flame?!
Prometheus!
The Phoenix's flame...
...is a rare breed-yoi!
Damn you!
How dare you!
You lowered your guard! You can't get away now!
Shoot him, Perospero!
Okay, Mama!
Lick.
Wait!
Give it to me!
Stop chasing me!
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
Two against one isn't fair!
Damn!
I'd rather help Kin'emon and the others!
Fighting you is nothing but a waste!
I've always hated you!
I hate you, too! You fool!
That asshole, Drake...
How could he do a 180 after getting caught spying!
Give me the antibody!
No, I won't!
I see...
That's Roronoa Zoro.
We better put an end to the second and third best
of the Straw Hat Crew before it's too late.
Speaking of which...
I didn't know Judge's son was their crewmember.
The king of the Kingdom of Germa,
and the evil army Germa 66's generalissimo.
Vinsmoke Judge.
His son, Sanji!
Stop, you bastards!
You hurt Pay-Pay!
Double! Quadruple! That makes it tenfold!
I'll pay you back one hundred trillion times!
Pay-Pay, I'm sorry! Let me apologize!
Don't call me Pay-Pay!
Take back what your captain said!
The next King of the Pirates is Kaido-sama!
Take it back!
- The next King of the Pirates...
- ...is our captain!
Huh? What did you say?
I couldn't hear.
Say that again!
"We're sorry for lying!"
"Our captain will never be able to
become the King of the Pirates!"
Apologize like that and take it back!
We weren't lying!
Screw you!
You guys are the ones lying!
Because the next King of the Pirates
is our captain!
He'll kick the cream cheese out of Kaido!
Prepare yourselves!
You're doing it again!
Damn you bitch!
What?! Me?!
Stop, you assholes!
Okay!
Now we can start a mission
to split their forces into two!
It's the strategy of divide and conquer!
Goodbye!
What?!
Just splitting up into two groups?!
I'm gonna teach that bitch a lesson!
I'll break that stupid long nose!
Their forces have been split, but...
Hey, stop!
This mission...
...was a mistake!
Brook!
Please stop!
Brook! Are you okay?!
Stay away from me!
I don't wanna harm my allies
like the other infected people!
If it comes to that, I'd rather...
Wait! Relax!
No, I can't relax!
We have to race against time!
No, down to the bone! Because I'm a skeleton!
There's no time for skull jokes!
I'm gonna become...
...an Ice Oni!
Brook!
Oh?
I thought I'd become an oni...
But look at me! I'm fine!
Good! You have no skin,
veins, nor body temperature,
so you're just like a corpse!
Oh, I see!
My body has always been like a cold corpse.
That's why I'm not becoming an Ice Oni
even though I was infected...
It's kind of sad!
But I'm invincible!
Wait a minute...
Brook is a skeleton, so his temperature
didn't change even when he was infected.
That's why the virus didn't multiply.
But when a normal person is infected,
their body gets cold.
That's how the virus rapidly multiplies...
That means if there's a way
to maintain their body warmth...
But...
...how can it freeze them from the inside?
This is...
Don't tell me this virus is...
Chopper! Look at your arm!
What?!
Oh, no! I didn't notice!
Chopper-san's gonna die!
ANIMAL KINGDOM BATH
Take it back!
Hey!
I'll teach her a lesson!
I'll make her take it back!
That monstrous Take-it-back Woman...
Go away! Just go away!
There you are!
You bitch... You're a pain in the ass...
Damn! What should I do?!
Say what you've got to say
before I smash your head to pieces!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
That's not it!
I said...
..."I'm sorry"!
Damn you...
I'm correcting your mistake nicely,
but you can't understand?!
If you can't understand my words,
I'll have to tell you a different way!
I'll beat it into you!
Take it back...
Rather than napping,
don't you have something to say?!
I'm a lizard buster!
Take this! Special Attack Green Star!
Platanus Shuriken!
What?! Platanus Shuriken has been fended off?!
You made fun of me
calling me a lizard again!
I'll break that ugly long nose.
How about this?!
Special Attack Green Star, Skull Blast Grass!
Can't you see that your attack doesn't work on me?!
Hey, bitch! Apologize to me!
Say you're sorry that your captain bullshitted!
What's the matter?
Your hands are shaking!
That's what happens
when you take on pirates with half-assed resolve.
Resolve to do what?!
To kill people like it's nothing?!
Is that a pirate's resolve?!
No!
The resolve to put your own life on the line!
Luffy wasn't bullshitting!
Are you sleep-talking? Are you still dreaming?
Special Attack Green Star!
Devil!
Eww, eww! So gross!
Yes, we caught her!
Dissolve her with your strong digestive juice!
It's slimy and sticky!
Help! Pay-Pay!
I'm sure you could have freed yourself!
Devil!
Pay-Pay, I love you!
- I love you so much!
- Stop! You're all slimy and gross!
D-D-Damn!
How about this?!
Bamboo Javelin!
What a boring attack.
I'm...
...not doing this for fun!
No!
Ulti-Mortar!
Again?!
Usopp...
I won't forgive...
...that lizard!
Hey, tramp!
Stop!
Don't kill me! I'm defeated!
I'm totally defeated!
Everyone can see that you're totally defeated!
Now, say it!
Say what?
I told you that I'm frustrated!
To hear your captain saying he'll take down Kaido-sama
and become the King of the Pirates!
I'm sorry!
Luffy is...
He's an idiot!
So don't headbutt me!
Please! I'll leave the island...
If you do it again, I'll...
...really die!
Then, say it!
That your captain will...
...never be able to become the King of the Pirates!
Okay...
Luffy will...
Wow!
You're really strong!
I'm a thief who steals from pirates!
The name's Nami! Hey, wanna team up with me?!
This has nothing to do with you!
I told you, leave the damn island already!
Yeah. You told me.
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course I will!!
Luffy will...
...never be able to...
That's it, Nami...
It's okay to lie...
If you don't watch your words now,
you'll end up dead!
After you've come this far!
Go ahead...
Just lie to her!
Luffy will...
...never be able to...
No, he will be!
I'm sure of it!
He will...
Because...
Because... Because...
...he will!
All right!
Die.
You idiot, Nami! Get away!
Onami-chan!
Go!
Komachiyo!
A dog?!
What?! That's...
Otama?!
What are you doing here?!
A fierce battle has erupted in the Right-Brain Tower!
The Armored Division led by Sasaki attacks Momonosuke!
Despite facing a shower of bombs,
Yamato keeps fighting alone.
His hidden strength surfaces to save the future Shogun!
He challenges the invulnerable army head-on!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sasaki's Onslaught! Armored Division vs. Yamato!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!