Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
LAW
Law...
GO
Go...
LAW
Law...
You are...
...free now...
My real name is...
...Trafalgar "D" Water Law.
Is that your secret name?
Yes.
I'm surprised.
You have the "D" in your name, too!
I told you because I trust you.
Thank you.
But I have no idea.
Although Luffy doesn't care,
I'm really...
...interested in the meaning of "D" too.
All we can do is follow the red stones?
I guess so...
In other words,
we have to defeat the Four Emperors!
But I don't think they'll give it to us that easily.
This isn't it...
I need red ones.
PEOPLE OF THE D
In some places, the People of the D have been called...
ENEMIES OF THE GODS
"Enemies of the Gods"!
Lammy!
Hey, Cora-san...
After all, I still...
...wanna know the reason I have to lead...
...this checkered life.
"Eliminate the Ice Oni!
Chopper's Fire Trick!"
I feel cold! I'm gonna become an oni!
Cry more and more!
Scream!
Amazing!
Give it to me!
Stop chasing me!
Two against one isn't fair!
What's wrong, Apoo?!
If you lose it, you'll be beheaded!
It might be better if you turn into an Ice Oni, too!
Then you can...
..."bomb" the two of them at the same time!
Damn Queen! That asshole!
Anyway, I gotta do something about this!
Chopper! Look at your arm!
What?!
Oh, no! I didn't notice!
Chopper-san's gonna die!
What can I do to minimize the symptoms
and stop the virus multiplying?!
First, I should slow
my body temperature from lowering...
Brook!
Warm me up!
What?!
Warm me up using a fire!
--That voice...
--Don't tell me...
She's coming!
Big Mom is back!
Why now of all times?!
--Is he gonna gather all the metal in the castle?!
--Damn!
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
Stop him! Don't let him get to the rooftop!
They're coming...
Then I'll greet them!
With this overwhelming amount of mass!
You don't have to get out of my way
if you wanna come with us!
Your shoulders must be stiff,
dragging around that many metal scraps.
Leave it to me! I'll make it light for you!
POKER - A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE RATTLESNAKE SMILE FRUIT
Your head is mine!
Captain Kid!
These scraps are for taking down Kaido.
All I need is an arm to bring you down!
If you can keep up with me, I'll fight you again!
Do you think this is enough, Killer?!
Our enemy is the world's strongest pirate...
The more the better.
You're right!
Crimson Cat Dance!
Canine Scourge!
Cut it out now!
I'm already sick and tired of you fools!
Everyone! It's not time to die yet!
I know!
If I can't take your head with me,
I'll be too embarrassed to face Oden-sama in the afterworld!
Since the day Oden-sama died,
we've desired nothing but vengeance!
No matter how much you beat us down,
we won't leave this world
until we can take you along with us!
Shut up!
Not yet!
Kaido!
Gah! You're so annoying!
Oden-sama...
I'm counting on you guys!
Open up the Land of Wano!
Run! To Kuri!
Don't look back!
You guys...
Kin'emon, you stay there.
We'll protect you!
Listen to them, Kin!
Dog! Cat!
Thanks to you-gara, we had a good rest!
Kin-san! Leave it to us! We're gonna...
...stop Kaido!
Kin! After we do it, you...
...attack Kaido with all you have!
You guys...
You fools are already done for!
Stop it...
Stop it!
Kiku...
Kaido!
I am going to take you down!
Don't worry! I only wanna go...
...up where Kaido is.
I gotta get to Kaido before it's too late...
That's...
The floor died down...
Hey, guys!
Don't just stand there forever!
I present...
...Ice Oni Tag!
Let's go crazy!
Excite!
That damn old bag! If she had created a mess here,
I might've been able to get away!
Damn! That asshole, Queen!
All right, Brook. Do it!
Are you sure about this?
Yeah! Do it!
If you say so...
Oh? It won't light.
Ow, ow, ow! It's burning too much!
This is...
Chopper-san, are you okay?
It's going well! Now I'm sure!
Let's go!
Chopper-san, to where?!
I know how to fight the virus!
You sure?!
Kiku...
Run, Apoo!
Don't end it yet!
This show.
Ohmasa!
Hey! Come to your senses!
There's no other option?!
No... I've finally made it this far...
I don't wanna die here!
Help me...
Help!
No! Somebody, help...
I feel cold!
Help me!
Enjoy my big game!
He's still chasing me!
Gee! How persistent he is!
Apoo!
Give me the antibody!
Drake, you bastard!
Now you're here! Back me!
What are you doing?! We gotta fight him together!
Damn you!
Like I said, two against one isn't fair!
He wants to be on his own!
Isn't that right?!
I don't know what's going on,
but I didn't expect you to be so understanding!
All right, then... Check it out!
What?!
Oh, good! You just scared me!
Screw you!
Hey! Zoro!
Yeah, Chopper.
Thanks!
Can I leave this floor to you?
I don't have time for this damn game.
You won't die, right?
Of course not!
I've already figured out how the virus works!
That's my man!
Damn Apoo! So useless!
But that's okay!
Pirates are all about fooling each other!
Everyone, listen!
Use fire against the Ice Oni!
This virus is fused with the gas that chills our bodies!
Look at me!
If you stop the chill, the virus won't multiply!
I'll make enough antibodies for everyone!
Stop Straw Hat!
What floor are we on?!
The next floor is the third floor!
The rooftop is above the fifth floor!
Okay! Kin'emon, wait for me!
That's...
Hey! Do you guys hear that?
Huh? Hear what?
I don't hear anything!
No way... That's from the third floor!
Whaddya say? Whaddya say?
Please don't!
I need it!
You shouldn't do that!
That's naughty!
Hearing a beautiful woman's voice screaming for help,
Sanji gets mad and bursts into the banquet hall!
What waits for him there is the enemy's cunning trap
and a bewitchingly gorgeous femme fatale,
Black Maria of the Tobi Roppo.
He's in trouble! Will Sanji be able to get out of it?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"It's Not Okay! The Spider lures Sanji!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!