Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
While waiting for Luffy's return,
Yamato continues to fight Kaido fiercely.
You've always tried to kill me!
Yeah, I have.
This isn't a family quarrel.
If you wanna identify yourself as Oden,
you gotta be prepared for a war.
This isn't a game!
Yamato!
Admiring someone...
...is a sin?!
I...
...love Oden!
Then, Yamato thinks back on the days
he spent with samurai in the Sacred Cave.
Eat it.
Samurai don't get hungry...
"The world is made up of four seas
and one long strip of sea.
And the world is round
like a rice cake ball.
Very strange!"
Yamato... Is your father really going to
let his child die?
At this rate, we may not be able to see the battle
that Oden said would happen in 20 years.
When that happens, I'll fight...
...alongside the Land of Wano...
I'll go out to the sea...
...to become stronger and stronger...
That's reassuring.
Then...
...by not allowing you to die here,
we'll take part in the future war.
What?
Because 20 years is...
...a little too long for us to wait.
"Luffy Soars!
Revenge Against the King of the Beasts"
Hey!
What are you doing, Momo?! Fly!
You flew earlier!
No... I... I know!
B-But...
I-I cannot move!
J-Just by raising my head...
d-do you realize how high it will be?!
I don't know, you fool!
You're full grown
but still scared of heights?!
Shut up! Do not be insolent!
W-We samurai have nothing to fear!
Then, fly! Fly now!
I cannot fly now! Maybe later...
What did you grow up for?!
You're a dragon! Fly!
I know! So stop pushing me!
I'm in a hurry!
If Kaido is running wild on Onigashima,
everyone will get beaten up!
I know!
But I'm not mentally prepared...
Stop making excuses...
Fly!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
W-Wait a minute!
Shut up!
You and I will take down Kaido together!
Thunder Bagua!
Mirror Mountain.
You defended yourself...
I'm not gonna die.
I can't die right now!
Until Luffy comes back!
I just wanna survive until that moment!
HALLOWED GLACIER SLASH
Hallowed Glacier Slash!
You look like...
...you're entirely part of the Land of Wano,
and you're challenging me...
Yamato!
You're an ogre's child!
You're Kaido's son
and you have my blood in your veins.
You can't get away from that fact!
Stop!
You're taking on something on your own,
but none of the samurai
who came here...
...think of you as an ally!
Shut up!
That has nothing to do...
...with how I feel!
You don't have any friends!
You've been living
on this island all alone.
Running around the island,
crawling about ceilings.
You've been alone all your life!
I have...
...friends!
Even though handcuffs were unavoidable,
if you hate your father so much,
why are you letting them chain your heart?!
I made this!
This is your Vivre Card!
Is this it?
It's just a piece of paper.
That's right! This piece of paper
will bring us together again!
Bring us together?
I have a precious friend!
No...
I had!
You did. Like those samurai...
We'll leave the Land of Wano to you.
All the people who were good to you
are dead!
No wonder it's so cold.
It's snowing...
I'm hungry...
There you are, Ogre Princess-sama.
Please wait, Ogre Princess-sama.
You must be hungry.
Here you go.
Before someone notices,
help yourself!
Thank you!
I appreciate it!
Yum...
So delicious...
Thank you...
That's good, Ogre Princess-sama.
Hey, why did he get executed
all of a sudden?
I heard he was secretly delivering food
to Ogre Princess-sama.
He even got her a blanket
thinking she was freezing!
Oh, how kind of him!
Ogre Princess-sama is still on the run
saying she wants to become Oden?
They didn't just die. You killed them!
They got in the way of
me educating my child.
They deserved it!
You should know better by now!
Yamato!
You don't have any friends!
Even if you think those people
from the Land of Wano are your allies,
the relationship is superficial!
They'll all be afraid of you!
You must rule over people by force!
Because you're an ogre's child!
You can't become friendly with humans!
That's your fate!
Yamato!
Fly!
Momo!
Fly now! Right away! Just fly!
This is why you grew up, right?!
Are you gonna let it go to waste?!
Kin'emon.
Show some guts!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Do not pull them!
I wanna kick Kaido's ass already!
Wait, wait, wait... Wait a minute!
You are hurting me!
My whiskers are gonna come off!
My whiskers!
I am flying!
Alright! You're doing great, Momo!
Fly to Onigashima!
Let's proceed on!
Go!
Momo!
Forward! Forward!
Advance at top speed!
So fast!
Only dragons can fly like this!
We can catch up to it soon like this!
We're off-course! Go left!
Momo! More to the left!
Left?!
Um...
Like this?!
That's it! Good!
All right! Onigashima!
We caught up to it!
Land, Momo!
L-Land?!
I see a shadow on the rooftop!
I think that's Kaido!
Go to the rooftop!
Rooftop?
I got it!
No, no! Not upward!
Downward!
Downward?!
Hey! No! No, no!
Not that way!
Are you keeping your eyes open?!
Idiot! How can I fly with my eyes open?!
What?!
I can do it! Count on me!
No!
This isn't the rooftop!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR, SKULL DOME
Three-Sword Style.
What's that?!
A dragon?!
What?! Kaido-san?!
No! That's not him!
Huh?! Another dragon?!
What? Luffy?!
Stop! Stop, stop!
Luffy?!
That's Luffy!
Luffy!
I'm glad that he's okay!
What?! What?! What?!
Stop, Momo! What are you doing?!
Where am I?!
Trafalgar!
I don't know. I guess
some monster is running wild downstairs!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Why don't you
worry about yourselves instead?
A dragon?! Is that Kaido?!
Straw Hat-ya?!
What the hell?!
What's going on?!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Enough!
Open your eyes, Momo!
I can't!
And besides, something got into them, too!
That's because you crashed into things!
Do something, Luffy!
Guts!
Show some guts and look ahead!
A wall! Stop!
What?!
This is the third floor inside the castle!
We have Kaido-sama rampaging...
No! That's not him!
What?! But I don't think
there are two dragons!
The color's different!
Find out who the pink dragon is!
It's noisy down there.
Is it Linlin?
We'll have to rebuild the castle.
I can't let it...
...end like this!
Divine Swiftness!
Alright!
There he is!
On the rooftop!
Are we there?!
Oh, gee!
We are in the air!
Let's go somewhere we can land quickly!
I found Kaido!
Dive down there!
Kaido?!
Gear Four!
Snake-Man!
Gum-Gum...
Divine Swiftness!
White Serpent!
Jet Culverin!
Bidding farewell to his weak self
and setting his heart in the face of a burning flame!
Momonosuke transformed into the same beast
as the enemy who killed his father and mother.
With the sorrow of being forced
to flee his country in his heart,
he now bares the fangs of rage
after 20 years have passed.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Two Dragons Face Off! Momonosuke's Determination!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!