Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy was trying to get back to Onigashima
with Momonosuke. However...
Hey!
What are you doing, Momo?! Fly!
You flew earlier!
No... I... I know!
B-But...
Meanwhile, Yamato is making frantic efforts
and standing up to Kaido all alone.
I have a precious friend!
No...
I had!
You did. Like those samurai...
All the people who were good to you
are dead!
Show some guts!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Do not pull them!
I am flying!
Gear Four!
Snake-Man!
"Two Dragons Face Off!
Momonosuke's Determination!"
Gum-Gum...
Divine Swiftness!
White Serpent!
Jet Culverin!
What?!
Luffy!
Oh, Yamao!
You're the one who held Kaido back!
That's so helpful! Thanks!
I'm relieved! I've been waiting for you!
Sorry! I was late because I needed to eat!
I'll do the rest!
I finally made it
to a place to stand on...
Um... You're...
A pink dragon!
Oh?
Don't tell me...!
How could you possibly survive?
Straw Hat!
I couldn't possibly die!
I'm the one who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
Don't be so cocky.
The One Piece is mine!
Who is that dragon?
Did you save Straw Hat?
Give me your name!
I'm a kind man and I'm asking you.
I-I...
I'm asking who you are...
...and where you're from!
I'm gonna fall!
It's too high! I'm scared...
I'm gonna die!
Your father was a silly lord.
My...
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
I am the one who will become
the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
FLOWER CAPITAL, LAND OF WANO
Fluffy!
Having a good time, Otoko?
Uh-huh!
Here, Daddy!
I think Daddy wants to eat it, too.
Because he's watching over us up in heaven
where the flame is rising towards, right?
Daddy!
Yeah...
I'm sure he is...
Why should a little child
have to go through such a terrible thing?
Otama...
Where are you going, Otama?!
Do you realize how dangerous
what you're doing is?!
Forgive me, Master-sama!
I can't help but do something!
Don't worry!
We'll protect her with our lives!
So please understand her feelings!
No! Come back!
It's too dangerous for a child like you!
Even so,
I wanna fight along with the others
at Onigashima!
Otama!
Is she okay?
She's across the sea...
There's no way to find out...
Let me inform you
about a mysterious dragon!
Currently on the rooftop, there is
just the wounded Young Master Yamato.
So it was Yamato
who was stopping Kaido-san.
And up in the air,
something unbelievable is happening...
Two dragons squaring off!
Facing Kaido-sama, the Azure Dragon...
...is a pink dragon!
And on its back...
...is Straw Hat Luffy!
The pink dragon's identity is unknown!
But there is no doubt it's our enemy!
Victory in this decisive battle...
...will be the only way to honor
our wounded and fallen comrades!
I'll make you pay the price
for Pedro's death!
Dragons bring thunderclouds.
And there are two dragons here...
No more moon tonight.
If I had taken one more strike,
I might not have been able to stand up.
The Sulong transformation is a double-edged sword
that will drain your energy.
So you're finished, not me.
He changed back!
Master Cat Viper!
Hold it! Don't get in my way!
Don't blame the moon.
It's not like you're unlucky!
Lick!
It's just that I'm luckier!
Boss cat!
Master!
Momonosuke-kun!
You look like...
...my father!
If I could turn into a monster like he does,
I would be of some help to everyone...
Momonosuke-kun!
How surprising. You're that brat!
But...
...this world isn't big enough
for two dragons!
It is a breath of fire!
Okay! Breathe something, too!
Breathe what?! I can't!
Guts! Guts! Go, Momo!
Guts have nothing to do with it!
Momo! You can breathe it!
People cannot breathe fire!
Blast Breath!
N-No! I am not here to fight!
I...
Hey, Momo!
Bite Kaido!
What?!
Gear Three!
Wait, Luffy! I can't! I can't!
I can't do that!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
Hey, Momo!
Bite Kaido!
I can't!
Mother!
Don't worry!
I'll make sure you two escape!
There is a way out of this!
Mother!
Your father was a silly lord.
What's your name?!
Say it!
Mo...
Father!
Kaido!
What are you doing, you brat?!
You're only a puppet...
Don't butt in!
I am not anyone's puppet!
I...
I can't forgive you!
You messed up the Land of Wano!
If it weren't for you...
Father would...
Mother would...
Kaido!!
I asked what you are doing!
Get away, Momonosuke-kun!
Blast Breath!
That's it, Momo!
What?! Momonosuke-sama?!
Momonosuke-sama became a dragon?
A pink (momo) one?!
That's our Momonosuke-sama!
You bit Kaido!
Is that Luffy?
How dare he make us worried!
Right! He always makes us nervous!
Big Bro... He's okay!
I'm so glad!
He finally came back!
Robin-san! Are you hearing this?!
It's Luffy-san!
I was waiting for you, Luffy!
Hearing his voice
makes me feel energized...
Sounds like he's in good shape!
You bit an Emperor of the Sea!
Is there anything left in the world
that can scare you?!
N...
No!
Momonosuke has sunk his fangs into Kaido
who tries to control everything by force.
The blood and tears that have been shed are woven
into a ray of hope which is entrusted to Luffy!
The clash for the fate of the Land of Wano
once again shakes the era!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Legend All Over Again! Luffy's Fist Roars in the Sky"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!