iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Yamato is running
to stop the explosion of Onigashima.
Shoot, shoot!
I repeat!
From the second floor to all floors!
The flame specter that's heading down
to the basement continues to descend!
That's not good!
CURRENT LOCATION / ARMORY
If it keeps descending,
it'll reach the armory!
If that happens...
it'll light up the stockpiled explosives...
To save the Flower Capital,
Momonosuke keeps making all-out efforts, too.
I can do it! I know I can!
Just like Luffy! Just like Luffy, I...
Zoro continues to fight fiercely
against King.
Imperial Deep Pride... Stake!
Enma! Not now!
I've never seen a swordsman
who is held back by his sword!
Kitetsu III!
That was hot!
Oh, good. It didn't fall off.
Wado Ichimonji.
How did a sword of the Land of Wano...
...end up in a remote region
in the East Blue?
"The Secret of Enma!
The Cursed Sword Entrusted to Zoro"
You got all of your three swords now?!
Imperial Slings and Arrows!
Enma!
Enma...
A sword from the Land of Wano...
A sword from the Land of Wano!
Zorojuro.
The word "Sunacchi"...
I was told not to say it.
I just learned it from an old man
of the village a long time ago,
but I've never said it even once.
What?!
An old man of the village?!
That old man
who was always on the sea coast...
I didn't know his name...
...for so long...
That white sword Wado Ichimonji
and Enma...
...were crafted by the same person!
The legendary swordsmith,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo.
EAST BLUE, 13 YEARS AGO
ISSHIN DOJO
Not there!
Go, go!
SHIMOTSUKI VILLAGE (ZORO'S HOMETOWN)
That's the spirit, Zoro!
Yes!
Sunacchi!
It's a good-luck word
to uplift your spirit!
Hmmm... I have no use for it.
What a weird word.
Anyway, old man,
were you a samurai?
Everyone at the dojo said so.
Silence their gossip.
The Navy will come invade soon.
OLD MAN OF THE VILLAGE
The Navy?! Why?!
I won't tell you!
Go home, you shitty brat!
What's your problem, you nasty old man?!
Is the dojo too boring?
I was beaten by Kuina again!
I have to practice more!
What?!
But I don't have any money!
You can have them.
They're blunt though.
I...
...can only forge swords like them now.
Use them for practice.
Listen. Swords are tools used to cut people.
They're made to kill people!
Swordsmiths try to craft them
as deadly as possible!
Every sword has a personality,
and it's a swordsman's job to tame them!
They call a dangerous sword
a "cursed sword"?!
Ridiculous! That's a fine sword!
If the weak fear it and call it cursed,
it's...
...an honor!
Swords are fearsome!
Because they yearn so deeply to be deadly!
The one I made when I was young...
...was the greatest piece
that I crafted in my life...
The sword was very serious!
To that fine sword
which gives you chills just by holding it...
I gave the name of the great king of hell!
The great king... of hell...
"Enma"!
I will not concede!
Wait! Stop!
Not so fast!
Th-These are Kaido's!
I see! Because I'm a dragon too,
I can grab them!
Even if I can't push it back...
If I can at least stop it...
If I can change its direction!
If I don't do it, who will?!
Who?!
I will save the Land of Wano!
I will not let it fall on the Flower Capital!
A big target is easy to hit.
Don't push your luck!
Catch me if you can!
Take this!
Check it out! Slash!
So weak.
Let me say it one more time.
Such an inconvenience must be erased.
Let's hurry up.
When did they get here?
Hey, hey, hey!
So persistent...
Yo, yo! You Government's pets!
I'll discipline myself a bit
and bite on my lip!
And I'll show you a thing or two!
Check it out!
The tide has turned!
The name of the village is Shimotsuki...
I guess it wasn't a coincidence...
On the day that old man died,
I learned...
...that he was Kuina's grandfather.
Catch me if you want
this Excellent Grade Sword back!
That's just a bamboo sword!
Give it back to me!
Hey, guys! Did you know this?!
My grandma said this village
was founded by a pirate!
What?!
A pirate...
The legendary swordsmith,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo.
More than half a century ago,
he illegally departed from this country.
That old man was a samurai
from the Land of Wano?!
The swordsmith, Shimotsuki Kozaburo!
Fine swords watch humans closely.
They choose the swordsman for themselves!
They say the sword chooses the owner.
I will give you a replacement!
A sword that was handed down to me
from my late father...
Enma the famed blade!
You came to me...
Because you chose me
and you wanted to test me...
Wado... Ichimonji...
You ready?!
Yeah!
My...
...2001st win.
Th...
This sucks...
I'm the one...
...who should be frustrated...
What?
You see, when girls grow up,
they get weaker than men...
You're always saying you're going to be
the world's strongest swordsman.
My dad told me a girl can never be...
...the strongest...
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
I want to be the world's greatest, too!
My breasts have even
started to grow out now...
If only I had been born a man...!
Don't be whining like that
after you beat me!
That's not fair! You're my goal!
Boy this, girl that!
Are you gonna say that stuff too
when I beat you someday?!
You act like none of it is skill!
You're insulting
all the hard training I've been doing!
So don't say that stuff!
Promise me!
Someday, one of us will
be the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll compete to see who gets there!
You dummy.
You're so weak...
It's a promise!
Kuina...
...is dead...
Damn it...
You just made a promise to me yesterday!
You can't run away, Kuina!
Sensei...
Let me have... her sword...
Yes. You can have it.
I'm going to get stronger for her, too!
I'm going to get strong enough
that my name reaches to heaven!
I'm going to be
the world's strongest swordsman!
Swords are guileless...
It's not doing this with malice...
That's absolutely right...
Then, it's my power that's lacking!
Could it be that
Oden was fighting with ease...
...even though you took away
so much of his Haki?!
Wasn't he, Enma?
There he is! Pirate Hunter Zoro!
He's all cut up!
King-san!
Let us take his head!
Give us a chance!
If we beat him, we'll get promoted!
Me! I'll do it!
What should I do...
...to control my Haki?
I'll die if I keep releasing
this much Haki...
No...
That's fine!
I see...
Are you trying to be a king?
If we fight the Navy together now,
you'll be a Government-defying villain!
Would you prefer that,
or being killed like this?
What are you, the devil's son?!
Well, whatever.
I'll be your pirate,
if I'm just gonna die here instead!
But look, I have an ambition!
To be the world's greatest swordsman!
At this point, honor doesn't matter!
Whether it's as a criminal or whatever else,
I will spread my name throughout the world!
Since you asked me to join your crew,
if I wind up having to give my ambition up,
you'd better slit your belly
and apologize to me!
That sounds great!
The world's greatest swordsman?
The King of the Pirates would need
no less than that on his crew!
Well...
I have made...
...a promise to...
...my captain and best friend!
A cyborg that provokes!
Queen's attacks remind Sanji of Germa.
Is a ruthless heart the way to victory?
As he questions himself about the fate
he thought he had broken free of,
an unknown blue flame flares up
in his nearly frozen soul!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Strike of an Ifrit! Sanji vs. Queen"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!