iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Ifrit Jambe!
Men should never hit women!
That's been common sense
since the age of dinosaurs!
You scum! Collier!
Basses Cote!
Paleron!
Jumeau a Bifteck!
Tendron! Flanchet!
Queue! Poire! Jarret!
Boeuf Burst!
Fly away, you asshole!
Thus, Sanji defeated Queen.
Meanwhile, at the Right-Brain Tower
inside the dome...
I see...
Are you trying to be a king?
Well...
I have made...
...a promise to...
...my captain and best friend!
"The Three-Sword Style of the Supreme King!
Zoro vs. King"
A promise, huh?
But as long as...
...Kaido-san and I are around...
...that promise will never be fulfilled.
Along with that sword called Enma,
I'll send you to hell!
Nice try.
I'm sorry. My constitution is unusual.
Your sword attacks won't work against me.
You're that weak,
but you wanna be a king?!
I'm slashing him!
But it's not affecting him at all!
Won't let you flee!
Think!
It's not like he's unbreakable!
There must be a reason!
Face your defeat and die!
Three-Sword Style!
Ultra Tiger Hunt!
Hey!
I thought so...
When the flames on his back go out,
he gets faster...
But his defense gets weaker!
King-sama's mask...
So the rumor was true!
Black wings, white hair, and brown skin...
You'll get 100 million berries for
informing the Government. He's the rare...
N-No, I mean...
Imperial Flaming Wings!
The castle's already on fire.
If you're a boss,
be nice to your subordinates and stay cool.
If you can't focus, come out here.
100 million for informing the Government?
What tribe are you from?
Why ask when you're going to die soon?!
He's definitely from
a particular kind of tribe,
but that's none of my business!
I don't have much time...
If this takes too long,
my sword may take my life.
I see now the danger you pose.
Same to you.
You guys have reigned long enough.
It's time to go, you fools!
Don't push your luck!
Kaido-san is destined
to become the King of the Pirates!
I'm sorry but he won't.
King of Hell...
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
...Oni Giri!
Are you trying to be a king?
I have made...
...a promise to...
...my captain and best friend!
King of Hell...
Three-Sword Style!
This life was given to me by you.
Kaido-san.
This is Punk Hazard!
A guinea pig has gone out of control!
The restraints were removed by force!
Come in! Come in!
Stop! Go away!
Let us out!
What have we done to you?!
This is stupid!
I will burn you all up!
Who are you?!
Me? I'm a pirate.
I see why the Government
can't let you go.
You're a Lunarian, huh?
I saw the durability test earlier.
I'm impressed that you withstood
that raging fire...
You're impressed because
I'm a member of the legendary tribe?!
Are you gonna do the same to me
as they did?!
I'm gonna get out of here
and form a new pirate group.
What do you wanna do, guinea pig?
Make the not-so-fascinating world
fascinating!
Choose! I'll let you decide!
Can you change...
...the world?!
Only I can change it!
We found the escaped guinea pigs!
Stop them at any cost!
I'm gonna blow their heads off!
There aren't many pursuers.
Yeah. You're right.
Shoot!
Guns can't take them down!
That's quite something!
It's nothing.
Oh, I haven't asked you!
What's your name?
Alber.
Alber! You're strong!
Call yourself King hereafter!
King.
Stay behind me, King!
I won't sell you out!
You're my right-hand man from now on!
The world only needs one king!
The flames are burning!
It's useless to attack now!
Take this, Roronoa!
Imperial Flaming Wings!
These flames are like magma!
That thing again!
I won't let you take these fine swords!
He's moving fast! That means...
...I can cut him!
Bird Dance!
Seems like you figured out...
...the mechanics of my strength!
Yeah, I did!
Now you finally see your defeat!
Ultra...
...Tiger Hunt!
Why are you trying to block?!
I thought it wouldn't harm you!
Or are you scared of my attack?!
You're biologically incapable of
defeating me!
I dislike making excuses like that
more than anything!
I'll remember you as a ballsy swordsman!
I'll carve it into your memory for you!
Though I don't know if you can survive!
Imperial Flaming Wings!
King of Hell, Three-Sword Serpent!
103 Mercies!
This is it, Roronoa!
Dragon Damnation!
Extra Large Imperial Flaming Wings!
K-Kaido-san...
You still think so, King?!
That I'm Joyboy?
The world I'm looking to create
is the world you want?
A legend is a legend.
I don't wish for anything anymore.
My life was given to me by you.
You must remain the strongest!
I won't lose, either...
I'll make you the King of the Pirates!
You need no less than
the world's greatest swordsman, right?
Until the day I defeat him
and become a master swordsman...
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that,
King of the Pirates?!
Nope!
I shall become...
...the king of hell!
The battle of the Right-Brain Tower
outside the Skull Dome.
The winner...
...is Zoro!
Usopp, who maintains his determination to survive,
even if it is unsightly.
The samurai, who believe in the Straw Hats
and are determined to live on.
The time is near for the bullets of their souls
to break the old wall that stands in the way
of their unwavering spirits' anticipation for the future!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy is on the Move! A Turning Point to a New Era!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!