iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Zoro and King's battle
grows increasingly intense.
King of Hell...
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
...Oni Giri!
Take this, Roronoa!
Imperial Flaming Wings!
I won't let you take these fine swords!
You're biologically incapable of
defeating me!
I dislike making excuses like that
more than anything!
And it finally comes to an end!
Imperial Flaming Wings!
King of Hell, Three-Sword Serpent!
103 Mercies!
Dragon Damnation!
K-Kaido-san...
I shall become...
...the king of hell!
"Luffy is on the Move!
A Turning Point to a New Era!"
King's just been defeated!
What?! Are you sure?!
Yes, he has been taken down
by Zoro, the swordsman of the Straw Hats.
All the Lead Performers
and the Tobi Roppo members have lost...
This is serious.
Of course,
there are still two monsters
who can jeopardize the Straw Hats' efforts...
Blast Breath!
...left out there...
Cognac, Mama-mash!
This time for sure, playtime is over.
From now on,
it's either you kill me or I kill you...
There's no other outcome!
Though it's obvious which...
I agree!
We'll kill you, of course!
Bring it on,
shitheads of the Worst Generation!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
The battle between Luffy and Kaido
is getting extremely intense...
However, there is another side
to this decisive battle!
Luffy's victory over Kaido will dissipate...
EXPLOSIVES
FLAME CLOUDS
...the Flame Clouds.
Onigashima will crash,
and the explosives in the basement
will cause the Flower Capital to explode!
Tens of thousands of people...
...enjoying the Fire Festival
totally unawares will die!
I won't let it reach the Flower Capital
no matter what!
Into the abyss...
And then, there's another crisis.
BURNING GRUDGE
Kanjuro's burning grudge
which Orochi masterminded...
...is heading towards the basement
to make Onigashima explode in midair.
And Yamato is pursuing it!
I knew he'd be here!
SIX
DOORS TO
THE BASEMENT ARMORY
Rokki is blocking the doors
to the basement!
I don't have time to take him down,
get the key
and pull the lever to open the doors!
I'll leave it to you, Fuga!
Yay!
Thanks, Fuga!
Keep Rokki busy!
"Arrival"! That means we've reached
the location you specified!
Thanks!
Kin'emon's upper body
must be up there!
Wait here, Hamlet!
Where are you?! Kin'emon!
Oh, gee... We gotta get out of here
before the whole space burns down!
Kin'emon!
Answer me if you're there!
Th-That voice... Is it Usopp-dono?!
Hey! Are you near?!
There he is!
A-Are you okay?!
I-Instead of me...
Take care of Kiku...
What?!
She's wounded so badly...
My body is back together...
H-How does your body even work?!
This is because of Law-dono's technique,
I do not understand either...
Anyway, both of you must let
Chopper treat you as soon as possible!
There they are!
The Straw Hats! Don't let them flee!
--Let's go!
--Take them down!
Why the hell are those fools
coming here now?!
Skull Bomb-Grass!
Look! He has a bounty of 200 million!
Don't let him walk away alive!
It's over! I'm gonna die!
I'm surrounded by flames and enemies!
U-Usopp-dono...
Forget about me... Please help Kiku...
No, Kin-sama...
I'm not going to make it...
Okay! I'm gonna leave you two
and get out of here alone!
Then why did I bother coming here?!
You damn suicidal samurai!
Dying with honor?!
Slicing your belly to take responsibility?!
I don't like your culture!
I'll hold on to life with snot dripping!
Even if it's unsightly, I'll live!
Shut up!
Usoland doesn't lie!
The hero would never lie to us!
My name is Usopp!
I'm gonna become your legendary hero now!
And live!
Everything... went as planned!
STOP MO"VI"NG ME,
Vi...
I SAI"D"
D...
Captain Usopp!!
And I lived through,
that's why I'm alive now!
Usopp-dono!
Don't be satisfied
just by making a raid, you fools!
I can't! I can't! I can't!
He's right!
Duck!
Hey, why is he here?!
The former commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates?!
That's Izo!
Marco was on the Performance Floor, too...
What's going on?!
Who are you?! Thank you!
Izo...
Kin'emon!
I was with her,
but I could not prevent it... I am sorry...
Kiku!
Big Bro... I...
Don't talk. It's bad for your wounds.
We can catch up as much as we want
after the battle.
But...
...I don't think I can...
As your brother,
I won't allow you to give up.
Okay?
Yes.
I'll get you guys out of here at any cost!
So...
...live!
If you guys really believe in
Straw Hat Luffy!
Yes!
Mm-hm.
You too, Big Bro... You must...
...live...
God Usopp!
What?! You know me?!
Of course I do!
You're the king of sniping!
Blush!
--Take those two!
--Count on me!
Hamlet!
--Yes!
--Let's go!
"Departure"! That means
we're setting out on a new journey!
I won't let you flee!
No one passes through here!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Paralysis Jutsu!
It's over! You caught fire first!
Undo the Paralysis Jutsu! Raizo!
You undo it first, Fukurokuju!
Okay. So be it!
You're unlucky.
Your death will undo the jutsu on me!
I'm Oden-sama's retainer!
I don't even find this little flame hot!
SECOND FLOOR
INSIDE THE TREASURE REPOSITORY
Is this a dream or reality?
I can't believe Komurasaki
who I thought was dead...
...is playing shamisen beside me.
All the nuisances will be wiped out
in this battle.
Then Komurasaki and I will get married
and live here in the Land of Wano!
What's taking you so long, Fukurokuju?!
We gotta get out of here
before this island explodes!
Lord, what is wrong?
Oh no... Nothing...
Oh yeah, Komurasaki!
Play that piece for me!
That piece I love
that you used to play for me!
Yes, of course!
SECOND BASEMENT FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Drake!
Let's get out of here, Inbi!
We don't need to confront those monsters!
Sorry, Zanki! Bye, Drake!
That was a pain...
They're quite strong.
Apoo ran away...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Have you caught Nico Robin?
Not yet. We got interrupted.
Hurry up.
We've got to get out of this castle.
All the Lead Performers are defeated!
No way!
If by any chance
the "Worst Generation" wins,
it will be quite a story.
And that will become a tailwind
for what is happening...
...around the world right now.
What's going to happen in the next few minutes
will set the course for the times to come!
That's true, but...
...isn't this...
...the farthest humankind can go?
Gum-Gum...
Gear Three!
I'm sick of hearing Gum-Gum!
Roc Gun!
It's getting fun!
I feel the same!
An annoying, living disaster of a mean drunk!
Kaido, a little bothered
but excited by the emergence of a youngster
who he can fight against with all his might,
drinks celebratory sake.
He denigrates the new-generation fighter by
gleefully barraging him with
complaints and a spiked club!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Drunken Dragon Bagua!
The Lawless Dragon Closing in on Luffy"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!