Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
I was sure that you had died.
Me, too!
Since the Gum power is affecting
things other than your own body...
I guess we can assume
your Paramythia has awakened.
But it's a little strange.
That kind of transformation...
...is an exclusive feature of Zoan type!
Luffy obtains a new power
and challenges Kaido again!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant!
They both exceeded their limits,
but the deadly battle continues!
What's wrong with him?!
Turning himself white,
and using both Color of Arms and
Color of the Supreme King,
he's fighting so freely
affecting things other than his own body.
I've never seen something like this!
This is fun, isn't it?!
Kaido!
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Who am I?
Monkey D. Luffy!
I'll surpass you,
and become the King of the Pirates!
"No Way Out!
A Hellish Scene on Onigashima"
The King of the Pirates?!
It's good to know that
you're still impudent, Straw Hat!
When your mind and body
catch up to your power, Awakening occurs!
How ridiculous your power is!
Go!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant!
I've already lost so much...
I've lost so much of what I've built.
Boeuf Burst!
Fly away, you asshole!
King of Hell, Three-Sword Serpent!
This is it, Roronoa!
103 Mercies!
Dragon Damnation!
Extra Large Imperial Flaming Wings!
My subordinates and the castle!
You've lost a lot, too.
Even so, there are things
I have to take back!
You'll lose more and more!
Because I will take more from you!
Kundali Dragon Swarm!
Screw you!
How's that?!
The floors and the castle
are all on fire below.
I'm sure thousands of your soldiers
are stuck there, too.
They'll all burn to death!
Don't underestimate them, Kaido!
I left everything below in their hands!
So I'll just...
...focus on kicking your ass!
The way you laugh annoys me!
Demolition Gust!
It almost hit my crotch!
I have an idea!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR INSIDE THE DOME
It's not just the castle anymore!
All the towers are burning!
Everyone!
Where are you?!
Hey!
Chopper!
Nami!
Are you alright?!
Otama, are you hurt?
Everyone protected me,
so I was only slightly wounded.
I'll treat your wounds later.
What about the others?
What should we do?
The fire can't be put out!
Zoro, Sanji, Franky, Brook,
Usopp, Robin, and Jimbei!
I can't find any of them!
Maybe they're in the fire!
Really?!
But...
...even if we tried to find them,
the whole of Onigashima is on fire now!
It's not safe here, either!
Unless it lands, we have nowhere to go!
Zeus, can't you use your rain
to put out the fire?
The fire is too intense,
I would get burned!
We all worked so hard
to get to this point.
It's so frustrating
to see it end like this.
--Don't worry!
--What?
It's gonna be all right,
so don't give up!
You're right!
We have to see Big Bro Luffy win!
BASEMENT INSIDE THE CASTLE
We can't escape! The fire's everywhere!
There's nowhere to run!
Damn!
I can't take it anymore!
I can't stand the heat...
FIRST FLOOR
You're giving us too much trouble, Bepo!
Ouch!
Maybe this really is it.
I don't think we can get out of here!
Help! Captain!
BASEMENT
My precious afro is getting frizzier!
--Yeah! I don't want to end up like you.
--What?
--What?!
--Huh?!
A skeleton!
I know you're frustrated!
Look at you!
I don't know what to say...
I feel sorry for you... You must have
failed to escape and got burned!
I'm not a burnt corpse!
I am dead though...
It's burning intensely!
Maybe there's no way for all of us...
...to run.
FOURTH FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
I'm sorry. I can't die just yet...
Don't mention it.
I like helping people.
I was extremely lucky to see you here.
I'm in on your secret plan with pleasure!
With my ninjutsu,
now is the time to salvage this situation!
Now is the time!
Everyone, endure it a little bit more...
These loathsome flames...
I'm going to put them all out!
PLEASURE HALL, LEFT-BRAIN TOWER
Oh, no. We can't get outside
because the yard is gone.
No...
An abyss in front...
And a hellish fire behind...
We can't even turn back!
Careful!
Don't worry! I'll protect you ladies!
Thank you.
We're in the air,
so there's no place to go...
The fire and the collapse
and the ladies...
What should we do?
BASEMENT
Stop complaining that it's hot!
Break the wall!
If we stay here, we're gonna die!
Just sacrifice one of your damn arms!
That big body's so useless, you idiot!
Do you wanna fight, you bastard?!
BASEMENT
The heat and the flames
have us backed in a corner!
Is there a way for us to survive?!
If we knew that,
we wouldn't be having a hard time!
We're gonna die from the heat
if nothing's done!
Just run!
Please do something, mister!
I'm gonna put out this fire!
Special Attack Green Star!
Sprinkler!
How's that?!
This is what
"a drop in the bucket" means, mister!
Shut up! I gotta figure out a way!
I promised Izo!
I wanna save Kin and Kiku,
and myself as well!
What?!
Mister! Please include me in that list!
Don't depend on me!
You have to save me!
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER
The castle is burning ridiculously!
Wait for us, Big Bro!
Where should we go?!
Zoro's life is in danger!
I have to take him to Chopper
as soon as possible!
We're all gonna get burned to death
before that!
It's hot! It's hot! I don't wanna die!
Help us, Big Bro!
Who's whining?!
I'm gonna burn you!
Please don't do that!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
It's a dead end again! Damn!
The flames and the debris
keep getting the way!
Did someone go around
and set fires?!
There is no way I'm gonna be killed
by fire and not by the enemy in a raid!
What kind of a fight is this?!
We're not gonna get defeated by fire!
Yeah! Let's survive!
Yeah!
FOURTH FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
I'm ready, Jimbei-dono!
Thank you for trusting me!
Luffy chose to form an alliance
with you samurai!
There's no way I'd doubt you.
Okay, come on!
Yeah! I'm trusting you, too!
I was ready since that day...
Toki-sama!
Momonosuke-sama!
Hiyori-sama!
Come on! Hurry up!
I couldn't save Oden-sama that day!
And I let Momonosuke-sama and the others
suffer in the burning castle.
Even if I could use ninjutsu,
I couldn't save anybody.
That was a big blunder that I regret!
I never ever want...
...to feel that way again!
Zou?!
Dogstorm, what kind of rain is this?!
Zunesha is bathing itself.
That's a lot of water! May I take some?!
I won't let
those who took part in this raid die...
...in this damn fire!
I'm sorry that it took so long, everyone!
Let me show you the incredible water flow!
Ninpo: Scrolling Jutsu!
The Elephant's Bath!
Restoration!
This is enormous!
Water Heart!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Run through every part of the castle!
Make it in time and save everyone,
Zou's water!
FIRST FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Let me down, guys!
You have to let us do this for you
at least, Killer-san!
Ouch!
What should we do?!
There really is nowhere to go!
What is that?!
I feel a rumble...
Water?!
We're okay now!
Hurry up, Momonosuke-kun!
Why?! Kaido is still alive!
You have to sustain the island
with your Flame Clouds!
Sustain the island? That's impossible!
Kaido is reaching his limit...
His Flame Clouds won't last much longer!
What?
You must create Flame Clouds
to sustain Onigashima!
What?!
That was the only option
from the beginning!
Otherwise, Onigashima will fall!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
I, Bartolomeo, will tell you all about
the bravery of Luffy-senpai
who is in a fierce battle
against the Emperor of the Sea Kaido!
You'll get to see so much of
Big Bro Luffy's heroic actions!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy-senpai Support Project!
Barto's Secret Room 3!"
Luffy-senpai's gonna become
the King of the Pirates!