yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
With weakness as my ally
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
I soar higher than anybody else
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
At times when you're lost somewhere
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
If my heart is also adrift
mitsukete agerarenainda
I won't be able to find you
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
Your kindness, nor your strength
wakatterunda
I already know
yoake no toki sa
It's the break of dawn
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
To the highest point of reach
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
mahi shite waratterundarou
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
With the world as my enemy
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
I stand my ground on quivering legs
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
HOLE MADE BY KAIDO
HOLE MADE BY BIG MOM
The battle on the rooftop of the Skull Dome,
Onigashima above the Land of Wano.
The declared winner was Kaido,
but the results have been revised...
Luffy!
Whoa...
"The Curtain Falls!
The Winner, Straw Hat Luffy!"
Good job, Momonosuke-kun.
Your efforts and Flame Clouds
saved everyone!
You guys are amazing, truly unbelievable!
I'm really happy!
The lives of all of us
and the people of the capital...
I can't believe he saved them all.
That's our great Shogun-meow!
It's been so long-meow.
Sky Boats of the Fire Festival!
Oops.
It's no mistake, you-gara guys!
Kaido has been sunk deep into the ground
by Luffy!
Onigashima's plummet was stopped
by Momonosuke-sama in his giant dragon form!
Isn't that right?!
Right!
So that pink dragon was Momonosuke-sama?!
A Devil Fruit power user?
It's been 20 years since that day...
This vengeance-filled battle
that started when Oden-sama died...
We finally won!
We took down the two Emperors of the Sea!
I didn't think I'd make it out alive!
Purr-meow-meow-meow!
Meow!
Ya-hoo!
Luffy! You did it!
All right!
A little more to go!
Chopper!
It always feels great to hunt a big game!
This doesn't feel good.
Captain!
Captain...
Cap...
Captain!
Hey... Get off of me!
Straw Hat took down Kaido?!
He did it...
Luffy won!
You did it! Big Bro!
Ya-hoo! Ya-hoo!
Luffy won!
Big Bro!
You did it! Luffy!
Gee... What a pain that was...
Everyone pushed themselves to their limit!
I'm lacking medicine and manpower!
Hey!
Chopper! Two seriously-injured people!
What?!
Chopper! Zoro isn't waking up!
Chopper-san!
I got burned and turned into a skeleton!
Not now. I'm busy.
If you'd been burned away,
you wouldn't have even needed a grave!
You're scaring me...
Well, you look fine.
Dr. Chopper! Please come here!
Okay!
Dr. Chopper! We need you here, too!
Dr. Chopper! The wound reopened!
--Doctor!
--Dr. Chopper!
Doctor!
Miyagi!
We have too many heavily-wounded patients!
Okay! Let's take care of them!
We scoured the castle
for medicine and medical equipment!
Meanwhile in the capital,
the lively festival is about to end.
Steady!
Hey, Tengu-san!
What is it, Otoko?
I heard my dad
was once in a high position!
And he knew that he would get killed
if he got caught!
But he tried to get himself caught,
somebody said!
I wonder why.
That's...
Yasuie-dono gave this country a chance.
If he didn't do...
...what he did that day,
all the lamps of hope that we had lit
until then would've been doused...
Cover your children's eyes!
The last Daimyo who served under Kozuki...
I mean, Ebisu Town's happy-go-lucky guy...
...will cross over to the other side!
He sacrificed his life
to save the future of the Land of Wano.
So that you can live happily in the future
he and the others have guaranteed.
He did it for me...
DAD, I MISS YOU
Toko! Toko!
Toko!
Don't tell me...
...you ate the fruit!
I told you not to eat that...
I-I'm sorry...
I was so hungry...
What should I do? Daddy...
I can't stop laughing!
Toko...
Could I have some?
What?!
I'm hungry and I can't take it.
Yo!
Fortune comes in by a merry gate!
If that's the case,
it'll be our loss not to laugh!
You see?
Yes! Yes!
How's this?!
Come on! Come on!
Toko, do you wanna dance, too?
Yeah!
You're quite a dancer!
You'll be the best dancer
in the Land of Wano someday!
You sure?!
DAD, I MISS YOU
Daddy...
For me? To live happily?
That's right.
Then I'll...
...change the message!
DAD, I MISS YOU
Is this good?
Yeah...
That's better...
Yes...
That is...
...the highest honor for a samurai.
DAD, THANK YOU
Steady!
Zunesha.
Zunesha, can you hear me?
I have thought it over.
I will not...
...open the borders yet.
I understand.
I defer to your decision.
I don't doubt you.
Mm-hm. Thanks.
I will protect...
...the people of this country.
Don't celebrate yet!
We still outnumber you!
--You snooze, you lose!
--Just give up!
There is no way Kaido-san could lose!
We're an Emperor of the Sea's crew!
Damn, they don't know when to give up...
Do you wanna fight?!
I still got energy left!
Wait, Franky-san!
Shut up!
Stop! Animal Kingdom Pirates!
You still don't get it?
You guys died once!
Young Master Yamato...
The one who stopped Onigashima from falling
after Kaido's Flame Clouds had gone...
...was our very own...
...commander-in-chief Kozuki Momonosuke!
Whose side was he on?!
You have lost the battle
and your lives have been saved...
But if you keep up your attack...
I'm gonna kick your asses!
Why is it shaking?
What is it? An earthquake?!
What's going on?
Babanuki-san!
What?!
S-Something wrong with the sea surface!
--Show me!
--Okay!
Why is this happening?!
Guys! Don't just stand there!
Go check on it!
What?!
An undersea volcano erupted?!
The battle in the skies
over the Land of Wano.
The declared winner was Kaido,
but the results have been revised.
Now it's Straw Hat Luffy!
--An eruption?!
--That's the direction of Udon!
What was that jolt?!
Are Kaido and the others up to something?!
Something is flying this way!
No need to worry!
This is not a crisis!
K-Kaido... sama!
Why is he here?
Today is supposed to be our one free day!
Everyone!
I am not Kaido!
What?!
The battle is over!
That eruption was...
...the final send-off for Kaido,
the Animal Kingdom Pirates' Supreme Commander!
Where did the dragon go?!
H-Hey, look!
A person...
How many are there?
What?! Komurasaki-sama?!
No way! Is that a ghost?!
We just had her funeral!
Am I dreaming?
She's really beautiful!
Boss Kyoshiro!
What happened
to your special faux-pompadour?
Now...
It's a long story...
...but we present...
...the new Shogun of the Land of Wano!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
The Flower Capital is thrown into confusion
when the Akazaya samurai appear from the smoke.
The last one who comes forth
has wavy long hair and gallant eyebrows.
After 20 years, the man who inherits Oden's will
finally returns to the future!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"He Returns! The Shogun of the Land of Wano,
Kozuki Momonosuke"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!