With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
"A Celebration Banquet!
The New Emperors of the Sea!"
--What is this picture?!
--What's going on?
Gee!
We told you to remove the "D." too!
No, we weren't told about it!
We got the pictures
from Guernica-sama of CP-0.
Reprint them immediately!
Okay?! We can't put this crap
out into the world!
But we can't contact
the printing company...
They're so useless!
Cease the distribution somehow!
He looks so mysterious here!
Deliver! Deliver!
Deliver every single copy of them,
my employees!
Cipher Pol infiltrated the Land of Wano
and no one's heard from them since.
In their last transmission,
they said, "It's Big Mom's ship!"
I won't let them manipulate information!
The truth is the most interesting thing
when the times are changing like now!
I love how everything
is happening in real time!
W-What's this?!
--It's an extra issue!
--Something happened?!
Hey, look at this!
Emperors of the Sea,
Kaido and Big Mom, defeated!
It didn't take long before such massive news
spread across the world.
The three pirate captains who took down
the two Emperors who reigned over the sea...
...for decades.
The Government has placed an exorbitant bounty
of three billion berries on each of them!
Three billion berries?!
--Boss!
--Wow, Captain!
Hey, let me see it closely!
Read here.
--No way!
--Unbelievable!
Hey, Boss?!
What's wrong with Kid?
Where did he go, looking upset?
Probably to the Flower Capital.
We have a new emperor of the sea, huh?
No wonder they picked that one...
Hey, guys! I heard
there is a banquet in the capital today.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Just in time! We gotta celebrate!
Let's get crazy!
Yay! Festival, festival!
We're getting excited!
It's going to be trouble again...
Add cloud ear mushrooms
and chrysanthemum leaves in the soup.
A plate of gisei tofu.
A bowl of flower-shaped lotus roots.
A small bowl of cucumber salad...
We must not let anything happen
to our valued guests.
So we grind everything once,
heat it up, and reshape it,
then test it for poison three times...
Now, I used all my skills today!
Please enjoy our traditional cuisine
that lives up to Shogun-sama's name!
Oh, what? W-Why?!
They all couldn't wait two hours
for the dishes to be ready.
But they look so delicious!
I appreciate your consideration!
It's boisterous out there.
Festival, festival!
Let's have a lot of fun!
Yeah!
Chocolate bananas and fried noodles!
Octopus balls and grilled squid!
Cotton candy, too!
This is the best!
Everything is free today!
Free!
I've never been to a festival! It's fun!
There are so many delicious things,
so it's hard to decide what to eat next!
Hey guys, what are those?
Those are called candy apples...
This looks like a jewel!
Beautiful!
It's sweet and sour! It's good!
Any other fruit wouldn't taste this good!
What are we waiting for?!
So good!
Hey, since you guys know so much,
tell me if there are
any non-food stalls, too!
Okay, count on me!
When you're full, you gotta go...
Gum-Gum Target-Shooting!
Yes! It's knocked down!
Luffy, you're funny!
Luffy, you can't use your hand!
Old man, can I try again?
What?!
It's broken...
Do you wanna try again?
Okay, it's my turn!
They got in!
Oh, that was great!
You're good, Chopper!
Your compliments don't make me happy,
you fools!
He looks really happy...
Yeah! Everyone,
are you having a good time?!
Yeah!
Yeah, all right! Brook, do it!
What I'm gonna play for you is a hit number
that will light up the Land of Wano!
I'm gonna give you the finest soul music
with the princess you love!
Yes! It's this song
that Brother Oden loved!
"Moon Princess"!
Princess Hiyori!
A Ponegliff.
What are these?
Are you interested in those, Nico Robin?
Tengu-san! How do you know my name?
--They're my collection.
--What?
Aren't they cute?
Beautiful girl kokeshi dolls!
Meh.
Oof!
No way... Th-This can't be happening...
My kokeshi doll collection was rejected...
I've taken the trouble to collect them...
You're being overdramatic.
You're a funny tengu.
By the way,
how come your collection is here?
You brushed my joke aside.
This is my secret hobby room
and where I was confined for years.
"Confined"?
I guess you're
more than just a swordsmith.
It's just a hobby.
Seems like I have a good aptitude for it.
Festivals and politics are exhausting...
Who are you really?
Me?
KOZUKI SUKIYAKI
FORMER SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
My name is Kozuki Sukiyaki.
I'm Kozuki Oden's father.
What a surprise!
Does Momo-chan know that?
No, he doesn't.
I'm not going to tell him, either.
But...
...the retainers may have noticed.
I'm the one who let Orochi
take over this Land of Wano.
I'm too ashamed to tell anyone
that I'm alive!
When I got out of this room
barely with my life,
Oden was already dead and
the Land of Wano was completely changed.
I thought about killing myself
by cutting my stomach on the spot,
but I had no choice but to hide...
...until the coming day
for the sake of my remaining mission.
Now, after what happened,
I have to thank you all for everything.
I'm sure they'll all be happy to hear that.
Yeah?
Hey, Tengu-san.
I wanna talk to you about something.
I'm aware this country has it.
An Ancient Weapon...
...Pluton.
How did you know that?
It's written on the Ponegliff
in the Kingdom of Alabasta.
I didn't expect you to know that much...
Yes, it's here.
FORMER EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
W-What was it?!
JUSTICE
DEATH RIVER DOUBLE SUICIDE
Gee. There are only scruffy men here...
Are you...
...a Navy soldier?!
Whoa-whoa, you're pretty beat up!
You must be Kaido's men...
Are you gonna welcome me?
Then bring me some booze!
Don't tell me what to do!
How could you be so relaxed?
You bastard!
Cut it out.
What can you do
with your mortally-injured body?
Shut up! This is a matter of pride,
you annoying Navy shit!
I really don't have time
to fool around here...
But if you stand in my way,
I'll have you removed by force!
Be careful!
He's not an easy opponent to beat
if you're injured.
Even so, let us fight.
We don't want to give the two trouble!
That's right!
Let's kick his ass!
No way!
Just two more!
We're against the ropes!
Queen!
Just one more!
What's wrong?! I think your injured body
is reaching its limit!
There's no way
that crappy punch could get me!
No, I'm a dare-not-be-skinny kind of guy...
I told you to cut it out!
If I get defeated by mere top officers,
I will be disgraced!
The Navy doesn't have the manpower
to clean up the mess now.
Just as I predicted,
you guys did well...
This booze isn't so good...
You should have aged it more.
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Hello, this is...
Hey, it's me.
Send one warship to the Land of Wano!
What?! Oh, R-Ryokugyu...
Don't tell Sakazuki-san! Bye.
Clank.
I really like it.
His "extreme" style.
I want to win praise from him,
like, "Good job."
By taking this brat's head.
Who's that?
All right, now...
He started it...
Ninjas, pirates, Minks, and samurai!
The king's retainers!
Yakuza and the Land of Wano!
Well done fighting, guys!
--All right, young man!
--Give a toast!
Go, banquet leader!
Yeah, leave it to me!
Luffy...
Don't tell the Land of Wano about me.
Why not?
It'd make me a hero.
What is wrong with that?!
It is true that you defeated Kaido.
You idiot!
Everyone has been waiting for you, Momo!
You're gonna make this a country where people
can eat and drink as much as they want every day,
and they don't need to be afraid of guys
like Kaido, and where every day is fun, right?
You should become a respectable Shogun
and make everyone's dream come true!
There's no need to mention me.
You're gonna change this country.
The Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance won!
That's good enough for me.
--Luffy!
--Gee! You're such a wonderful guy!
Hey, what are you doing?!
My wounds are gonna reopen!
Don't mess it up, Momo!
I got it! Count on me!
Gee... You are such an amazing guy.
Get out of my way!
Straw Hat!
If I can get rid of you here...
Jaggy!
Let's set them off!
All right! To tomorrow's food...
What are you doing?!
Here we go!
Cheers!
Let's get loud!
Yeah!
This makes me wanna drink more and more.
It's a banquet!
Listen, guys!
We're gonna drink all night tonight!
Pirates are such wild people.
Gee... I've never even heard of
a massive banquet like this!
But I never thought I would see
such a peaceful moment in my lifetime.
Boy, I hate it.
As you get older,
you're moved to tears easily.
Hey! Can we see these beautiful fireworks
next year and the year after?!
Yes, of course.
All thanks to everyone...
...for saving the present moment
and the future.
So from now on,
no matter how many seasons pass...
And look.
You can do this one all the time.
Awesome!
Luffy...
Everyone...
Thank you.
I will not forget this banquet...
Never ever...
Forever.
Hey, don't get me involved!
Oh, come on! It's a banquet!
I don't know what's happening overseas...
But look at this!
I came to get rid of you!
What?!
That's right. Eustass Kid
came to Luffy, looking upset...
...for a very clear reason.
It is a sign of the end of the old regime,
and the beginning of a new era.
Buggy the Genius Jester.
"Blackbeard" Teach.
Red-Haired Shanks.
And Straw Hat Luffy...
These are the new emperors...
The Four Emperors of the Sea!
The festival music sounds joyful...
But the Navy isn't in the mood for that, brats...
The banquet is over...
I'm gonna bleed all of you dry...
The outside world is a mess...
I'm gonna take your head,
so just wait for me there...
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
The Akazaya samurai clash against Ryokugyu,
who launches an onslaught on the Flower Capital!
The fresh greenery growing from the earth
is truly the finest Logia type!
Can the Akazaya samurai defend the Land of Wano
in the face of overwhelming abilities
that transcend human knowledge?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The World Will Burn! The Onslaught of a Navy Admiral!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!