yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
With weakness as my ally
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
I soar higher than anybody else
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
At times when you're lost somewhere
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
If my heart is also adrift
mitsukete agerarenainda
I won't be able to find you
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
Your kindness, nor your strength
wakatterunda
I already know
yoake no toki sa
It's the break of dawn
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
To the highest point of reach
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
mahi shite waratterundarou
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
With the world as my enemy
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
I stand my ground on quivering legs
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
OFF THE COAST OF THE LAND OF WANO
It's been a while...
This is the first time since
we said goodbye to Oden-san here...
Momo and Hiyori must have grown up...
An odd visitor...
JUSTICE
...is sneaking onto the island...
Jaggy!
Let's set them off!
All right! To tomorrow's food...
What are you doing?!
Here we go!
Cheers!
Let's get loud!
Yeah!
This makes me wanna drink more and more.
It's a banquet!
Listen, guys!
We're gonna drink all night tonight!
"The World Will Burn!
The Onslaught of a Navy Admiral!"
Raizo, I'm sure Oden-sama
would be happy about this, too!
Come on! Drink!
We should enjoy the festival!
O-Oden-sama!
Here, eat as much as you want.
Yay!
Thank you!
Gee, you-gara...
I haven't had food this good in a while!
Yeah...
Kunoichi-san?
I'm getting a bad vibe.
It is from outside.
Shinobu!
You felt it too?
Something is approaching.
Listen, you all.
Luffy-dono and the others
are recovering from their battle wounds.
Do not let them know about this!
So you-gara noticed, too.
We should not let
the sound of the festival stop!
Understood!
It's our mission
to protect the Land of Wano!
Mm-hm!
Let us go!
Influence is something...
...that eludes you...
...no matter how much you want it.
Hey. I only have business with
Straw Hat Luffy.
Don't get in my way, samurai.
H-He is... a Navy soldier!
Luffy-dono and the others' enemy abroad!
You know about the outside world.
Then how about this?
Flower Shuriken!
Shinobu!
--Raizo!
--Yeah!
Kappa Style!
River of Retribution!
Gee...
What?!
You're so persistent!
Samurai!
Raizo-sama!
The Celestial Dragons
are the gods of the world!
Since this country isn't a member of
the World Government,
you have no rights!
Sorry!
Raizo! Let us stop him here!
Groves of Wrath!
I use the Woods-Woods Fruit power,
I'm a Woodsman!
Along with the sea,
the woods birth life as well!
It's the very essence of Logia!
If you get in my way,
I can just kill you all.
Because no matter how many people I kill
in this country, the law can't touch me!
Don't look down on us!
How could you think so little of our people?!
Of course I look down on you!
I'll tell you something. Mankind has always
kept some of their own down!
Because the sacrifice of the few
is essential for the peace of the many!
Non-member countries like yours
are a sacrifice for the world!
By looking down on you guys,
the rest of us can live our lives!
Discrimination is a comfort!
Don't hate me!
That's how the world works!
Stop me!
Even if it means
killing thousands of people,
I'll reach Straw Hat Luffy!
Everything you said is...
...inexcusable!
Boss! Let's go see Luffy!
He's already become a great pirate!
He's unbelievable!
Really unbelievable!
We'll reach
the territory of the Land of Wano soon!
H-Hey!
We can't land there!
I'm...
...not ready to see Usopp...
Yeah. I bet that brat Kid
must still be there, too!
He came to pick a fight with us
the other day!
Calm down!
Boss will decide what to do.
This is...
--We're having a storm already...
--What bad luck.
--What's the matter?!
--There's a suspicious ship behind ours!
--That's...
--Red-Haired's ship!
CP9 agents are onboard! What a pain.
Who cares?! Let's go!
Shoot! Keep Red-Haired away!
Damn! What are they doing?!
What do they want?!
There's no treasure on this ship!
There's only a Devil Fruit...
What's so important?!
It's just a fruit that turns you into rubber!
I'm really serious!
I'm gonna prove it to you!
Yeah, do it!
Ouch!!
--You idiot!
--What are you doing?!
Hey, wait, Luffy.
His arm stretches!
What's going on?!
Get lost!
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
I guess the top officers know
Straw Hat Luffy in person...
Straw Hat Luffy is...
I heard he is an out-of-control violent man
who is like a monkey monster...
Let's go! Boss!
I have no intention of seeing Luffy.
What?!
Think what's going on
in our territories these days.
The guy who said he was Luffy's henchman...
Barto...
What was his name?
He burned our Jolly Roger
and changed it to Luffy's...
The future King of the Pirates,
Luffy-senpai!
This is his group's sticker!
This island is the territory of
Shanks, the Emperor of the Sea.
What?!
The Emperor of the Sea?! I don't care!
Oh yeah, that happened...
If we just let it slide...
I would lose people's trust in me.
Well, that's true. But...
Gee, Boss! I wanna see him!
What's the harm?
--I wanna see him!
--Me, too!
SABO MURDERS KING COBRA
We can't leave the Revolutionary Army
at large anymore, Akainu!
I know,
but there are no more soldiers to deploy.
Sabo...
He's a hero of the world now!
KUROUMA (TENSEI)
DIRECTOR, NAVAL BUREAU OF INVESTIGATION
Assassinating King Nefeltari Cobra,
the only Reverie participant
out of all the descendants of the First Twenty...
...who created the World Government
800 years ago,
meant so much
to the Revolutionary Army!
A few hours before that, in the Land of the Gods
where the Celestial Dragons live,
they destroyed the Hoof of the Celestial Dragon,
the symbol of the World Nobles and declared war!
The Navy led by Admiral Ryokugyu
and Fujitora fought back, but as a result,
Bartholomew Kuma,
a former Revolutionary Army member...
...who was enslaved by the Celestial Dragons
was freed and they all escaped!
It must've been hard for the Admirals
to fight in the Land of the Gods.
You don't need to make excuses for them.
What about the disappearance of Princess Vivi
that occurred at the same time as the murder?
We're currently investigating it, along with
the connection between the two cases.
Alabasta is in shambles.
King Cobra's ship
is still at the Red Port...
They can't go home.
Can we close the case
on the attempted murder of Saint Charlos?
Regarding Saint Myosgard
excusing the assailants,
they're still deliberating
in the Land of the Gods.
The Holy Knights intervened
and it's getting complicated.
Leave them to it.
People are excited to think
Sabo was behind all these incidents.
The lands that were a part of the recent
"Eight-Nation Revolution"
and all the small sparks
of the rebellion across the world...
...have begun to worship him like a god!
They're calling him the Flame Emperor!
His popularity now exceeds that of...
..."The Insurgent Serpent" Dragon,
the leader of the Revolutionary Army!
On top of all that, his brother Straw Hat Luffy
is now one of the Four Emperors of the Sea.
Even in the world of pirates,
Flame Emperor's brother destroyed the old regime!
REVOLUTION
The times are about to change now!
Sabo-sama!
Ow, ow, ow...
What a strong Haki!
They endured 20 years of domination...
And they were finally fully liberated,
so I won't let you spoil their banquet!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm Yamato! Kaido's son!
Kaido's son?
That is right, Yamato!
Momonosuke-sama!
I will not let you touch our heroes
who are not fully recovered yet!
A dragon?!
Blast Breath!
Momonosuke-sama!
Anyway...!
Go away!
To a place out of sight of the capital!
Do not make the people uneasy!
I made a promise to everyone!
That's strange. A pink dragon?!
I've never heard of
such a Devil Fruit power!
You're in my way!
Momonosuke-kun!
Yamato!
You should not fight!
What?
This has been a waste of time.
Gee...
I became the Admiral of the Fleet
during a terrible era.
But no matter how they come at me,
I will strike back at them all!
SIXTY-SEVEN SAKE, NO.5
Hey, Beck.
It's time to go and acquire it...
The One Piece!
"jikan gire sa"
"Time's up"
dareka ga mata waratta
Someone laughed again
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
All right, now hide-and-seek
owari
Is over
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
(1-2-3)
Be tough, there's still time
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
Ryokugyu takes advantage of the still-unhealed wounds
of the Land of Wano and tramples on the samurai.
Just as he takes down Momonosuke
with his overwhelming power
and a new era is about to close once again,
a man with a strong belief in the future appears!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Coming of the New Era!
The Red-Haired's Imperial Rage"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!