With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been
lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days
is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
As people enjoy the big banquet
in the Land of Wano where peace was restored,
the trouble that Sabo from the Revolutionary Army
caused was creating a sensation.
Gee...
I became the Admiral of the Fleet
during a terrible era.
But no matter how they come at me,
I will strike back at them all!
On top of that, the Emperor of the Sea
Shanks is about to make a move.
Hey, Beck.
It's time to go and acquire it...
The One Piece!
Stop me!
Momonosuke-kun!
Yamato!
You should not fight!
What?
TARGET SHOOTING
Onami-chan, you can do it!
Missed! That was close, young lady!
I got a candy apple!
Let's go there next!
Oh, I missed...
I wanna do it, too!
Me too! Me too!
Guys!
Whoa-whoa, you guys!
Aren't you forgetting about someone?!
Usopp!
Leave the shooting to me!
That's our Usopp!
Young man, that was awesome!
Let's make it the greatest banquet ever!
Yeah!
"The Coming of the New Era!
The Red-Haired's Imperial Rage"
This is so yummy!
Zeus, do you wanna try it?
Is it okay, Nami?!
Of course. You worked hard, too.
Yay!
I like Black Balls better.
I'm so happy!
Is it good?
It's so good!
Hey, guys!
I found a shaved ice stall over there!
Shaved ice!
I wanna eat shaved ice, too!
Let's go, Onami-chan!
Mm-hm.
Onami-chan! Hurry up!
There are so many flavors!
What should I have?!
I wanna have red-bean-soup flavor!
How annoying!
I see no end!
Momonosuke-kun!
I'm gonna help you now!
Do not!
Why?! Why shouldn't I fight?!
Do not! Do not do anything!
Yamato!
That's enough!
Just bring Straw Hat Luffy already!
Momonosuke-sama!
Damn you, Navy!
Ninpo: Scrolling Jutsu!
Fire Escape!
Did that do it?!
Burn to ashes!
Navy!
Just kidding.
Firebreak Forest!
How could I serve
as an Admiral of the Navy Headquarters...
...with such an obvious weakness?!
Water is important for
both the natural world and humans.
You know?
Let go of me!
Raizo!
Damn! Even if you cut them,
they keep growing back!
Raizo-san!
Doesn't he-gara have any weakness?!
Do we have to cut all of them?!
Dog!
No...
Admit that you don't stand a chance
with me here!
Momonosuke-kun...
Why?
Stairs?
We can go farther down from here.
Shall we?
Oh?
How did you sniff out I was here?
You weren't with the others.
Of course, I became suspicious.
Don't talk about me like I'm a hyena.
So you want to know, too.
Shall we go?
Watch your step.
It's moldy.
I didn't tell Kaido and Orochi
about this route.
But because the Lead Performer Jack
is a Fish-Man,
they found the Ponegliff in no time.
Why would being a Fish-Man help find it?
You'd better see it yourself.
How far down do we go?
Well...
Hundreds of years into the past.
Hey, Tengu-san...
Where does this dim light come from?
There is a glass block installed.
You can look through it if you want.
We're already at the bottom of the sea.
Room.
What?
Cheater.
Can you see something?
The Land of Wano... at the seafloor?!
That's the Land of Wano
from about 800 years ago.
The other one.
800 years ago? What do you mean?
That's just what it means.
But I don't know
how it ended up like that.
Since that's not sea water,
it's well preserved.
Here is what I know.
The Land of Wano was once located
at a base of a huge mountain called Fujiyama.
At one point, walls were created
enclosing the island,
and rainwater kept accumulating there.
People abandoned the unlivable town,
moved up the mountain,
and built a new country.
And that's the current Land of Wano?
That's right.
Here we are!
A Road Ponegliff.
This is the third one.
If we can find one more,
we can make it to Laugh Tale.
We're on the high ground in a cave
at the foot of Fujiyama.
CURRENT LOCATION
OLD LAND OF WANO
What's more, they say...
...the Ancient Weapon Pluton
lies farther down!
What?
I've never seen it
and I can't show it to you now.
To retrieve it requires
the removal of the walls!
So opening the borders means
destroying the defensive walls,
and unleashing the Ancient Weapon!
Opening the borders
means unleashing the weapon?
Why did Kozuki Oden want to do that?
Open up the Land of Wano!
That's everything that has been
handed down in the Shogun family.
I have no idea what Oden learned abroad.
Yummy!
Yum! Yum!
Hey, Bepo! There was a shaved ice stall!
What?! Shaved ice?! Where?! Where?!
Get out of here now.
Momonosuke-sama!
Mere humans are
no match for Mother Nature!
Can't you get it?
If Kaido were here, I wouldn't be here!
It's sad but Kaido's domination...
...deterred the enemies of this nation!
If you understand,
bring Straw Hat Luffy to me!
I'll leave as soon as I get his head!
Momonosuke-kun!
Let's ask Luffy and the others for help!
They won't lose to this fool!
We cannot do that!
What?
We will not get help from you, either!
Do not help us!
You had been imprisoned on Onigashima
and you can finally be free!
So I will send you off properly.
I have been depending on Luffy,
Zoro, and the others all this time as well!
If we who will remain in this country
cannot drive out any enemies...
If we rely on those who are departing...
We will not be able to...
...defend the Land of Wano in the future!
Momonosuke-kun...
Get out of here, you woods monster!
Why?! Why doesn't it come out?!
Oh no, he's like a kid...
I didn't know there was
such a pathetic dragon.
I'm gonna consign you to the earth.
Momonosuke-kun!
Wither away as if you never existed!
Damn! Momonosuke-sama!
Damn! Come out!
Momonosuke-sama!
Come out! Come out!
Come out!
Momo!
Get out!
It came out!
Momonosuke-sama!
Wow, that's like Kaido's...
Get out!
Get out of the Land of Wano!
Damn...
Stop, you bastard!
That's amazing!
He makes full use of his dragon body!
But he has poor aim.
That's so cool...
Gee...
Are you gonna burn down
a town or something?
So you wanna fight, all right.
You Kaido wannabe...
I'm gonna skewer you
from mouth to tail!
I can't move...
Color of the Supreme King?!
Who is it?!
Don't tell me...
The Red-Hair Pirates?!
Are you there?!
Boss! Don't use Haki all of a sudden!
It's too hard on the newcomers!
I won't say that's not fair, Navy...
But raiding the worn-out "new-green-leaves"
after they changed the history of the pirates...
...is a bit tasteless, don't you think?
Does the new era scare you so much?!
I'm not gonna fight you guys!
Not yet!
All right!
Wow!
You did it, Momonosuke-kun!
You drove him out!
You defended the Land of Wano!
I-I...
I defended the Land of Wano?
I really did it?
You're amazing, Momonosuke-kun!
He's gone!
Good job, Momo.
They didn't need us.
I felt tremendous Haki.
Yeah. What was that?
An old familiar face appeared in my mind.
"jikan gire sa"
"Time's up"
dareka ga mata waratta
Someone laughed again
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
All right, now hide-and-seek
owari
Is over
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
(1-2-3)
Be tough, there's still time
kakage you
Let's raise it
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
We're young, so we're free
baka na yume
A foolish dream
ikiru
We live it
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
jibun no ashi de Try
Get on our feet and try
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Let's see the ends of the world together
issho nara ikeru Fly
Together we can go and fly
As Luffy became an Emperor of the Sea,
astonishing news was shaking up the world!
These guys are the most brutal
and the worst in the world.
And the one who caused earth-shattering trouble
that jeopardizes the Navy
returns along with former
Warlords of the Sea.
The guy with the red nose?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The World That Moves On!
A New Organization, Cross Guild"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!