With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
"The Last Curtain!
Luffy and Momonosuke's Vow"
The sky is dark
The storm rages on
Thank you for your purchase!
This one is so fresh!
At Onigashima
A blue dragon roars
A legion of beasts howl madly
At Habu Port
A shower in late autumn passes
And maple leaves turn red
To avenge Kozuki Oden,
his retainers raced around.
This is a story of loyalty.
Though I am not so eloquent
--Yes!
--Akazaya!
I will try my best to tell the story
Now...
At twilight
on the day of the Fire Festival,
before a stormy night with pouring rain,
gathering at Habu Port...
...to raid Onigashima
where the dragon king waited...
...were warriors,
all excellent and brilliant!
Leaving the boisterous Flower Capital,
FOREST LEADING TO TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Momonosuke and the others are heading
towards Tokage Port trying to catch up to Luffy.
Momonosuke-kun!
I'll stay in the Land of Wano!
What?!
Are you not going out to sea, Yamato?!
Mm-hm! I'm not!
I've already told Luffy and the others!
So you are staying, Yamato.
Should I not?
No, it is reassuring to have you here...
But did you not say
you made up your mind earlier?
I thought you decided to leave
with Luffy-dono and the others.
Oden started by traveling
across this country, right?
I don't know much of the world, either!
I'll follow the same path as him
and go out to sea someday!
That's what I decided!
What?! Luffy and the others
even discussed that with Yamato?!
Then I am even more upset with them!
They made a fool of me until the end!
Momonosuke-kun?
Why are they leaving without saying goodbye
to me and Kin'emon?!
Why?
Your name?
Your father was a silly lord.
Who are you and why are you here?
I'm Luffy.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Cut the "samurai" crap!
I'm gonna become
the King of the Pirates someday! Idiot!
I am going to become
the Shogun of the Land of Wano someday! Fool!
--What did you say?! You eel!
--You are so arrogant! You monkey!
Who did you call "monkey"?!
Are you just a figurehead, Momo?!
Are you gonna just cry?!
I want to bring down Kaido!
Let's join hands!
We're allies!
Luffy!
That's right, Momo!
You...
...are just a chicken-hearted stupid brat,
but you always boss people around,
you squirt with a funny topknot!
Survive however you can!
I'm gonna come rescue you!
Because you're my friend!
Let me ask you one more time, you brat.
What's your name?!
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
I am the one who will become...
...the Shogun of the Land of Wano!!
Momo, go!
You can fly!
Yeah!
Go stop...
...Onigashima!
I'll defeat...
...Kaido...
...at any cost!
We may not be the best of friends,
but we have been on a long journey together
and you do not even care?!
How horrible you are!
I thought you were better than that, Luffy!
He is confusing freedom with disrespect!
Right, Kin'emon?!
That is right!
By the way, Momonosuke-sama,
why are you not flying?
Shut up!
Yes, sir! I apologize for my rudeness!
Momonosuke-sama is
the real Shogun of the Land of Wano now!
Depending on Luffy-dono's response,
we may have to cut him off!
Yeah! That is the way of samurai!
You said we were friends, Luffy!
Don't be so mad...
I am humiliated! I will make him pay!
I will punch him first! Then, bite!
And um...
Anyway, I will make him pay!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Next time I see you guys,
we're just enemies.
Don't complain even if you get killed.
Yeah, of course I won't.
I hope you don't complain.
Bye, Tra-guy!
Shut up.
What?!
See you, Jaggy!
I'll destroy you next time.
Let's set sail!
Hey!
You guys!
Wait up a minute!
Hey! We came to send you off!
Momonosuke! Kin'emon!
Yamato-chan!
Luffy!
What?!
I got you!
Luffy!
What are you thinking?!
Are you leaving without a word to us
who have known you longer than anyone else?!
What?!
Shogun and I are infuriated!
Go ahead and make an excuse!
Well, you're seeing me now!
Luffy...
This is the Shogun's order...
W-What?
Do not go!
I am sad!
I want you to stay with me forever!
I do not want to be
separated from you guys!
You guys were the reason...
...I was able to live!
...I was able to smile!
Thank you for avenging...
...my father and mother!
I am stupid
so I cannot put everything into words!
I fear what is to come!
So please do not go!
How pathetic.
Momo-chan is still just a child...
Usopp!
Yeah, it's ready!
There!
We were waiting for you on the Sunny
to give you this!
"The Shogun's order"? Momo!
You got bigger,
but we know who you are inside!
You are stupid and dumb and a coward!
But...
...I think of you as my little brother.
This is...
A flag?
When things gets tough,
remember the adventure of the sea!
Fly that over the Land of Wano!
If trouble shows up, show it to them!
Screwing with our friend
means screwing with us!
"Friend"?
That means I am one of you?
Kin'emon! Yamato!
Momo!
If you wanna become a pirate,
we'll come pick you up anytime!
But wimps aren't welcome!
Set sail!
Steady!
I'm counting on you, Yamato!
Uh-huh!
Bye!
Wish you all the best!
Yeah!
Do your best, Shogun!
Good luck, Momonosuke!
You better stop crying!
Look after yourselves!
See you!
Take care!
--Kin'emon.
--Yes?
I will surpass Kozuki Oden someday!
I will see you through it!
Surpass me?
No!
Okay, let's go to Hakumai!
Hakumai?
I was told that there is an official port
which has a lift to lower ships.
Great!
Since we climbed up the waterfalls to get here,
I thought we'd have to take a plunge!
Don't you remember how tall it was?
There's no way we're gonna do
such a dangerous thing!
I thought not!
Of course not!
We don't wanna take that risk!
Ah! Straw Hat and Trafalgar...
So you're gonna use the official port.
That's what regular pirates like you guys
should do!
Because, after all, it's safe!
--Sa...
--...fe?
That suits underdogs like you guys!
Under...
...dogs?!
No, no, Luffy!
It's good to be safe!
Don't take the bait!
What? Captain, what's wrong?!
It's okay to use the official port!
Shut up and follow me!
Okay!
--It's not okay!
--Stop him!
Jimbei, let me take the helm!
No, Luffy!
Captain, don't do it!
Go!
The pirates that Momonosuke-sama
and Kin'emon brought...
...were so strong!
As if they were the real Gods of Fire,
they rampaged like fierce winds
and raging waves!
The dragon king Kaido,
and the monster Oiran
couldn't withstand their attacks,
and their death cries tore the sky!
Meanwhile, Orochi was thought to be
burned to death!
He vindictively
pounced on Princess Hiyori!
Slash!
Just like that,
someone cut him off in a single sweep...
It was Kozuki Oden's
second henchman, Denjiro!
The remaining head was set ablaze!
It was the end of the line
for Kurozumi Orochi!
Thunder roared!
Onigashima and the Dragon King Kaido
fell in the same manner!
The dark clouds...
...that had been covering the skies of
the Land of Wano for 20-odd years...
...now...
...slowly cleared off.
With the sounds of the Flower Capital's
festival music in the distance...
Roll!
Burning unbelievably,
Orochi who still glared this way said...
"The Kurozumi Clan's grudge...
...will curse this country
for generations to come!"
20 years of pain in the Land of Wano
came up in Princess Hiyori's mind!
The undaunted look in her eyes!
"It is dangerous, Hiyori-sama!"
Cried Denjiro the samurai,
but she waved him off.
Our Princess Hiyori didn't give an inch
against the burning Orochi.
Instead, she gave him the final word!
A fan in her hand.
Kozuki's family crest.
She bit her lip
thinking about 20 years of suffering.
"Father. Mother. Brother."
And she thought of her home country
and said!
--Yeah!
--I've been waiting for this!
All right, everyone!
Let's say it together!
"Black charcoal
would not be called kurozumi...
...if it wasn't burned!"
On the day of the Fire Festival at twilight
The "Reversed Crescent Moon"
The port of rendezvous
It's a tale of the bloody battles
To get revenge and rebuild a clan
That will pass down for generations
This is the story of...
...the legendary warriors' comeback.
--It's just about time.
--Momonosuke-sama!
--This is it for today.
--Shogun-sama!
I hope to...
...see you again.
Where shall I fly the flag?
THE END
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
The mastermind of
the Impel Down prison break
and a new Emperor of the Sea, Buggy!
He is bad news who even has
the infamous Crocodile and Mihawk under control!
He takes command of a new organization,
Cross Guild,
and this charismatic smooth talker
goes into action!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A New Emperor! Buggy the Genius Jester!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!