With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
"The War on the Island of Women!
A Case Involving Koby the Hero"
NEAR SPHINX, WHITEBEARD'S HOMELAND
NEW WORLD
I see the island, Marco.
Okay.
Then I'm leaving now-yoi.
Thanks for giving me a ride-yoi!
Shanks.
What?
I thought you were gonna join my crew,
Marco.
No way!
I never wanna babysit
a great pirate again!
Idiot! I'm not high-maintenance!
Right, Bec?
--No, you are.
--What?!
See you!
Yeah! Bye!
A LITTLE WHILE AGO IN THE LAND OF WANO
What?!
You're not gonna come?!
Let's go pirating!
Yamato-chan! You can't do that!
I can't imagine a day without you...
You guys noticed it too, didn't you?
About the woods guy earlier?
What?!
You're so persistent!
Samurai!
The Celestial Dragons
are the gods of the world!
Since this country isn't a member of
the World Government,
you have no rights!
JUSTICE
I use the Woods-Woods Fruit power,
I'm a Woodsman!
Along with the sea,
the woods birth life as well!
It's the very essence of Logia!
Someone's tremendous Haki
saved this country.
Kaido is gone now, but those guys
will target the Land of Wano.
I can't ignore it!
You can't go on an adventure
while having concerns, right?
Neither of us can!
But I wanna be one of you!
Call me your friend!
I know, but...
You're right.
If you stay in the Land of Wano,
we won't have to worry.
Then I'll leave Momo and the others to you!
Mm-hm!
But Yamato, Momo has too much pride.
You'll have a hard time with him.
I know. I'll find my own way!
Yamato-chan!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Marco!
There's a ship nearby that's going my way,
so I'm leaving now-yoi!
Oh, you're going!
Yeah!
You saved my life
during the Paramount War, right?!
I'll get you this time for sure!
Straw Hat!
I'm not gonna let you kill him!
Take Ace's brother with you, Jimbei!
All right!
Straw Hat's life is
what keeps Ace's will alive!
We will protect him at any cost
on behalf of Ace!
If we let him die,
it's a dishonor to the Whitebeard Pirates!
Thank you!
Everyone was working to save you
at that time.
Why was that, Jimbei?
Well, that was a long time ago.
I don't remember!
I'm sure Ace would be proud of
how far you have come-yoi!
You think so?
Luffy!
The times belong to you guys from now on!
Buck up!
Yeah! See you!
AMAZON LILY, ISLAND OF WOMEN, CALM BELT
KUJA
"No men admitted"
was an irrefutable rule for centuries...
We've never been invaded by men like this.
Part of the mountain was cut down
and the town was heavily damaged.
As long as I'm here,
the Navy will come back.
Where should I go?
When it comes to this...
I wanna marry Luffy...
You've always wanted that.
Now that the Seven Warlords system is abolished,
the agreement with the Government that prohibited
entry into the Island of Women has been repealed.
Troublingly, the Navy can
even pass through the Calm Belt...
...with Sea Prism Stone paddle ships.
A FEW WEEKS AGO
All soldiers, prepare to attack!
Fire!
We broke the gate!
Dock the ships! Let's land!
Damn!
They've come...
If you step into Amazon Lily...
you won't go home alive.
The mast!
Keep attacking!
Sink them along with their ships!
Deploy the new Pacifistas, the Seraphim,
to the battlefront!
Activate the camera to record!
Got it!
Look at them...
I won't let them go any farther!
Sweetpea!
Who's that?!
We can't fight a child like that!
She's strong!
Besides,
she...
Hancock hasn't shown up yet.
YAMAKAJI - NAVY HEADQUARTERS VICE ADMIRAL
Hey, I'll leave the ship to you.
Yes, sir!
A-A warship! Look out behind!
Someone got here first! That's annoying!
Behind us! That's a pirate ship!
What happened?!
That's...
The Emperor of the Sea
Blackbeard's pirate group appeared!
It's a Seaquake!
The Neptunians will notice!
Let's go, guys!
We're gonna land!
I came for you, Pirate Empress!
I won't let the Navy
have your Devil Fruit power!
Hancock... That beautiful face...
I wanna take her head
and make it my treasure.
You can do so as long as I get her power!
Hey! Shouldn't we take her alive
and have fun with her?
Wait, Blackbeard Pirates!
Vice Admiral Yamakaji!
Give the order to attack
the Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard!
Wait for HQ's approval!
--What?!
--Clank.
Hey!
Don't get in my way!
I have no business with you guys!
Show yourself!
Boa Hancock!
Blackbeard!
Well, it's no surprise that
a pirate wants to capture a former Warlord!
Damn!
I see no end!
Watch out!
I'm gonna die!
Let's go.
We've got to do something
about this situation first...
Hancock-san!
We, the Navy, don't want to fight!
I promise you we'll withdraw
if we can take you into custody!
Koby the hero, don't push your luck!
Leave him to us, Big Sis-sama!
That's absurd...
No one can capture me.
I won't bow to anyone!
B-Big Sis-sama...
Wait! No, Big Sis-sama!
Come on, let's grab her alive!
Shut up! She'll be a part of my collection.
Just getting close to her can kill you.
Approach her discreetly from behind.
If she sees you, you're done in an instant...
H-Help!
Commodore Teech!
Nothing's working against this one!
Whoa-whoa...
Did you all get beaten by just one brat?!
Hey, you gotta be kidding...
White hair.
Brown skin.
Black wings?!
"PX"?!
Don't tell me...
...he's a Pacifista!
Damn!
This brat is a Pacifista?
What's this all about?!
H-He is...
...big!
There he is!
Damn!
Black...
...Hole!
Whoa-whoa, this doesn't look good...
Not now!
Thump!
Hancock!
The Blackbeard Pirates?!
Slave Arrow!
Oh, no!
We've got to go stop her, Helmeppo-san...
Helmeppo-san!
Vice Admiral Yamakaji!
Pacifistas! Wait!
Everyone who was petrified will break!
Pacifistas! This is an order! Stop!
So he's Koby!
Perfume...
No...
I can't dodge it!
Black Vortex!
How's that, Boa Hancock?
My darkness absorbs Devil Fruit powers.
EMPEROR OF THE SEA, "BLACKBEARD"
BOUNTY: 3 BILLION 996 MILLION BERRIES
FORMER WARLORD, "PIRATE EMPRESS"
BOUNTY: 1 BILLION 659 MILLION BERRIES
Snake Princess-sama!
Her Devil Fruit power has been nullified!
Get your hand off me.
Disgusting.
I guess you're not known as
the Pirate Empress for nothing!
Gee!
All my stupid crewmembers
have been turned to stone!
What should I do?
Just as I thought,
she's unimaginably tough!
Boa Hancock!
I wanted to have your Devil Fruit power!
This power is nothing without my beauty!
If you kill me,
your people will remain petrified!
The next user can't undo it!
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
Holding the oath he once swore
with his brothers in his heart,
Luffy continues to travel the seas
with an unchangeable faith.
In the tumultuous world,
he still holds on to one idea
through tears, heartbreak, and laughter.
What is the idea that will move the hearts
of those who hear it?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Dream"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!