(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
Gum-Gum...
Wait!
So please!
Don't hurt my father!
Idiot! Run!
It's a Pacifista!
"The Mystery Deepens!
Egghead Labophase"
Hey! Is it true that Kuma is your father?!
Yes! Why would I lie to you?!
That surprised me!
That's why you came to see Vegapunk!
You bastard!
He's alright! I only did it to buy time!
Let's go!
Dad!
Bonney! What are you doing?!
Hey, let go of me!
Idiot! Let's go!
It didn't buy us much time!
Subdue them.
This way!
It's a dead end!
We have no choice!
Bonney, I'm sorry but...
...I gotta stop him by force!
What? No...
Sorry, Bonney.
Close your eyes for a while.
Alright!
Hey, what are you up to?!
You two, don't drop your guard!
This is Egghead, Vegapunk's island!
Maybe he's different from
the Pacifistas we know!
Let's go!
Don't do it!
What?!
What happened?!
Oh, crap!
Subdue the...
Why did he stop?
What the...
What's going on?
S-Suddenly...
...m-my body...
...is paralyzed...
Luffy! Chopper! You guys became decrepit!
You became...
...a child...
What?!
I see.
He no longer recognized us.
That's good...
Let's escape while we still can!
Okay...
What's wrong?!
My back hurts!
Are you okay, Luffy?
Ouch!
Luffy!
Luffy vanished!
That Pacifista suddenly stopped.
Now Bonney...
LUFFY, 70 YEARS OLD (IN A POSSIBLE FUTURE)
You could have disguised me as a better age...
And I know how you feel, but...
...if you don't let us bust up the ones
who are not your dad, we'll be in trouble...
Hey, Luffy!
Sorry, Bonney.
We've been through a lot
with the Pacifistas so...
And turn me back to my original self...
Oh, boy...
Since they are clones of someone
who originally was a human,
it stands to reason that he'd have a family.
Don't get offended, Bonney.
What I know about Kuma is...
...that he was an evil king of
the Sorbet Kingdom...
...who was expelled by its citizens,
and then became a pirate.
After becoming a member of
the Revolutionary Army,
he was arrested by the Navy
and sentenced to life.
But because Vegapunk was deeply interested
in his physique and potential,
he was allowed to return to sea
as one of the Seven Warlords...
...on the condition that he submits himself
to body augmentation and cloning.
Am I wrong?
The Warlord and cloning parts add up.
But not the cyborg part.
That's like the death penalty!
No one would accept it
if they knew that's what it's all about!
You're right...
But there are different kinds
of life sentences.
I wonder what crimes
Kuma the Tyrant committed...
My father wasn't a tyrant!
He didn't like the World Government!
There's no way he'd cooperate with them!
He must've been forcibly modified!
Hey, are you trying to kill us?!
That was close!
By the way, that was...
A beam saber?! Wow!
This is a scrap heap...
These are the scraps of Vegapunk's inventions.
I can use this...
Anyway, this is murder
in the name of science!
My father said
he came from a special tribe.
So what?!
That doesn't give them
the right to experiment on him!
the right to kill him!
That's true!
A special tribe?!
Bonney...
Could you turn me back, too?
Okay, let's go!
Cool!
We're flying!
The robot is flying in the sky!
Is that Vegapunk's island?!
If we tell Luffy and Chopper
that we flew in the sky by giant robot,
I'm sure they'll be jealous!
How could such a huge thing fly so high?
It's anti-gravity.
This Vegaforce-01 is
propelled by the jets on its back,
and kept afloat by an anti-gravity device.
"Anti-gravity"?!
The air conditioning on this island makes it possible,
but it may be all over the world someday.
Wow! Look at that city!
I've never seen buildings like those.
We'll go higher!
Hey, there is a monster! Cool!
There's a giant robot! How many are there?!
Fish are flying!
Is it because of the anti-gravity device?
It's a futuristic city!
That's right!
This is an island where the future is made!
The Future Island Egghead!
Above the clouds is the laboratory level,
Labophase!
Down there is the factory level,
Fabriophase!
Workers and researchers live there.
Your captain is messing around
down there, too.
Good to know he's okay.
We're here.
I can't help getting excited!
What do I get to see next?!
Hey Zoro, aren't you coming?!
And you, Brook?!
--I'll look after the ship.
--Me, too.
You sure?! It's a futuristic island!
I can't trust that woman.
Gee, that fool...
Lilith-chan!
You can just forget about that stupid Mosshead!
--What is it?
--Try it.
Try what?
--The surface is like the Sky Island!
--Right?!
Really?!
What, what?!
Interesting!
This is so familiar!
Yeah? This is the first time for me!
What's this?!
Is this also Vegapunk's handiwork?!
Yes! You guessed right!
By perfectly controlling
the air conditioning on the island,
I was able to modify the density of Pyrobloin
and moisture in the condensation nuclei,
and recreate the Island Clouds
and Sea Clouds of the Sky Islands!
My guess wasn't that sophisticated!
This is the entrance of the lab!
Cool!
Showy!
Change to lab clothes before entering!
The Trancos on the sides
are changing rooms.
I wonder what kind of clothes there are!
I can't wait!
Future, future! Can't wait, can't wait!
--I wonder what kind of clothes they have!
--Can't wait!
Can't wait!
Hey! Stop!
You idiot!
How can I leave Nami-san and Robin-chan alone
at an unfamiliar place like this?!
I have a duty to watch them closely!
That's why I'm doing this. Okay?
You fools who slight ladies.
You are the fool! Go away!
Welcome.
Choose the clothes you like.
The clothes I like...
Should we push these buttons?
What's this?!
Pull the levers on your Dom Shoes yourself.
They'll fit any type of foot!
These, right?
They look heavy...
So light!
Cute!
Robin, you look great in them!
It's perfect!
They can strangle a wearer to death
if they want!
Don't say such a scary thing...
I'm so excited in these futuristic outfits!
Vegapunk is impressive!
They fit perfectly even on my body!
Super!
This is just an aloha shirt
no matter how you look at it!
Nami-san and Robin-chan are cute,
so it doesn't matter!
I've never seen this fashion!
Robin, you look great and strong!
Yeah?
How do I look?
You're a pervert no matter what you wear!
That's too much of a compliment!
I'm a pervert!
Didn't you have to go with them?
This is a Government island.
Who will help them if they get caught?
That's what I thought.
Want some tea?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks.
You misters!
Are you still here?
We already left the Land of Wano long ago.
Goodbye.
Whoa-whoa, wait!
I did get a ride on the condition...
...that the destination would be anywhere
outside the Land of Wano...
But not here, mister!
It's a Government island!
Thanks for helping our captain.
Get out.
I'll make these fools pay!
That looks like fun!
All right!
This is fun!
The stairs are moving!
The stairs are pouring out from the bottom!
What's the mechanism? What powers it?
The source of power on this island is fire!
Fire can be converted
to all forms of energy.
Are there a lot of resources here?
I've been researching what I should burn.
I thought I could even make a sun
if only there was a flame that wouldn't go out...
A sun?!
--You're in our way!
--Franky, move!
Sorry, sorry.
What?!
You're walking into a wall!
What's going on?!
This is a wall, right?
Hey!
--Open it!
--Lilith-chan!
What are you doing? Just walk through it!
Don't be fooled by what you see.
Lilith! Lilith!
What's wrong, Edison?
Lilith-chan!
I can't hear anything now...
His neck! His head!
Don't worry. If his head has been cut off,
there would be a lot of blood.
Thanks for a sober analysis! You scare me!
Sanji! Are you alright?!
Yeah.
You can just walk through.
But it doesn't look so...
--Alright.
--What?!
--I'll go, too.
--H-Hey...
Bye.
I came through...
Why?
Why did they make it so confusing?
What?!
What?! It's just an iron door
after we made it through! How does it work?!
Lilith-chan's gone!
Hey!
Walk straight ahead!
Who is it?
I'm Vegapunk Edison!
Another Vegapunk?!
I'm glad you made it.
Just follow my lead.
Still straight ahead.
Turn right there.
Turn left.
Aren't we there yet?
I wonder what's ahead.
I gotta hunt for "future treasure"!
What's "future treasure"?
Something like flowers made of gemstones!
I can't tell if that's childish
or old-fashioned...
Future Kick!
--What's this place?
--Is this a dead end?
They look like doors...
I'll open it for you.
Someone's there!
--What?!
--Hey! Why?!
Jimbei?!
But he's too young.
And he looks different.
The first possibility. Jimbei's child!
The second possibility.
Jimbei was turned into a child!
No...
The third possibility.
Jimbei's look-alike!
He has wings.
And he has a strange vibe...
Hey! Who are you?!
He looks like a kid, but as big as Jimbei!
Hey...
I have a bad feeling!
The fourth possibility!
A Pacifista!
Geniuses can even see their own future...
What are you talking about, Vegapunk?
GOOD
I...
...will die soon...
Stop joking! That's not funny.
I just wanted you to know that...
Dragon.
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
Bartholomew Kuma!
He is a pirate and a former Warlord of the Sea
who is also known as "the Tyrant."
He is a Paw-Paw Fruit power-user...
...which enables him
to repel anything with his paw pads,
and send it flying over great distances.
He was born on February 9th
and likes honey and salmon.
He was one of the Seven Warlords,
but he was also actually an officer of
the Revolutionary Army!
We had a fight once with him,
but he saved us from Kizaru and Sentomaru.
We owe him!
I am an officer of the Revolutionary Army.
I have a connection with them,
and I want to help them get out of here.
Kuma was being modified into a cyborg
little by little by the Navy,
but before he lost his free will,
he made a request
to be programmed to protect the Sunny.
Mission accomplished.
And he completely lost his free will
before the Paramount War.
I wonder why he had to become a cyborg.
That's it for this week! See you next time!
Bye!
The possibilities of science are infinite!
The research has already begun!
Their unfathomable spirit of inquiry
overwhelms the Straw Hats.
Good and evil. Wisdom and greed.
An idea and an explosion.
Talented minds overflowing
from all directions now gather here!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Brain of a Genius - Six Vegapunks!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!