(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
"Powers on a Different Level!
Luffy vs. Lucci!"
NAVY HEADQUARTERS
The Straw Hats are at Egghead?!
Why?!
According to the report,
they seem to be siding with Vegapunk...
See?!
Things are getting complicated again!
CP-0's attempt to land on the island seems to
have set them off on an interception mission.
Does that mean that Vegapunk
was aware of CP-0's purpose?!
Yes. That's why they forced their way in...
That's like a declaration of war...
I wish those brats had asked me first!
Anything else?
We already lost communication,
so we don't know anything more...
If Vegapunk has Straw Hat on his side,
we could lose
a tremendous number of forces.
Where's Kizaru?
He's already on his way to Egghead...
...for the mission
we've been working on for some time.
Tell Lucci to wait until the Navy arrives.
Yes, sir.
No matter what,
don't let him fight Straw Hat!
EGGHEAD, NEW WORLD
Many intruders! Evacuate immediately!
Evacuate immediately!
I'll carry her, Chopper!
Yeah, let's take her to Franky ASAP!
Luffy, come with us...
Go ahead, guys.
Luffy!
This is not good...
Hey, look what you've done.
I don't give a damn.
Don't, Luffy!
This is not the time for quarreling!
She's injured!
You're right...
You know you shouldn't fight him, right?
Lucci!
Don't do it!
Guys, I'll leave you the rest!
What's that on your wanted poster?
Are you curious about it?
Of course I am.
JOYBOY
DRUMS OF LIBERATION
I feel it! Feel it! Feel it! Feel it!
Feel it! Feel it!
What's going on?!
Is that... Luffy?!
So that's...
...the Warrior of Liberation!
I see...
This is gonna be fun.
Lucci!
Men are so stupid!
What the hell is that?!
Luffy got bleached!
That's it!
That's the Luffy who kicked Kaido's ass!
The white warrior!
Hey, Pigeon! Where are you?!
Let's fight more!
Your attitude is flippant as always...
It annoys me!
Straw Hat!
You're not the only one who got stronger!
CAT-CAT FRUIT, MODEL: LEOPARD, AWAKENED FORM
What's that?!
Did Rob Lucci always look like that?!
Stop, Lucci!
We haven't gotten permission yet!
He's so fast!
It's so rare!
Most of the time, when a Zoan type Fruit awakens,
it robs the user of their personality!
Kiss my ass!
Wait, wait, Luffy!
Think about your position!
This could cause a major uproar!
Shaka!
Did the white warrior appear?!
The real one!
But he was just down there a second ago!
I can't believe it!
Tell me! What is this transformation...
...he underwent?!
We don't know much about it!
It's the Gum-Gum power, right?!
One of the Devil Fruits, the Gum-Gum Fruit!
There is no such Fruit...
...in the old Devil Fruit Encyclopedia!
What?!
No, no! Even if you say that...
He says "Gum-Gum."
How beautiful he is!
I knew it was fate!
I didn't expect to meet him like this!
Hey, if you know something, tell us!
What happened to our captain?
This appearance of his...
He resembles a being in the old books..
He resembles a god!
A god?!
It's Luffy! And he's an idiot!
Are you saying
this is the appearance of a god?!
Yeah...
The Warrior of Liberation who plays the fool
and makes people smile!
Also known as...
The Sun God!
Nika!
Nika?
I've never heard that name before...
No wonder.
It was erased from history.
But as long as people yearn for it,
its existence will never disappear!
All things are brought into this world
because they are desired!
For example...
The Devil Fruits!
What?!
The Devil Fruits...
...are manifestations of
the people's aspirations for human evolution!
"I want to be like this."
"I want to be like that."
All the different powers represent
the diverse futures of humanity!
And so, that "unnaturalness"...
...comes with the punishment of
being loathed by the mother of nature, the sea!
The power-users...
...are the ones
who live in different realities...
...that someone dreamed up!
That is my theory!
You don't even need to think about
whether or not there is a god!
Isn't this world interesting?!
Do they know where they are?!
This isn't a playground for the Government and pirates!
SENTOMARU
CAPTAIN OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS SCIENCE TEAM
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Today is my day off.
What took you so long, Sentomaru?!
Hey! Old Man Punk! What should I do?!
Cipher Pol is our ally!
Pirates are our enemies!
Should I just fight alongside CP-0?!
No, it's not like that, Sentomaru!
The thing is I am CP-0's target!
Old Man Punk! What did you do?!
Did you rebel against the Government?!
I'm sorry
but I want you to drive CP-0 away!
Wait a minute! That will make me a traitor!
Who are they?
That one looks like Jimbei!
You're right. I must ask your opinion!
Sentomaru...
You owe me a favor...
...for saving you...
...from poverty...
...in the past!
--What are you gonna do?
--You're pressuring me!
Is he gonna fight us?!
They got three Seraphim...
This is gonna be tough!
Hey, S-Bear! Take one of them down!
Don't move, S-Bear!
There's no chance, Kaku!
We have a worse hand!
S-Bear! Get rid of those officers!
Retreat!
We're in trouble...
Yeah...
Sentomaru overrides
the Authority Chips that we have!
Yeah. The Pacifistas follow
a hierarchy of authority
and their priorities
depend on who issues the orders.
First, the highest priority is the Five Elders.
The second is Dr. Vegapunk.
The third is Sentomaru.
AUTHORITY CHIP
Authority Chip holders like us are the fourth.
No matter what we do,
Sentomaru's commands will be prioritized!
Then we'll ask the Five Elders
to stop them!
It's no use!
They must be commanded directly!
Even if it's the Five Elders, the Pacifistas
won't take orders through Transponder Snails!
And if you think about it,
it'll be the Government's loss
if we take down the Seraphim!
Damn Lucci! He didn't even think ahead!
Gum-Gum...
...Mole...
...Pistols!
Let's do it!
S-Snake! Guide the Straw Hat and the others
to the Vacuum Rocket!
So they can get to the Frontier Dome!
S-Hawk, S-Shark! Hold CP-0 back!
Chopper! I can't believe my eyes!
All those darker-skinned ones resemble
the former Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Yeah! They look like you all!
I can't believe they made clones out of us!
Our plan is screwed up!
Muscle! Muscle!
Hey! Ax!
It's been a while!
Straw Hat!
Don't talk to me cheerfully
calling me by my weapon's name!
We're enemies!
Are you going to help Old Man Punk
get out of here?!
Yeah, he asked me! No problem!
I don't know if I can rely on you or not...
I can't believe
you were named an Emperor of the Sea!
And that look of yours is ridiculous!
Hand Pistol!
Ax!
The commander just needed to be eliminated...
Seraphim, follow our orders!
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Sentomaru!
He is the captain of
the Navy Headquarters science team
and claims to have
the world's tightest defense.
He is apparently good at
repelling his opponent's attacks.
He was born on March 10th and
likes rice balls and baked sweet potatoes!
He was also working for
the Navy Admiral Kizaru,
and cornered the Straw Hats
who assaulted a Celestial Dragon...
...on Sabaody Archipelago two years ago.
But he let them get away
due to Bartholomew Kuma's intervention.
Later, he led an army of Pacifistas and cornered
the Whitebeard Pirates in the Paramount War,
and took down
the Luffy imposter Demalo Black.
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
Jet Pistol!
Straw Hat...
He is using Haki!
See ya!
I think I'll see you somewhere again!
A Navy officer and a pirate.
They're enemies,
but maybe he somewhat
thinks highly of Straw Hat.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
We'll unravel our connection to Cipher Pol,
the World Government's
intelligence organization!
Let's look back on
the history of Lucci, Kaku,
and the others who came to
the Future Island Egghead!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Log of the Rivalry!
The Straw Hats vs. Cipher Pol"
Are you willing to help us make our captain
the King of the Pirates?!