(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Are your dreams still pure?
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
All of us tabibito e tsugu
All of us, I tell you travelers
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
No such thing as a pointless fight
barabara no bunmyaku ga
When random contexts
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
Start to make sense on their own
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
"Sinister Schemes!
The Operation to Escape Egghead"
You're admirable in a way...
Because you fulfilled your duty...
...as Vegapunk's bodyguard.
So...
...it's a shame, Sentomaru.
This is an inevitable result.
He turned against us.
Dr. Vegapunk.
He's giving us a lot of trouble.
Let's get this mission over with.
The Navy told us to wait
until they get here.
How could they take it so easily?
LAB
If we wait, he'll run!
As you can see...
their target is me.
When you're a genius, people hate you.
What? Are they really trying to kill you?!
You're the smartest man
in the world, right?!
If the Government loses you,
it's their loss!
Yeah, I guess.
Maybe this is how the higher-ups think.
I have made inventions
that have been beneficial to the Government.
Innovations in navigation technology
through the use of Sea Prism Stones.
Modifying animals into Cyborg Animals.
Furthermore, a study on the Devil Fruits
and the application of its results.
Creating the Pacifistas, the human weapons.
And...
...the completion of the Seraphim!
I have accomplished
countless other feats, too.
How would you like it if I were to move against you
with the world's greatest intelligence?!
Oh, you're right...
I'd be annoyed!
Yeah! I would eliminate you!
Don't!
I don't even have
the slightest intention of revolting,
but those hard-headed people
firmly believe that I do.
Sometimes things can take a horrible turn.
Don't say it like
it's someone else's problem!
Then your group led by
an Emperor of the Sea came along.
I think it's fate!
Are you gonna come aboard our ship?!
You're most welcome!
Super!
Take a look at General Franky!
Take a look at the Sunny!
Wait a minute!
If he comes aboard,
we'll be targeted by CP-0 as well!
No, no, I'm against this!
She's right!
I'm all for what Nami-san said!
Yes, yes, yes!
It is risky.
But...
...they're taking the Sunny hostage,
so we have to do...
...as Dr. Vegapunk says.
What?!
Are we really gonna have him onboard?!
That's a huge burden!
Don't worry, Nami-san! I got you!
I'm counting on you!
Do your best-Quasar!
Hey! Why don't you free our feet then?!
You jerk!
Atlas-sama!
Oh no! This is serious!
We'll take care of you right away!
Prepare to treat and repair her ASAP!
Thank you for bringing her in!
Leave her to us!
Yeah, thanks.
Hey guys, where's Vegapunk?!
I know he's here!
Tell me!
Hey! Stop it!
Calm down a little!
So this is his lab!
Cool!
Look at this place!
That bastard!
I'll make him pay no matter what!
Bonney, where are you going?!
If Vegapunk's answer to my request
to change back my father...
...is those bugs...
I have no choice left but to kill him!
Y-You're just taking it out on him...
Wait!
Stop, Bonney!
Hey! Bonney!
FABRIOPHASE
Our Authority Chips are back in effect.
The Seraphim are now ours.
The tide is turned!
I took down one of the Satellites.
There are six more
including Vegapunk himself.
I think so.
But...
...that defense system is formidable.
I'm not gonna let anyone, even an ant,
off this island!
Destroy all ships on the island!
Block off all the escape routes as well!
Don't let them escape from anywhere!
RED PORT AT THE FOOT OF THE RED LINE
What is it?!
What fell?
B-Bartholomew Kuma?!
--What?
--Where did he come from?
I heard he recently escaped
from the Land of the Gods!
Why is he here?!
He's the Celestial Dragons'
Invincible Slave, Kuma...
Why's he here?!
In the northeast region of the island
around the entrance of Bondoras!
A former Warlord of the Sea,
Bartholomew Kuma appeared!
Navy soldiers, rush to the scene!
Citizens, please leave the site immediately!
It's dangerous!
He has already lost all sense of being a human
and is a slave kept by the Celestial Dragons!
His current programming is unknown!
It's very dangerous!
Please leave the site immediately!
All right!
We'll soon have complete control
of all the escape routes.
Now it's impossible for them to escape.
All there is left to do is take out Vegapunk.
Now, how should we drag him out?
The Frontier Dome is a pain.
That's tough.
Are you really going to go?
So you're not going to
listen to the Navy, Lucci?
I don't acknowledge Straw Hat
as an Emperor of the Sea.
I don't know what to say...
Officers are making haste
to block all the sailing routes.
All the ships on the island
could be seized.
I wish we could have snuck out
and escaped before they knew,
but unfortunately, Vegaforce-01
can only fly within the island.
Contain us to the island,
hunt us down, and take us out.
The enemy's plan is effective.
Great!
We're gonna avenge Atlas, right?!
I'm getting excited!
Well, I don't think
anyone can come up here,
so there is no need for us
to go out of our way to fight them...
Are you saying we should sit back
and wait for death?!
Calm down, guys.
Our only objective now is to escape.
Having said that...
I guess a fight is inevitable.
What is it? Is it something fun?
Stella is right.
We must fight. Let's just attack them!
Lilith!
If it's a thoughtless attack, don't do it.
Hey, Shaka! What's your problem?!
What's wrong with attacking back
against the fools trying to kill us?
Our goal is not to attack back,
but to let Stella escape.
We can't accomplish that
without taking them down!
Whoa-whoa, that's enough.
We're his Satellites.
We will ensure his safety,
even at our own peril.
That's our priority.
We can't have you running wild as you like.
You're acting goody-goody as always.
I don't like you.
That's fine by me.
Gee.
Why isn't Luffy here yet?
What's gonna happen next?
Are they gonna start a war?
Maybe.
Even if we have no intention of fighting,
in the end it depends on what they do.
Even if we make it off the island,
they'll come after us for sure...
I don't even wanna think about it.
What a huge burden!
I came up with innovative technology!
But!
I don't have enough time
or manpower to do the research!
I'd welcome even a cat's help!
Oh, Joshu!
Thank you for coming to help!
Oh, Sentomaru... You took my side
and this is what happened...
I'm sorry!
What should we do?
There is one more ally on the island...
No, no, no!
If that one takes our side now,
they won't be able to stay where they are
and the Government will hunt them down!
Yeah, you're right.
So that's what happened...
What?
Now I'm stuck in the lab.
Hey! Don't tell me... Wait!
That's not a good idea!
Stop it!
I'm sorry, but could you save me-Quasar?
What a shameless cry for help!
Of course.
I've been waiting for your order.
Clank.
They said they'd help me!
They were waiting for my order!
Looks like that's the best option we got.
Yeah!
Once they get CP-0 under control,
honestly, escape is a piece of cake!
Stella! Get on board Straw Hat's ship!
All right!
And then I'll take the ship to the port
with Vegaforce-01!
That's good. Now hurry up.
Don't boss us around!
That's the part of you
that gets on my nerves!
Now, let's start escaping.
Don't ignore me!
All right, guys.
I'm ready
so let me aboard your ship first-Quasar.
Yeah! Let's go!
Oh, wait.
There are seven of us that need a ride.
Seven?
Does it mean all the Vegapunks?!
Going on a voyage
with seven of the world's best scientists!
Super!
What? That's bothersome.
It's becoming more and more of a burden!
Seven Vegapunks...
Does that mean...
...Lilith-chan will come along?!
Then you're totally welcome!
Lilith-chan!
Vegapunk!
How dare you attack me with the bugs?!
Bugs!
Calm down, Bonney!
Oh no! Her anger at Vegapunk has completely
turned into resentment over the bugs!
Hey! I promised him
I would get him out of here!
Don't kick his ass, Bonney!
I won't forgive him!
What's that?
Labophase defense system,
Frontier Dome, deactivated.
Why? Who did it? What's their purpose?
Pythagoras! What's going on?!
I don't know! The Frontier Dome...
The interception alert has been lifted!
The enemy can make it to the Labophase
without any obstacles!
Is there anybody in the control room?!
Let me check!
Confirmed!
I see no one in the control room!
Then who did it?!
The Frontier Dome is deactivated.
What happened all of a sudden?
Lucci! The barrier is deactivated!
Now is our chance!
Wait. It could be a trap.
If this is true, it's a great chance!
We don't wanna miss it!
This is too convenient for us.
Don't you think it's strange?
We'll know if it's a trap or not
once we get close to it!
If we just stay here,
we can't fulfill our mission!
I'm going!
Follow me!
That's what he said.
See?! It doesn't activate!
It's turned off as I thought!
It wasn't a trap!
This is our chance! This is our chance!
We've got the best chance!
Your life is at stake now,
but I guess you're down on your luck,
Vegapunk.
Is that the Straw Hats' ship?
There is a robot, too!
I get it now.
This is why we didn't see their ship
down there.
Let's destroy it.
JUSTICE
So the Straw Hats are siding with Vegapunk.
Then they can escape easily.
But it probably...
...won't turn out the way they imagine.
Proceed as planned.
Send all the available ships...
...to Egghead.
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
Still looking for the future
hontou no yakusoku wa
The real promise
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Lies much deeper in my heart
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
A dream that no one can catch up with
tada hitotsu dakishimete
That's all I hold on to
taiyou no youni warau anata e
To you who smiles like the sun
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
I'll sing the same song as that day
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
kono negai ga todoku made
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Borsalino!
He is a Navy Headquarters Admiral
and also known as Kizaru.
He is a Glint-Glint Fruit power user
which enables him to transform his body into
photons to move and attack at the speed of light.
His motto is "Uncertain Justice"!
He's an elusive person.
He was born on November 23rd and
likes ginger, bananas, and miso ramen!
After receiving reports
that a Celestial Dragon had been harmed,
he went to Sabaody Archipelago
to capture the Straw Hats.
Their era is just about to begin!
The crimes of a pirate cannot just go away.
He had them on the edge,
but was interrupted by Rayleigh and Kuma
and let them escape.
In the Paramount War, he got in the way of
the Whitebeard Pirates and Luffy
who were trying to rescue Ace
over and over again.
He's now on his way to Egghead
along with a fleet.
Sentomaru who is on the island
calls him Uncle.
They seem to go way back.
Pirates, the Navy, and Cipher Pol.
What in the world is gonna
happen to Egghead?!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
What could the scientist be thinking?
Even when cornered by Bonney,
Vegapunk remains silent
on why he modified Kuma.
However, the daughter's intense feelings
for her father outweigh his determination,
and she pries open the door to the truth!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Turn Back My Father! Bonney's Futile Wish!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!