(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Are your dreams still pure?
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
All of us tabibito e tsugu
All of us, I tell you travelers
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
No such thing as a pointless fight
barabara no bunmyaku ga
When random contexts
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
Start to make sense on their own
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
CP-0 who was out for Vegapunk's life...
...blocked all possible escape routes
on Egghead.
Contain us to the island,
hunt us down, and take us out.
The enemy's plan is effective.
What should we do?
There is one more ally on the island...
No, no, no!
If that one takes our side now,
they won't be able to stay where they are
and the Government will hunt them down!
Yeah, you're right.
So that's what happened...
What?
Now I'm stuck in the lab.
I'm sorry, but could you save me-Quasar?
What a shameless cry for help!
Of course.
I've been waiting for your order.
"Turn Back My Father!
Bonney's Futile Wish!"
Is that the Straw Hats' ship?
I get it now.
This is why we didn't see their ship
down there.
Let's destroy it.
Leave it to me.
I'll destroy it with one strike!
I finished the dishes.
There's still time
so I might as well clean the deck, maybe.
I wonder what the alarm earlier was about.
Tempest Kick!
Sky Slicer!
What happened?!
What?
What was that explosion?!
Who disrupted my sleep?
Who are they?!
Oh, somebody was guarding the ship.
Roronoa!
You are...
But my swordsmanship is the best in CP9.
Don't underestimate me.
What a tough guy you are.
I'm flabbergasted.
I've trained my body, you damn gi-riff-raff!
Gi-riff-raff? I am a giraffe!
Gi-riff-raff.
That's wrong!
Sky Slicer!
You're Gi-riff-raff from Cipher Pol
that I met some time ago.
I'm not Gi-riff-raff! I am a giraffe!
Let me handle this guy.
I don't know what you're here for,
but if you're trying to destroy our ship...
I have to slice you up.
Bring it on!
Frontier Dome, activated.
Shaka!
The Frontier Dome has recovered,
but CP-0 has already entered.
Oh no! It's too late!
They're trying to destroy
the Straw Hats' ship.
Yes.
Those who must've been watching the ship
are fighting back!
We have to back them up
or we'll lose our means of escape!
See?! We need to fight after all!
We gotta ambush CP-0!
Calm down.
I don't want you to get out of control.
Damn Bonney! Where did she go?
This is bad. We completely lost her.
What was the alarm earlier about?
I have a bad feeling.
Hey! You guys!
What?
Luffy! Chopper!
Jimbei!
You guys are here, too!
I'm glad that we met up.
Hey! There is a bunch of cool stuff here!
Like a robot!
Yeah, we know!
We've been watching you on a monitor.
Even when you were in a fight
with Cipher Pol.
On top of that, we heard that
we'd have Vegapunk aboard our ship.
What? You did?
We know what's up!
Let's quickly get off this island
with Vegapunk and the others!
What?! We're leaving already?
We just arrived on the island!
Let's stay a little bit more.
We want to as well! But this is
the Government's island in the first place!
You saw Rob Lucci, didn't you?!
Something's going on outside.
I'm sure Cipher Pol will get here soon,
so we can't waste any time.
But...
Did you see Bonney?
A female pirate with long hair.
Is that who you were with
down at the robot?
She's trying to kill Vegapunk.
What?!
Why?
Speaking of, where's Vegapunk?
Oh yeah, I haven't seen him.
Since when?
Why did he just go somewhere
without telling us? That old geezer!
Gee! Where did he go at a time like this?!
I hope he hasn't been killed by Bonney.
I wonder if he's okay...
Vegapunk!
Damn you!
Stop running!
Stop it, Bonney!
I don't have time for this!
But I want to talk to you!
Listen to me first!
Shut up!
Stop it, Bonney!
Wait, you bastard!
What I wanna hear...
...is whether you can turn back my father
or not!
I just want a yes-or-no answer!
I can't... do that.
I'm sorry.
Then...
I have no choice but to kill you!
But there is a reason!
Damn!
What?
Bonney.
Even if it won't accept her,
she came in this world.
She is undeniably human.
It was a success.
I'm sure...
...this is a great first step toward peace
for the world.
Dr. Vegapunk, the director of MADS,
the Laboratory for Peace.
It hurts!
I think I broke a bone.
B-Bonney.
I can't stand up.
Oh no!
Are you okay?!
I have to get the medical team!
Bonney got hurt!
Distorted Future!
Vegapunk!
What?!
I was fooled!
Stop running!
Don't, Bonney!
Even if you kill me...
Age Skewer!
You can't run anymore.
Damn...
These glittering objects
are the years I lost, right?!
How could you turn me
into a helpless child?!
Give me back the shining years of my life!
Don't worry.
My powers don't affect
living things permanently.
You said there was a reason!
Then, say it.
Why... did you kill my father?!
But if I tell you, Bonney...
it'll... only hurt you.
So...
I made a promise with Kuma...
RED PORT
Kuma started climbing the Red Line!
There's no way he can get to the top!
I promised him that
I would never tell you the reason...
You had a reason to kill my father,
but you can't say it?!
Do you think I'm stupid?!
Screw you!
I don't think... you're stupid!
Let go of me!
The decision to give up his humanity...
...was his own, not anyone else's!
You're lying!
There is no way he'd leave me behind
and try to die!
You killed him!
It was hard for me, too!
I don't even want to remember!
Kuma is a respectable man!
I'm proud to call him my friend!
I really like him!
So please understand, Bonney!
I can't say anything!
No, tell me!
How can I be convinced
by such a self-serving excuse?
You're abusing me!
Please stop!
What?
That's... um...
That's nothing. Wait, Bonney!
It has nothing to do with Kuma!
Stop! Hey, don't go there!
Looks like it does.
Oiled Shock.
No, Bonney!
A CERTAIN SEA AREA, NEW WORLD
The fish was exceptionally big!
It's apparently not a normal sea area.
I'm excited.
Is that an island?
Kid, wake up!
We're arriving at an island.
Should we make landfall?
Why are you asking that?
There's no island
we'd be hesitant to land on now!
Hey, what is that?
I assume that island
is the home of the Giants!
It's Elbaph!
Elbaph...
NAVAL BRANCH G-14
Give me a break, Vice Admiral Garp!
We're planning to leave for Egghead soon.
Don't take any of my troops away!
Don't be so uptight, Doll.
Why are you laughing?!
Besides, if you're gonna attack an island
occupied by an Emperor of the Sea,
did you get permission...
...from the brass?!
What? Why do I need it?
You've been in the Navy for decades
and you don't know that?
Don't worry about it.
I'm already here.
"Here"?!
What should I do?
Koby-senpai...
Helmeppo!
Come on out!
What is it?
Is it a pirate?!
Are they calling Helmeppo
to kill him alone?!
No! That's...
JUSTICE
Helmeppo! There you are!
Vice Admiral Garp!
I wanted to see you!
Koby... He got caught by Blackbeard...
I couldn't do anything!
Stop crying! How pathetic!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Then...
...get on board!
We'll set out for
the Pirate Island of Beehive...
...to beat the hell out of the pirates
and rescue...
...Captain Koby!
Vice Admiral Garp!
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
Still looking for the future
hontou no yakusoku wa
The real promise
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Lies much deeper in my heart
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
A dream that no one can catch up with
tada hitotsu dakishimete
That's all I hold on to
taiyou no youni warau anata e
To you who smiles like the sun
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
I'll sing the same song as that day
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
kono negai ga todoku made
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Eustass "Captain" Kid!
He is the captain of the Kid Pirates
and a pirate from the Worst Generation.
His bounty is the same as Straw Hat,
3 billion berries.
He uses the Magnet-Magnet Fruit power
which enables him to manipulate metal
with magnetic forces.
He was born on January 10th
and likes cabbage rolls.
Just for the record,
his least favorite food is curry udon.
The belligerent Kid Pirates quickly
distinguished themselves even in the New World.
They boldly challenged the Emperors of the Sea,
the Red-Hair Pirates and the Big Mom Pirates!
That's when he allied with Basil Hawkins
and Scratchmen Apoo.
But he was betrayed by them, captured by Kaido,
and imprisoned at the Land of Wano.
He escaped, but tried to rescue Killer,
his childhood friend and partner,
so he ended up being tortured and stuff.
After he somehow managed to free himself,
he and Trafalgar Law confronted Big Mom.
And after a great struggle,
they finally defeated the Emperor of the Sea!
Let me help you...
...get to hell!
Kid now has a bounty on his head
equal to that of Luffy!
I can't wait to see his future rampages!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
CP-0 descends on the Labophase
with overwhelming force!
The Seraphim unleash laser beams
without mercy!
Will that flash of light accomplish
the assassination of Vegapunk?
The lab is on the verge of destruction.
Is it all over for the Straw Hats?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Desperate Situation!
The Seraphim's All-out Attack!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!