(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
I can't... take it...
Help, somebody!
I don't wanna go back!
Dad?
"A Shudder!
The Evil Hand Creeping Up on the Laboratory"
D... Dad...
What's the matter?
Da...
There he is!
Don't escape!
Stop messing around! Come with us!
No! I don't want to!
Shut up! Just come with us!
No! Let go of me!
Please! Let go of me!
Help! I can't take it anymore!
You little punk! You gotta go back now!
If you escape, we'll all get killed!
But... But... I don't wanna go back...
I don't wanna go back! Help!
--I can't take it anymore!
--Just come!
Help!
Stop it!
No! I don't ever wanna go back there!
Stop it! He doesn't want to!
What?
I can't get closer...
Crying won't do any good!
You shitty brat!
No... I can't take it anymore...
--Stop resisting!
--Go back!
--No!
--You little shit!
--Screw that place!
--Hey!
Why don't you kill me here?!
Even if I go back...
I will die anyway!
What?
Shut up!
Stop!
Stop! I said stop!
Stop it!
It hurts...
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Stop! Stop!
It hurts... I'm sorry...
Just kill me...
Stop...
Please... stop it...
Help!
Please stop...
Stop it now!
Shoot him down!
Bartholomew Kuma is climbing the Red Line now
seemingly headed for Marijoa!
Don't let him enter Marijoa!
If you do,
it'll tarnish the Navy's reputation!
Dad's past...
I don't think I'll be able to face it...
...with half-hearted determination.
But...
But I have to know it to be convinced!
Hey, Dad.
Show it to me again.
Stella! Are you there?
Oh boy...
Look how much damage they caused.
The Seraphim were all born here,
but looks like they didn't hesitate at all.
Gee! I wonder what he's doing
at a time like this!
Stella! Come on out already!
Stella?
Are you there?
Hm? Was it my imagination?
Stella?
An explosion?!
Respond! What was that explosion?
Are you okay, Pythagoras?
Respond!
Pythagoras!
Answer me!
What happened?!
What? Something just exploded?!
Are you okay, Luffy?!
This is strange...
Luffy! Can you hear me?!
Yeah.
Is everything okay there?
Has Vegapunk come back?
Everything is alright here,
but Old Man Apple isn't back yet...
Oh please, where in the world did he go?!
Is Zoro there?
Yeah, he's been here the whole time.
Make sure you keep an eye on him
so he doesn't wander off.
We don't need another one getting lost.
I know.
Anyway, Old Man Ap...
What?
--What did you say? Say it again...
--It's happening again!
What? Luffy? Hey!
What?
Luffy-san? Please respond!
I guess it's not working.
Building C, Cam-snail 12,
scan the area.
Find Pythagoras!
Was it an accident?
I hope he wasn't caught in it...
I just saw something!
Cam-snail 12, search through the smoke!
A shadow?!
Who is it?! Hey!
The Cam-snail has been destroyed...
Hey, Nami! Can you hear me?
Sanji! Usopp!
Oh, no.
What's wrong, Luffy?
This thing is broken.
Didn't you break it?
No, I didn't!
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go see Helmet for a bit.
Don't go anywhere!
Shut up!
BUILDING C, BUILDING A, BUILDING B
THIRD FLOOR, BUILDING A
Where are you, Vegapunk?
Gee, he's nowhere to be found.
Vegapunk-san!
Respond if you're there!
I don't even know where to look.
Yeah, this place is pretty big.
If we play hide and seek here,
it'll never end.
Nami-san, what happened?
Gotcha!
Where?! Where?!
They're jewels!
Hey! They're not what we're looking for!
Can I have them?
"They're jewels!" is
most commonly followed by "Beautiful!"
It's fine, isn't it?
You're all going to leave the island anyway!
Let's take them with us!
That's true, but...
...is your common sense buggy?
All right...
It's heavy so should we go back?
We came to search for Stella!
You're overstuffing your bag!
You'll hardly be able to look for him
if you have that on your back!
That's right...
So you carry it!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa, wait!
I have no choice...
I'll leave it here, so make sure
to lead us here on our way back!
I promise I'll come for you, my treasure.
Just so you know, those are
man-made diamonds for industrial use.
What?!
Can you make diamonds?
That's like a dream!
What's wrong with your eyes?!
The future is full of dreams.
These guys are crazy!
Stella! Where are you?!
This place is really amazing!
It's truly a facility that brings together
the best of science.
Hey, Atlas.
You got beaten up by Lucci...
But was your face a mask?!
SECOND FLOOR, BUILDING A
You can change your face and appearance
as you like! That's what the future is like!
Oh... Is this...
...Vegapunk?
Where?! Robin!
It's not.
That's an organoid.
It's an artificial organ!
An organoid...
It's technology
vital to the future of medicine!
What?! You can make organs?!
Awesome!
It's really a stunning technology.
I'm relieved. I thought...
...this was a piece of
a dismembered Vegapunk...
Hey, that's too scary!
Vegapunk, where are you?
I never thought
I could go on a voyage with you one day!
You were at Mom's party, weren't you?
You really pay attention.
How can I not notice
such a beautiful woman?!
From that moment, I've been your...
...servant!
Please call me a dog.
Get serious and look for Stella.
You silly boy.
Woof!
Follow me.
Woof! Woof!
This is a big laboratory.
If you search every nook and cranny,
it'll take forever.
We're on a weapons-development floor,
so don't set off any shock waves.
SECOND FLOOR,
BUILDING B (ON THE RIGHT)
You be careful, too!
Woof!
Hey! Helmet!
What's going on?
Edison! This is Shaka! Respond!
Lilith! York! Somebody! Respond!
Did something happen?
I can't contact anyone.
CONTROL ROOM,
FOURTH FLOOR, BUILDING A
Oh, this thing, right?
I could hear them until a few minutes ago,
but suddenly, I can't hear them.
But I don't think I broke it!
No...
I really didn't!
I didn't slam it into anything!
I know.
Look at this.
The video feeds...
...are going off one by one.
Why?
Someone else is...
...in the lab.
What?
Hey! Vegapunk!
Where are you, Vegapunk?!
THIRD FLOOR,
BUILDING C (ON THE LEFT)
Keep looking, York!
Okay...
Where did he go?
If we don't leave soon,
the Government will catch us.
Then, let's use this!
What's that?!
This is a Bubble Gun!
A Bubble Gun?!
Cool!
That's right.
With this, I can launch a very powerful
bubble attack that can deflect anything!
You say "deflect" but call it an attack?
That's strange.
If you can't imagine it,
do you want a demonstration?
Is it really okay?!
It's made by Vegapunk.
It must be an awesome weapon!
Oh, you're really interested.
Hey! Come here!
--What? What?
--Did you find Stella?
That's terrible! What happened?
What?!
A big explosion must have taken place here!
Is it an enemy?!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa, what's going on?!
Someone's down on the floor!
Hey, don't tell me that's...
Pythagoras?!
Hey, stay with us!
His head is missing!
How cruel...
His head was blown off!
So this was the explosion we heard earlier!
Hey, Pythagoras! Stay with us!
Who is it?!
No, don't shoot!
That voice...
Everyone!
It's me.
Don't tell me...
You're alive!
Pythagoras!
His head?!
What?!
Limbs are growing out of his head!
I thought I was gonna
get shot in the head as well.
S-Sorry...
What happened? Was it an accident?
No, judging from the situation,
was it an enemy attack?!
Well, it's inexplicable!
It can't be true...
...but I don't think I was mistaken...
What is it? Just say it!
Is it an error in our design?
It really can't be true, but...
What is it?!
Where's York?
What?
Earlier, Edison gave you an order to stop.
You have to be outside waiting for us.
You're so cute!
York, what are you doing?!
Well...
...I found this cutie here.
Love-Love...
...Mellow!
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Boa Hancock!
She is the empress of Amazon Lily
on the Island of Women,
the captain of the Kuja Pirates,
and one of the disbanded Seven Warlords.
She is a Love-Love Fruit user
and can turn anyone she charms into stone.
She was born on September 2nd
and likes hot pot!
She is arrogant and selfish,
but behind it all is the trauma of having
once been a slave of the Celestial Dragons.
She kept the brand on her back secret,
but Luffy accidentally saw it.
Hancock was gonna kill Luffy,
but learning about his fearlessness
in beating up a Celestial Dragon openly,
and witnessing his kindness and care,
she fell in love with him.
You can call me Hancock.
Alright, I got you, Hammock!
At the request of her love, Luffy,
she went to Impel Down
where Ace was being held.
In the Paramount War, despite being a Warlord,
she apparently supported Luffy.
After the Seven Warlords system
was abolished,
the Navy and the Blackbeard Pirates
came to the Island of Women
and a three-way battle erupted,
but with Dark King Rayleigh's help,
she escaped the crisis.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
The Seraphim suddenly launch
an attack on the Straw Hats.
They even ignore orders
from the Satellites.
Who is commanding them?
While all the Vegapunk Satellites
are under suspicion,
the Seraphim's relentless assault
corners Luffy and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Incomprehensible! The Seraphim's Rebellion!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!