(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Are your dreams still pure?
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
All of us tabibito e tsugu
All of us, I tell you travelers
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
No such thing as a pointless fight
barabara no bunmyaku ga
When random contexts
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
Start to make sense on their own
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The Straw Hats were searching for Vegapunk
who vanished.
However, further anomalies occurred
in the Labophase.
Stella! Come on out already!
Stella?
Are you there?
An explosion?!
Respond! What was that explosion?
Are you okay, Pythagoras?
The video feeds...
...are going off one by one.
Why?
Someone else is...
...in the lab.
Meanwhile, Usopp and the others found
Pythagoras who got blown up.
And...
"Incomprehensible!
The Seraphim's Rebellion!"
Experience...
...my power!
Love-Love...
...Mellow!
Oh, no!
York!
Why?!
It's a Seraphim!
What?!
Stop, Seraphim!
W... Why are you moving?!
Whoa-whoa, do something!
You have the best brain in the world, right?!
Please!
She didn't listen to me, either!
It's a laser beam!
Damn!
Why?! This can't be happening!
I'm Vegapunk!
I thought so.
I knew you wanted to fight!
If you wanna fight to the bitter end,
I'll go along with you!
Hey!
Damn you!
Who are you targeting?!
Your aim sucks!
I see...
I thought you came to fight me...
...but it was arrogant of me to think so.
I need your help, Luffy!
What's the matter, Zoro?!
Are they our enemies now?!
Guys.
Why are you here?!
They started attacking out of the blue.
What's going on?!
Explain it to me, Vegapunk!
This is... impossible...
I see. All right, then...
Let's just...
...kick their asses!
Wait!
They're the Seraphim.
I'll test the rank of authority.
S-Hawk!
S-Bear!
Stop!
Who is commanding you?
Great.
Is that how you stop them?
They came after CP-0, too.
I don't wanna let these fools die cuffed
because it'd leave a sour aftertaste.
No way!
They're not listening to you!
See?!
She doesn't obey our orders!
Hover!
Use your Dom Shoes!
Okay!
All right!
Wait!
Oh, no!
I caught a glimpse of heaven...
Shaka?
Respond!
It's not working!
Communications are out!
Damn!
I thought she'd obey you!
Can I fight back?
That little brat!
Are you kidding me?!
She isn't someone you can defeat!
She's our creation...
The strongest form of humanity!
That was close!
This is a really troubling situation.
They're not following my orders...
That means...
...it's one of the Vegapunks
who is commanding them.
What?
What if the communication failure...
...and this situation of
being trapped in the barrier...
GOOD
...were all calculated?
That means somebody...
...wants to kill us all!
What?!
Kill us all?
Damn Seraphim...
Screw them!
Hey, Straw Hat and Roronoa.
Why don't we make a truce...
...and form a temporary alliance?
If you uncuff us...
I think you'd find us useful.
They look disgusted!
INSIDE THE LABORATORY
Give me... food...
It's been two months...
...without decent food...
Can we get out?
Are we gonna die in here?
WORLD GOVERNMENT INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES
CP5, CP7, AND CP8
Are you listening?
Two months ago,
after we investigated Egghead,
we left the island
but were attacked by the Sea Beast Weapons...
So we headed back to the island.
The other Cipher Pol agents
who came to investigate our disappearance...
...all ended up here, too.
I'm sorry...
...but I thought you were the mastermind.
Dr. Vegapunk!
Yeah...
I'm sorry. I didn't know anything.
I had no idea...
...this was happening on Egghead.
Oh, dear...
It sure was strange...
There is no way
that research on the Ponegliffs...
...could be leaked to the Government.
Naval Branch G-9, the ships set out!
NAVY
The number of vessels, large and small,
headed for Egghead exceeds 100 now!
Roger.
All of you, get off the island!
FABIRIO, EGGHEAD
What do you mean, Sentomaru-san?!
What is happening on the island?!
Why did you deploy the Pacifistas
all over the island?!
A long time ago, an island called Ohara...
...suddenly disappeared from the world map.
Because they rebelled
against the World Government.
The Ohara Incident...
The Ohara Incident.
It took place on the island of Ohara,
home to the world's largest historical library.
Scholars and residents
who attempted to decipher the Ponegliffs...
...which was forbidden by the Government...
...were killed in a Naval bombardment.
Only a single girl survived.
Nico Robin.
The fact that Old Man Punk, who has
the best brain in the world, is being targeted...
...means they contemplated all the losses...
...but still decided that he should be killed.
If so, a worse incident
than the one at Ohara...
...could happen here soon!
Hurry up, Straw Hat!
What's happening up there now?!
Let's say we uncuff you guys
and fight together with you...
You'd just let us cuff you again?
I don't think so!
Yes, we will.
Once we get over the crisis together...
we submit to you cuffing us again...
Okay! Then we'll uncuff you.
That was obviously bullshit!
Is that...
...Baldy's technique?!
The Dice-Dice Fruit power!
ONE
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
Still looking for the future
hontou no yakusoku wa
The real promise
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Lies much deeper in my heart
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
A dream that no one can catch up with
tada hitotsu dakishimete
That's all I hold on to
taiyou no youni warau anata e
To you who smiles like the sun
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
I'll sing the same song as that day
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
kono negai ga todoku made
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Dracule Mihawk!
He is a former member of the Seven Warlords
and the world's strongest swordsman.
With a swing of the Black Blade "Night,"
one of the Supreme Grade Swords,
he can slash anything into two!
He was born on March 9th
and likes red wine!
No matter how many years it takes, I will hold
this seat of the strongest and wait for you.
Try to surpass me! Roronoa!
He and Shanks had a longstanding duel
back in the day,
which apparently has never been settled.
His residence was a deserted castle
in the ruins of the Muggy Kingdom.
After the Paramount War,
at the request of Zoro who was sent flying there,
Mihawk gave him training in swordsmanship
for two years.
While Luffy and the others were in a fierce fight
against the Emperors of the Sea, Kaido and Big Mom,
the abolition of the Seven Warlords system put him
in the position of being hunted by the Navy.
So he joined forces with Crocodile and became
a member of a new organization, Cross Guild.
There was a row about Buggy becoming
the head of the organization before they knew it.
Will someone emerge to threaten
his position as the strongest swordsman?
I'm curious!
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Zoro-san, we'll feature the great pirates
who rule the New World, the Four Emperors of the Sea!
It doesn't matter who is an Emperor!
We'll just beat the hell out of anyone
and make our captain the King of the Pirates.
On the next episode of One Piece! "Making History!
The Turbulent Old and New Four Emperors!"
Luffy's gonna become the King of the Pirates!