All of us! Dream save us, all of us!
All of us Dream save us All of us
Us! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, us!
Us! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Us
The farthest dreams, the farthest seas
yume no hate umi no hate
Each of us got somewhere we wanna be
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But before we set off
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
We gotta launch a dazzling legend!
densetsu o buchiagete kara da
Crackling! Bursting! No limits! Now it truly begins!
bachibachi No limit koko kara ga
One Piece!
ONE PIECE!
For all of us, I say to the wanderers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
We sure our dreams are still as clear as they always were?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Gonna make your restless cells laugh 'til they burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Even now, all of us're on an adventure!
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
To all of us, I tell the wanderers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
There's no such thing as a meaningless battle
imi no nai tatakai wa nai n da
When the scattered passages combined take on a will of their own
barabara no bunmyaku ga ishi o mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time will be woven back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
As the world changes, so will we
oretachi to tomo ni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
All of us! Dream save us, all of us!
All of us Dream save us All of us
Blackbeard held Koby captive
on the Wasp’s Nest, Pirate Island.
Hey!
I’ll help you out,
but in return you’re going to head further in
and free Moria-sama from his cell!
Managing to escape, Koby attempted to
free other prisoners by serving as a decoy.
As the island descended into turmoil,
Navy reinforcements showed up at the port.
C’mon, c’mon, c’mon!
She’s whipping a building...
Why the stares?
I’ll whip you into shape.
All hands in position, sir!
Prep is nearly complete!
For My Protégé
The Clenched Fist of Vice Admiral Garp!
Not looking good...
Far too many...
Not to mention this shackle...
Is there any way for me
to get out of this alive?!
You’re done for, Koby the Hero!
That bounty’s as good as mine!
Fire!
Huh?
Buh?!
Hmmm?
Eh? Whuh?
Wheh?!
It’s so pretty!
Pretty stupid!
What the hell’s this?!
Why’re flowers comin’
out of our muzzles?!
No, hold on a sec...
This is...
...that invention of Dr. Vegapunk’s...
...that earned him the Mobel Peace Prize!
Nobody even asked!
Who the hell’s doin’ this?!
Koby-senpai!
C’mere, will ya!
Wait, no!
I didn’t mean nothin’ by that!
Hibari, Navy HQ Lt. Commander (SWORD)
Hibari-san! Why are you here?!
Don’t tell me...
That’s right! I shot Flower Bullets,
flowers that bloom from gunpowder!
Our enemies can’t use their weapons!
Now’s your chance to get outta there!
A-And...
...if you’re feelin’ peckish, I...
...packed...
...some lunch for ya!
Hueh?
No, I mean...
Ring, ring, ring...
Clik.
Prince! Any progress?
Yeah, we just wrapped up here.
Navy HQ Rear Admiral
Prince Grus
Glorp-Glorp Fruit
Clay Man
Koby’s okay, too!
Golem
(Mud Puppet)
My mud puppets
aren’t easily taken down!
I’ll keep them busy fighting out there.
The pirates won’t be getting
anywhere near the plaza.
What are these damn things?!
And...
...they won’t be getting away
from me, either!
H-Hey... Was the plaza always this shape?
Nuh?
Is it just me,
or is that building moving?
H-Hey, wait!
W-We... We can’t get out of here!
See, you can do it if you try.
Well...
Whenever you’re ready, then!
I was able to contact Prince, sir!
We’re all set,
Vice Admiral Garp!
Hit ‘em dead center!
All hands, hold fast!
Sortie!
C’mon, hurry!
You came to rescue me,
didn’t you, Hibari-san?
Wha...
Y-Yes, sir!
Naturally, sir!
Thank you very much for that!
Whoa?!
Y-You don’t need to...
Right! Let’s get out of here!
Overhead, incomiiing!
Whaaaa?!
Whaaaaa?!
There’s a Navy battleship
flying up there!
Why?! How’s that even possible?!
Who’s on it?!
Ain’t it... falling toward us?
R-Run!
Look there, aboard the ship!
Ain’t no way!
I thought he retired!
It’s... the legendary hero,
Vice Admiral Garp!
Koby! I’m here to save you!
Run! Just get the hell outta here!
We can’t... We don’t got no way out!
Ahoy there, pirate scum!
Here he comes! Run for it!
Vice Admiral Garp...
Why?! I’m not worthy of saving...
You little roaches!
Do you know just who it is
you’ve kidnapped?!
Koby’s the future of the Navy!
And...
...my protégé!
Galaxy...
...Impact!
We gotta run or it’ll crush us!
Why is he...
in the Wasp’s Nest?
Cumuloglorpus!
He destroyed the town
in just one punch...
Still pullin’ crazy stunts...
Damn you, Garp!
He’s insane!
I’ll make that old fart pay!
Don’t move a muscle, pirate scum!
You can do this the easy way!
Or, you can try to fight us off
and end up in a world of hurt!
Drop your weapons!
I ain’t satisfied...
I’ve lost my touch!
How full of it can you be?!
The hell’s with that “I could do better” attitude
after what you did to the damn place?!
There’s almost nothin’ left to wreck!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Oh, Koby!
No worse for the wear, I see!
Ah, c’mon, Koby...
Man, what a load off my shoulders!
They didn’t kill him after all!
Koby-kun, glad you’re fine.
Good work, everyone!
Goodness...
He took it a little too far.
Garp’s such a bad boy!
Garp-san did say Koby’s the Navy’s future.
To hell with that!
I’m gonna hamstring him!
You’re not supposed to
say that part out loud...
...you sweet, sheltered child.
Hey!
Koby!
Captain Koby!
Everybody...!
Koby-kun!
Come on!
We’re returning to home port!
Helmeppo-san! Tashigi-san!
There’s even sailors not in SWORD...
Everybody likes ya, Koby-senpai!
What’s with the extra weight, Koby?
Must be hard,
runnin’ with that in tow...
Vice Admiral Garp!
We couldn’t remove his shackle...
It’s got us stumped, sir!
Please...
...do...
...some...
...thin’...
Hibari!
Hibari-san!
So, what do the bunch of you...
...think you’re doing, exactly?
Kuzan.
Kuzan-san!
What are you doing?!
Please thaw out Hibari-san!
Blue Pheasant’s here!
Captain Kuzan!
Kuzan-chan!
Kuzan-san, please, you must!
No use trying.
Don’t go causing problems for me, Koby.
Can’t have you running off...
...while Teach is away.
Two years ago,
a huge quarrel erupted over who would be
the next Navy HQ Fleet Admiral.
The duelists: Admiral Red Hound, versus...
...Admiral Blue Pheasant.
After ten days of life-or-death struggle,
victory went to...
...Red Hound.
Out of mercy, Red Hound
allowed Blue Pheasant to live.
However, Blue Pheasant refused
to serve under Red Hound.
And so, he separated from the Navy.
An island in the New World
What the hell...
Blackbeard’s here!
Run! We gotta leave town!
Hey!
The hell happened here?!
Hold it, people! Who did this?!
Why’m I botherin’ to ask...
There’s only one guy in the world
that can pull this off...
And that’s you,
Blue Pheasant!
Ya left my crew frozen solid
on the outskirts of town!
Thaw ‘em out!
You’re annoying me.
Wouldn’t go using your Tremor-Tremor Fruit...
You’ll shatter your crew and kill them.
You’re their captain,
so I’d think you understand...
Do you think I started it?
That, and you do know
what happened to me, right?
I’m mourning...
and a bit on edge, you see.
Go on, guess whose fault it really is.
How far have you run to get here?
dore dake hashitte kita no ka
Not knowing, you count your scars instead
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
With the treasure map that's always in your mind
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
You'll keep seeking the future
mirai o sagashi tsuzuketeru
True promises dwell deeper than the bottom of your heart
hontou no yakusoku wa mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
Everyone has a dream they can't catch
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
A lone dream they hold dear
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you, with your smile like the sun
taiyou no you ni warau anata e
I sing, just like I did that day
ano hi to onaji uta o utau yo
Even if I grow up, I never want to forget
otona ni natte mo wasuretaku nai
Until the day my wish reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
Diving Into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!
Diving Into the Sea of Information！
The Punk Records Library！
Yo! I’m one of the humble genius scientist
Dr. Vegapunk’s Satellites, Lilith!
Ah’m one of the Vegapunks too!
Edison’s the name!
Today we’re introducin’
this ‘un here: Helmeppo!
Navy Lt. Commander - Member of the Covert Spec Ops, SWORD
He’s a lieutenant commander and
a member of SWORD, a top-secret special forces unit!
He was born on July 16th,
an’ loves caviar an’ fancy steaks!
He’s the son of a former Navy branch captain,
Axe-Hand Morgan, the once-tyrant of Shells Town.
Son of Axe Hand Morgan
He’s the son of a former Navy branch captain,
Axe-Hand Morgan, the once-tyrant of Shells Town.
He used to flaunt his dad’s influence
to boss people around.
One day, he put Zoro under arrest
on trumped-up charges.
He promised Zoro he’d free him if he could
survive without food or drink fer a month,
but he went back on his word
an’ tried to execute Zoro.
After all that, an angry Luffy and Zoro
beat him and his dad up!
He joined the Navy and spent some time
as a chore boy alongside Koby.
I guess he’s sort of
making up for it all now?
He’s currently flourishing
as a lieutenant commander!
When Blackbeard kidnapped Koby,
he spoke up, demandin’ to go get Koby back!
I’m begging you guys!
We’re all on the same page, ain’t we?!
On our own,
we don’t stand a chance...
CAPTAIN KOBY ABDUCTED BY BLACKBEARD. STATUS: UNKNOWN
...of saving him!
Helmeppo’s shinin’ brighter
than he ever has, ain’t he?
That’s all for today!
Since you watched it all,
you owe us a research fund donation!
See y’all next time!
Kuzan, barring Garp from his mission
to save Koby!
After separating from the Navy,
what are his true intentions in joining Blackbeard’s crew?
Garp’s former number-one pupil,
now turned pirate,
is about to unleash
a blow of rebellion upon his ex-mentor!
Next time, on One Piece:
The Navy, Stunned!
Former Navy HQ Admiral Kuzan
I’m gonna be the Pirate King!