(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Are your dreams still pure?
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
All of us tabibito e tsugu
All of us, I tell you travelers
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
No such thing as a pointless fight
barabara no bunmyaku ga
When random contexts
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
Start to make sense on their own
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
Guys!
To prepare for the looming new era,
we founded Cross Guild!
Let's do it in a flashy way!
"Let's Go Get It!
Buggy's Big Declaration"
You're okay now. I'm here to help.
Where's your family? Did you get lost?
NAVY HQ VICE ADMIRAL T-BONE DEAD
Beloved by many Navy soldiers and citizens,
Vice Admiral T-Bone's death in the line of duty...
...shocked the public,
but the Navy never revealed
the cause of his death.
Have they found the killer?
I don't know.
All I know is that the killer's family
is now living a happy life.
The world is going to the dogs, Tsuru-chan.
It's hard when the citizens you're supposed
to be protecting stab you in the back.
When bounties are put on Navy soldiers,
it's not just pirates who want money.
The murder took place in Pepe Kingdom where
over a thousand people die of starvation annually.
Poverty and money change people.
But I don't mean to defend the killer.
If this is what he had in his mind,
we underestimated the Genius Jester.
Can you risk your life to save citizens
while fearing being killed by them?
We need to destroy Cross Guild soon.
Otherwise, it could demoralize the soldiers
and weaken the Navy!
What is it?
Hina!
Do you know where Garp is?
I want him to try
a new rice cracker flavor.
Oh, well...
Several days ago, he said
he was gonna go save Koby, and...
Save Koby?!
I think he is with SWORD.
Probably Kujaku, too.
What?! No way!
They went to Beehive?!
I can't believe you made it across the sea.
Yes...
Well done!
Rulers of the underground are so happy!
A big evil star is born!
I heard you sent my family money...
Thank you so much!
Of course I did!
You're the master of evil who took out
one of the Navy HQ Vice Admirals!
I heard Navy soldiers got quite panicky
the day it happened!
Once they find you...
they'll cut your head off!
I figured
even if I'd never see my family again,
it was better than my whole family
starving to death!
Don't worry!
I'll take you in as a pirate!
A pirate?
Hi, freshman!
No, I...
You don't get it, do you?
What?
An Emperor of the Sea,
Buggy-sama the Genius Jester...
...is a noble man who
ordinary pirates will never get to see!
So take a good look at him! That's...
...Buggy-sama in the flesh!
Buggy in the flesh!
--Buggy in the flesh! Buggy in the flesh!
--I like that, guys!
Buggy in the flesh! Buggy in the flesh!
Excuse me, Barley-sama so fresh!
I'm not cereal!
It's finished!
Cross Guild's ship!
Great!
Let's unveil it soon!
Tell Mihawk and Crocodile to come!
Okay!
I can't wait to see it!
We spent lavishly on this ship.
Right!
We gotta show them
what we're really made of!
Get ready for it!
It'll make your eyes pop out of your head!
Oh yeah?
Now take a look!
Oh, this is...
Why?!
How did it end up like this?!
It's great, isn't it?!
What are you doing?
Chairman Buggy should be at the bow!
--We did great!
--The best ship ever!
--Well done, guys!
--Stop it...
Hey, what is that?
Do you remember what you said
with confidence?
Leave the shipbuilding to me!
We got an amazing shipwright!
Why should we sail on such a bizarre ship?!
Come to the meeting room!
N-N-No... I mean...
MEETING ROOM
Cross Guild's public reception
has been excellent.
It's about time for the Navy
to notice the threat it poses.
Just... Just kill me already...
I can't take it...
We need to establish a utopia,
a military nation
that won't be threatened by any power.
What we need for that is...
...overwhelming strength.
No...
This is not the life I envisioned for myself...
Where did it go wrong?
All these guys keep getting in my way!
To afford that,
it'll take an enormous amount of...
...money and power, right?!
I-I'm sorry for saying that...
Shut up.
You should be thankful
just to be displayed there.
What am I? An ornament?
It's not like I wanted you in my life!
Gee, if you wanna kill me,
you can just do it!
But how can you call yourselves pirates?!
Your goals are small scale!
Don't try to take a roundabout approach!
Are you desperate?
I bet you heard that Red-Haired
began to make a move.
He and I were aboard the ship of
the King of the Pirates,
but we've never been to Laugh Tale
for some reason.
What did you guys want to become
when you grow up?!
Standing next to Shanks
who was so promising,
I had given up on my dream!
24 YEARS AGO, DAY OF GOLD ROGER'S EXECUTION
You said it, Shanks!
You said we'd make it to Laugh Tale
with our own ships someday!
Yeah.
But I've changed my mind.
I'm not going for it at this point.
What?!
But I'll continue to be a pirate.
I'm disappointed in you, Shanks.
I thought you would become
the king of the next generation.
Come with me, Buggy.
I'm not gonna be your subordinate, idiot!
You coward!
What Captain Roger wants is
for you to follow his footsteps, isn't it?!
I hope you remember!
I lost my treasure map because of you!
I haven't forgiven you for that!
The next time we meet, we'll be enemies!
But now Shanks is making a move.
Why, after all this time?!
I'm...
...on equal footing with him
even if it's by luck or accident!
So I wanna be the King of the Pirates!
Power?! Money?! We can have it all!
Let's go get it!
The greatest treasure in the world!
What?!
Shut up!
No!
They say titles give people
delusions of grandeur,
but can you really be this conceited?
Do you think we'll fall for
your smooth talking?
You have nothing planned or prepared.
Piracy is a business!
Red-Haired, Blackbeard, and Straw Hat.
Are you saying we should fight them all?
We can just outsmart them!
A treasure hunt is a race after all!
Let me show you guys!
How these words can inspire everyone!
All pirates...
...set out to the sea
to get the same thing!
Clank.
Hey, guys!
Buggy-sama?
Stop it, Buggy!
Guys!
What dream drove you out to the sea?!
Next thing you know, you could be dead...
So isn't your soul screaming?!
Here we go again!
Chairman Buggy ignites the spark
that we lost!
You cowards
who are content with the status quo!
Reach out for the thing you want the most!
You guys got me!
Let's go get...
...the One Piece!
Hey!
The One Piece!
Whose ship is it?
We're almost there! Too hard? You okay?
USHIANO (MORLEY'S ASSISTANT)
VICE CAPTAIN, REVOLUTIONARY ARMY WESTERN FORCES
Is it our ally? Or...
KAMABAKKA QUEENDOM, GRAND LINE
I have a bad feeling.
AHIRU (BELO BETTY'S ASSISTANT)
VICE CAPTAIN, REVOLUTIONARY ARMY EASTERN FORCES
JIRON (KARASU'S ASSISTANT)
VICE CAPTAIN, REVOLUTIONARY ARMY NORTHERN FORCES
Hey! Tell me!
What do you think of that ship?
Is it our enemy? What? Who?
What should we do?
Hey! It's coming this way!
Be quiet.
Whir.
Clang! Clunk!
Hey, do you wanna make a bet?
On the unknown ship?
GAMBO (LINDBERGH'S ASSISTANT)
VICE CAPTAIN, REVOLUTIONARY ARMY SOUTHERN FORCES
I bet that's an enemy ship! For how much?
Okay-je!
Rwwhhhh.
Then I'll wager...
...a million on Sabo-san's return.
What?!
A million?!
Dragon-san! Iva-san!
Sabo-san...
...returned!
Heehaw!
I'm glad!
So he's okay!
I missed him!
Sabo!
Sabo-san!
Everyone!
I'm back!
Welcome back, Sabo!
I know you cheated! A million?!
I'm not gonna pay you!
No, I'll make you pay.
You used a telescope, didn't you?!
I don't have it-je.
What are you eating?! Isn't it a telescope?!
Whir.
Clang!
Welcome back. I almost shot you!
Glad you didn't, Ahiru.
Did you worry about me?
Maybe!
Sabo! Safe! Happy!
I'm happy to see you too, Ushiano.
Gee!
You're good at keeping people hanging!
We all were in a stew!
Sorry about that.
What took you so long to come back?
This is a Lulusia ship.
What? Lulusia?!
The kingdom that suddenly vanished?!
Yeah.
I'll explain later.
First, let them rest.
Sabo-kun!
How could you go radio silent?!
Koala, I'm sorry!
I couldn't get
an Encryption Transponder Snail,
and I knew all my communications
would be intercepted!
But I signaled three times,
the code that I was making an indirect call.
Dragon-san!
King Cobra's assassin...
...isn't me!
I wasn't in Lulusia.
But...
I was worried about you!
Sorry.
Sabo!
Gee!
Why are you boys all like this?!
Morley!
Don't make me worry!
Sabo!
I'm really glad that you're back!
Welcome!
I remember you losers of Lulusia!
Sorry for what happened to your home.
I heard you wanted to
join the Revolutionary Army.
Yes! That's right!
First!
Get some rest.
Sort out your feelings first.
Thank you...
I heard about Kuma-san.
I'm sorry.
All your efforts have gone to waste.
He may have been programmed
to return to Mary Geoise at any moment.
No...
It must be harder on you two
than it is on me.
Sabo. Even the captains can't hear
what you have to say?
Yeah... It might endanger their lives
to know it.
What's it about?
This Reverie was tumultuous...
I'll tell you all about
what really happened...
at the Holy Land Mary Geoise!
doredake hashitte kita noka
How far I have run
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
Without knowing it, I counted scars
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one! Crocodile!
He is a former member of the Seven Warlords
and a Logia type Sand-Sand Fruit power user.
He can transform himself into sand
and dehydrate anything he touches!
His bounty is
1 billion 965 million berries.
He was born on September 5th
and likes crocodile meat and tomatoes!
He was ostensibly a hero
for hunting pirates.
But behind the scenes, he was a president of
Baroque Works, a secret criminal organization!
His goal was to take over the Kingdom of Alabasta
and get Pluton, an Ancient Weapon,
to establish a military nation.
Love for the kingdom
will be what destroys the kingdom.
But he was defeated by Luffy
and his plan failed.
He was sent to Impel Down, but he escaped
and got involved in the Paramount War.
He is now a co-leader of Cross Guild,
a new organization represented by Buggy.
He used to have a dream of
becoming the King of Pirates.
Will he go after the great treasure of
the One Piece again?
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!
Hi, everyone.
We'll look deep into the force
that opposes the World Government,
the Revolutionary Army!
We'll thoroughly explain to you their
relationship with Luffy-senpai and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Log of the Turbulent Revolution -
The Revolutionary Army Maneuvers in Secret!"
Luffy-senpai's gonna become the King of the Pirates!