mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Just give me...
...red-bean soup!
What?!
Olin-san!
Queen-sama!
"A Grudge Over Red-bean Soup!
Luffy Gets into a Desperate Situation!"
Red-bean soup...
Sniff, sniff...
Olin-san...
Olin is as strong as she was
when she was Big Mom!
Luffy!
What a strong old lady!
She's not just an old lady...
She's...
...an Emperor of the Sea!
No... way!
Queen-sama!
Don't scream so pathetically...
I'm not gonna get taken down...
...by that crappy attack!
I won't give you any red-bean soup!
I'll make a cracker out of you and eat you up!
Get squashed!
This is...
...a battle between a beast and a monster!
I'll have the head of the Emperor of the Sea!
The red-bean soup is all mine!
Red... bean... soup!
Red-bean soup!!
Hey...
Quit lying around, you damn lizard!
Stop, you old bag!
Don't you know who I am?!
Luffy!
Red... bean... soup!!
Give me red-bean soup!
Red-bean soup!
Give it to me!
Get down, old man!
U-Udon is...
Udon's in danger!
Thank goodness. They're...
Hey, are you okay?!
Shut up!
We don't need your pity.
We're not that helpless!
Queen-sama!
Queen-sama! Stay with us!
Queen-sama?
He passed out...
I can't believe that a man with a 1.3-billion-berry bounty
got knocked out in just two hits!
I can smell red-bean soup more strongly now!
She beat the formidable Queen so easily...
She's on another level...
That's how strong the Emperor of the Sea Big Mom is!
Report to Kaido-san!
Roger!
The Never-Opening Cell's been destroyed!
We don't know what's in it!
I believe it was chained up...
Not being able to escape,
it must've died inside.
EXECUTIVE TOWER IN THE EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
Roger! I'll report to Onigashima right away!
I smell red-bean soup this way!
Babanuki-san! Can we open fire?
No! Don't agitate her!
What's Kaido-san's order?!
Chief Warden! The thing is...
...the smails aren't able to get through!
None of us can reach Onigashima!
What?!
Hey! What's wrong?!
Hello! This is Building B...
Huh? The Smail isn't working!
Hello?!
Because of the turmoil outside,
security is so poor here.
Caribou is quite helpful.
The enemies are in close contact,
"They went that way" or "They're over here."
That communication uplink is a pain!
Now, here is the important part.
Look.
The Land of Wano's Smart Snails
have one disadvantage. They have weak signals!
SMART SNAIL (SMAIL FOR SHORT)
BOSS SNAIL
To compensate, every Smail's outgoing signal...
...is first sent to what's called a Boss Snail
that's set up in every region,
and it relays the signal to the receiving Smails.
I understand how the system works, but...
Come on! You're so thickheaded!
If I gobble up the Boss Snail in Udon...
What do you think will happen?
All of Udon will lose signal?!
That's correct!
I haven't been captured this long for nothing...
Incidentally,
I happen to know where the Boss Snail is.
Is that true?!
So trust me to cut their communications!
Why don't you go steal all the keys,
Raizo-chan?
Wait for me, Kawamatsu!
I will get you out at any cost!
Red-bean soup!
It's so close!
Where is the red-bean soup?!
Red-bean soup!
Oh?
Here it is!
This smell!
There's no mistake!
Red... bean... soup!
How sweet and rich the smell is!
And there is so much of it!
It was worth coming all the way here!
Now...
Babanuki-sama!
I have an urgent update!
What? I'm busy now!
That pot is actually empty!
Empty?!
What'll happen when Big Mom who is obsessed with food
finds out that there is no red-bean soup?!
Who will she be mad at?!
She may kill us all...
Red-bean soup!
Everyone, evacuate now!
Save yourselves!
I don't how bad it'll be,
but this is gonna be a disaster!
Damn! Who in the world ate it?!
I see. So she really wanted to eat it.
I understand why she's sad
because I wanna eat it again, too!
The red-bean soup was so delicious!
Straw hat man!
So...
--So...
So you're the one...
...who ate it!
Why's everyone looking at me?
Well, you just said...
...that you ate the soup out loud...
What?!
Did I say that out loud?!
The red-bean soup was so delicious!
I just said it silently to myself!
You do realize you just said it again, right?!
Luffytaro-san...
I finally found Luffy...
But as usual, you're in the center of trouble!
Hey...
Did you...
...eat all of the red-bean soup?!
You smell like red-bean soup!
Oh, no!
Red-bean soup!
That was close...
I forgot that if we step out of the ring,
we'll die!
I won't forgive you...
Wait a sec!
I'm begging you! Wait, Big Mom!
Again, the name Big Mom...
Who is that?!
And you who ate the soup! Who are you?!
What?!
You don't know who I am?!
Oh, yeah! I'm disguised as a samurai now,
so she doesn't recognize me!
Making Big Mom angry over food brings disaster...
If she's lost her senses
and slipped into a Hunger Pang attack now,
no one can stop her!
This is bad! Really bad!
It rang again!
We're in trouble...
If we get pushed once more, we'll be dead!
We can't yield even an inch!
If that pot was filled with red-bean soup,
I could have shared it with everyone from that town!
That town?
She means Okobore Town?!
This is sweet red-bean soup.
Go ahead, Olin-san, try it!
Whoa! It smells good!
Thank you!
So good!
It's delicious!
Everyone in that poor town was so kind to me...
So I wanted to bring back a lot of red-bean soup to them!
What?!
That delicious red-bean soup...
I wanted them to have it, too!
Sh... Sh...
She's not having a Hunger Pang attack?
It's her kindness!
She's rampaging because of her kindness!
Red-bean soup!
Why did you eat it?
Why did you eat it?!
You little brat!
Stop!
Old man!
Come off!
Damn! I won't let him die!
I'm not gonna die!
Come off!
Come off!!
This is it...
Come off!
Come off!!
What?! The collars!
What?
The collars came off!
Old man! What did I do?!
Yay!
--It came off!
--I can't believe it... That was...
You got away again!
Alright! Let's run, old man!
Straw hat man!
Before you forget that feeling,
protect me!
A moment of crisis will reveal your true power!
Come on!
Practice now?!
If I fail, you'll die!
I know!
What a fool.
Ryuo, huh?
Alright!
Red-bean soup!
Bring it on! Emperor of the Sea!
The enraged Big Mom is on a rampage!
She fights furiously against Luffy whose back is to the wall!
As the labor camp is about to be destroyed,
Luffy's enemy Queen plans a strategy to capture Big Mom!
What will happen to Luffy?!
And how will the deadly operation end up?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Stop the Emperor of the Sea! Queen's Secret Plan!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org