mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
The Never-Opening Cell's been destroyed!
We don't know what's in it!
I believe it was chained up...
Not being able to escape,
it must've died inside.
How sweet and rich the smell is!
And there is so much of it!
It was worth coming all the way here!
Red-bean soup!
The red-bean soup was so delicious!
Straw hat man!
So you're the one...
...who ate it!
"Stop the Emperor of the Sea!
Queen's Secret Plan!"
Why did you eat it?!
You little brat!
Old man!
Damn! I won't let him die!
I'm not gonna die!
Come off! Come off!
Forget it! That's enough!
Come off!!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Huh? Huh? What?
Old man!
The collars came off!
What did I do?! Oh, wow!
Yay!
I can't believe it...
That was...
You got away again!
Alright! Let's run, old man!
Straw hat man!
Before you forget that feeling,
protect me!
What are you saying?! Let's go!
A moment of crisis will
reveal your true power!
I won't let you get away!
Practice now?! Are you crazy?!
If I fail, you'll die!
I know!
Bring it on! Emperor of the Sea!
I can't do what Rayleigh did back then!
I'm going to remove your collar now.
Are you ready, girl?
Hold on, old man!
Don't be crazy! It'll explode!
We've seen a slave's collar explode before!
That's a bad idea! A very bad idea!
Are you sure about this, Luffy?!
It'll be all right. Just stay still.
I'm telling you, it's too dangerous!
It won't come off without the key!
It's ringing! What're we gonna do?!
Stop! Stop it!
Camie!
He took the collar off barehanded?!
Yes!
It was exactly the same as
what Rayleigh did back then!
That thing that I just did!
Even with two years of training,
I never came close to mastering it!
So that was Ryuo.
But I was so desperate.
I don't remember how I did it!
You can't get away now!
Straw hat man...
The Ryuo technique you just showed...
...was superior to
what I can teach you!
So I'm sure you can stop her!
Slam the monstrous woman's fist,
and save our lives!
I know you can do it!
Come on! Let's see what you've got!
You might die, you know?!
I don't mind!
Okay!
Is he trying to catch it?!
How reckless!
No...
I'm sure Luffy can do it!
Instead of straining myself,
I should allow Haki to flow to my fists!
Come on!
Luffytaro-san!
Luffy!
Luffy!!
So predictable!
Damn!
Sorry, old man! I failed!
Stay with me!
Ow, ow, ow...
Are you okay, old man?!
I-I used Ryuo to shield just in case...
Old man!
You're still alive?!
Listen to me...
All I can teach you is...
...the Ryuo technique
that covers the outside of your body...
That's what you call Haki...
Hey, stop talking!
Haki is...
...a very strong power that defends you like invisible armor
and can also be used offensively.
But if you take it up a notch,
the Haki that covers you
will become even stronger,
and it will enter your enemy's body
and destroy it from the inside!
Earlier, those steel collars...
...were destroyed from the inside
using your Haki!
You've already got it!
Old man...
You've already acquired the Haki
that covers your body!
You just don't realize it yet...
Believe in your power!
Hey! Don't die on me!
Hey! Old man!
He finally dropped dead?!
Hyogoro the Flower!
Old man! Hey!
Stay with me! Old man! Hey!
Hey, old man! Don't die on me! Hey!
Old man!!
Hey! Old man!
Don't die on me, old man!
Hey! Stay with me! Old man!
Hey! Don't die on me!
Hey!
Old man!!
How dare you eat the red-bean soup
that was for me and everyone else!
I won't forgive you!
Good luck! Straw hat man!
You're alive! Thank goodness!
You got away again!
I won't forgive you!
Tsk! He's alive! That damn Hyogoro!
How annoying!
Damn! Give up already!
Red-bean soup!
IRON 02
PRISON IRONWORKS, UDON
Hey, I can't make contact!
I heard that the Boss Snail disappeared!
What?!
Why's the earth rumbling?!
B-Big Mom?!
Stop!
I won't let you get away!
All hell broke loose.
Who's that young guy?
The furnace in the Prison
Ironworks has blown up!
What can we do?!
Big Mom is an Emperor of the Sea!
Even Queen-sama was no match for her...
We have no chance of stopping her!
Q-Queen-sama!
The Land of Wano is Kaido-san's territory.
I won't let that old bag
do whatever she wants!
Stop!
I have a plan.
There's only one chance.
Listen carefully!
You can't get away from me, brat!
You see, Big Mom is like a wild boar!
She'll charge forward going around Udon,
and loop back around here!
So set a trap here!
I'll get rid of her!
Damn you!
Take this!
Wait!
We must stop Olin-san!
Wait! We can't compete against her!
Leave her to Luffytaro!
What an interesting kid!
He singlehandedly turned
around a terrible situation!
We can get out now!
Great!
Keep going! Keep going!
RED-BEAN SOUP
Queen-sama! We're good to go!
Queen-sama! She's here!
Damn! She's so persistent!
Stop!
Red-bean soup!
Yes! She fell for it!
Ya-hoo!
It's empty!
You ate it all again!
Damn you!
No! I didn't eat that one!
Brachio...
...Bomber!
Yay! Bull's eye!
Hurrah for Queen-sama!
That's our Queen-sama!
He saved the Land of Wano!
Olin-san!
--Mama!
Mama!
My sweet babies!
How's that?!
Mama!
What the?!
Oh, yeah...
You've got to be kidding!
Now I remember everything!
Brutal ammunition made by Queen, the Plague Rounds,
dash all hope in the Excavation Labor Camp!
Getting shot means death!
The dreadful weapon discourages
the prisoners and Luffy becomes the target!
He's in trouble all by himself!
Is it all over for him?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Brutal Ammunition! The Plague Rounds Aim at Luffy!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org