You can't get away now!
流桜 Ryuo, Flowing Sakura
Straw Hat Man...
The Ryuo technique you just showed...
...was superior to
what I can teach you!
So I'm sure you can stop her!
Slam the monstrous woman's fist,...
...and save our lives!
I know you can do it!
Even Queen-sama was no match for her...
We have no chance of stopping her!
The Wano Country is Kaido-san's territory.
I won't let that old bag do whatever she wants!
Stop!
You see, Big Mom is like a wild boar!
She'll charge forward going around Udon,
and loop back around here!
So set a trap here!
I'll get rid of her!
Stop!
Oshiruko!
Queen-sama! She's here!
You ate it all again!
Brutal Ammunition!
The Plague Rounds Aim at Luffy
Mama! Mama! Mama!
Mama!
My sweet babies!
Oh, I have a headache...
What am I doing?
Oh, yeah!
I traveled all the way to the Wano Country
to take Straw Hat's head...
...and was thrown into the sea by the damn King.
After I washed up on the shore...
I went to the dirty little town...
and had Oshiruko there...
大看板 Okanban, All-Stars
Don't mess with a All-Star!
Damn! You gave me a lot of trouble!
I've had enough, you old bag!
Hey...
Why?
Why isn't she collapsing?
Did you...
...bash me in the head?
Yes... Now I remember everything...
I'm hungry...
Oshiruko...
No! No! That's not good!
What's the matter, Chopperemon-san?
H-Hey... This can't be true...
That didn't hurt her at all?
Oh...
You're Kaido's subordinate, Queen,
aren't you?
I'm doomed!
No way! No way! No way! No way!
I can't beat that monster!
She's like a different person now!
Anyway, I know that...
...you've got Oshiruko.
Just give it to me.
Oshiruko... Oshiruko...
What happened to her?
Give me Oshiruko!
Th-This is it!
W-What the...
Oh, Big Mom is...!
I-I guess I escaped death!
Guys!
海楼石 Kairoseki, Sea Prism Stone
Bring me 100 percent pure
Kairoseki cuffs and chains!
Hurry up!
Yes!
Wrap her body 100 times!
It's done!
All right!
It's not enough!
I don't feel safe yet!
Do something more!
Inject 100 shots of tranquilizer for savage animals!
Yes!
All right! Is the ship ready?!
Yes, it is!
Then, leave the minimum necessary number of guards
and the rest of you, get on board!
Babanuki! I'll leave the whole of Udon to you!
Y-Yes!
That old bag broke most of the doors in Udon!
So once I've left, lock Udon down
with the emergency gates!
Throw all prisoners into their cells
and set things right!
Count on me!
But there's one man -
Let's go!
There's no time to lose!
Let's take the old bag to Kaido-san!
Hurry up!
Set sail!
Advance at full speed! To Onigashima!
They're gone...
All right! Activate the emergency gates!
What is going on?!
I wonder if everyone's all right...
Momo-kun! The gate is closing!
It cannot be helped.
We promised them that we would wait here.
Trust in everyone. Let's stay here.
Let's go!
Wait for me, Aniki!
Have you closed all the gates?!
Yes, it's done!
Is the connection restored?!
No, not yet!
Currently, Udon is completely isolated!
There's no way to communicate with the outside!
What?!
In that case, I can do whatever I want!
I wish Big Mom and the balloon
were still here to fight,...
...but let's continue my training.
Oh, yeah. He freed himself.
I've always been free!
You're just a prisoner.
Don't push your luck.
I'm sorry...
but I'm gonna take over Udon!
I wish Big Mom and the balloon
were still here to fight,...
...but let's continue my training.
Oh, yeah. He freed himself.
I've always been free!
You're just a prisoner.
Don't push your luck.
I'm sorry...
...but I'm gonna take over Udon!
Catch Straw Hat Luffy!
Here they come!
Imagine Haki...
...flowing in my body...
I got you!
That's not it!
Go to hell!
Oh, why?!
That wasn't it!
I can't take down Kaido
just by hitting him from the outside with Haki...
To let Haki flow into an enemy...
If I can allow Haki to flow,...
...I can even break Kaido's tough scales!
Oh, no! I strained myself too much!
Screw you!
Damn! That wasn't it! No!
But...
...there are still this many enemies
to practice with!
I'll master Ryuo at any cost!
He never gives up. The Straw Hat Man...
Chopperemon-san, let's go!
Yeah!
To rescue Olin-san!
What?!
No! Forget about Olin!
I'm just glad she's gone!
We need to help Luffytaro, Kiku!
Why doesn't he try to run?
Let's go!
Okay!
Who are you guys?!
He transformed!
Is he a raccoon dog?!
You're so strong, Chopperemon-san!
What?!
Damn you!
No! This isn't even close!
You...!
Next!
What's wrong?! You fools! Just bring it on!
Otherwise, I'll forget the rush
that I finally got after all that trouble!
You bastard!
Shut your mouth!
That Straw Hat kid! He's full of energy!
Okay! Next!
What useless shits...
Chief Warden! Should we put the prisoners into cells
before they do something stupid?!
Yeah...
Luffytaro, he's fighting well...
Yeah, he's so strong.
It's possible...
There are fewer guards now.
Maybe we can do it!
Don't worry...
As they say, "One poison drives out another."
Daifugo, get it ready!
You want it? I see...
You wretched prisoners, listen carefully!
One of your friends, Luffytaro, is out of control
and we're in deep trouble...
You know what I mean, don't you?!
What is he talking about?!
Hey, what should we do?
Like we have a choice?
How could we fight him?
I see...
I guess you guys wanna
break the peace yourselves!
None of you mind getting executed because of
the actions of some guy who does whatever he likes?
The first offense, your arms will be cut off...
For the second, your legs...
And for the third...
You know, right?
Go! I know you guys can get Luffytaro
under control!
Huh? What are you talking about?
They're not gonna listen to you!
What?
Whaaat?!
Stop! I'm on your side!
Don't you wanna get out of here?!
Yes, we have resentment against the guards!
I admit that when you fought against them,
I felt so excited!
But even if we break out,
Kaido and Orochi will still be in charge!
We tried to avenge Kozuki Oden-sama!
But the pirate Kaido...
He killed our families and allies,
and beat the crap out of us!
Yasuie-sama's execution earlier...
...evoked the sense of fear and despair
that I felt back then...
Even if we can break out of here,
we have no place to go and have nothing to eat!
There is no freedom in this country anymore!
That's right!
You'd better just stay here and obey us!
Don't be so selfish!
No, you're being selfish!
You're a stranger from overseas.
I don't care if you run or fight...
But don't get us involved anymore!
Don't give us unnecessary hope again!
You guys...
Are you okay?!
Hey, stay with us!
Hey guys! You're in no position
to be concerned about others!
It's hot... It's hot... Help me!
Hey!
What's wrong?!
What's this?!
I told you to be careful!
That's a contagious plague!
One touch and you'll be infected!
I made them as an example!
If anyone does something stupid,
I'll shoot him!
Queen-sama loves to craft things.
It's his hobby to build mechanical weapons
and create viruses.
It's hot!
These are Queen-sama's special...
...Plague Rounds!
Straw Hat! Did you think that
the prisoners would fight together with you?!
It's too bad that their rebellious spirits
are already crushed!
Shut up! I won't get shot!
You idiot! Didn't you see?!
If someone gets shot, they'll pass it on!
Hey, spread out!
We're all gonna get infected!
That's fine!
We'll all die here...
Damn! If I were allowed to tell them everything,
they'd change their minds!
This is it for you, Straw Hat!
Hey! Tell them everything, Straw Hat kid!
That there is still hope!
That there is one last chance
to take down Kaido!
I heard a voice from the Never-Opening Cell!
So he's still alive...
Chief Warden!
I thought some kind of beast was in there!
Oh, yeah. You guys didn't know.
It's not a beast that's held in that cell.
"If we keep feeding him fish...
...that are contaminated with industrial wastewater, he'll die."
That's what Orochi-sama ordered 13 years ago,
he meant it as an execution...
We couldn't disobey Orochi-sama's order,
so we kept him alive,...
...but he should have been executed
before anyone else.
In that cell, we're holding...
...a member of the Akazaya Nine!
What?! No way!
I thought they were all dead!
Kill him now!
It'll be dismissed as an accidental death!
That laugh...
I'm sure it was Kawamatsu-san!
Hey!
Kawamatsu-san!
I'm on my way!
There's the filthy one!
He's one of the legendary Akazaya Nine?!
I'll get the credit!
Is it a needle?!
No, it's a fishbone!
In the dark cell, I have thought about my lord,...
...and endured for 13 years...
No matter how many poisonous fish I consume,...
...I, Kawamatsu will never be defeated by you small fries!
The Akazaya Nine! Kawamatsu the Kappa!
I am alive and kicking!
Here comes Kawamatsu,
the Wano Country's greatest yokozuna!
The members of the Akazaya Nine and...
...Boss Hyogoro reveal
their true identities and join hands with Luffy!
The prisoners are moved seeing their strong allies!
In the tumultuous Prisonder Mine,
Luffy's rebellious spirit stirs up a storm!
Next time on One Piece!
Start Fighting Back!
Luffy and the Akazaya Samurai!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Start Fighting Back!
Luffy and the Akazaya Samurai!