mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
I will avenge everyone!
Even through difficult times,
I could carry on without giving up...
...because of one wish.
To realize that, I need like-minded allies...
I need the help of you all
who are living in the Land of Wano!
We all share one wish!
Take back the Land of Wano!
Everyone... For the last 20 years,
thank you for waiting for us!
I am the heir to the Daimyo
of the Land of the Wano...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
Now is the time to rise up!
"Orochi's Hunting Party!
The Ninja Group vs. Zoro!"
Zorojuro!
Don't be afraid! Run!
Okay!
I'll deal with them here. You go ahead!
I'm sorry. Please be careful!
There are so many!
Zorojuro-san!
Two-Sword Style!
Tower Climb Return!
Zorojuro!
You're a serious criminal
who pointed a sword at Orochi-sama!
I'll make you regret
standing against Orochi-sama!
Zorojuro! Prepare yourself!
Damn you...
Is that it?
How many ninja are there?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I am sorry for getting in your way...
Yeah...
Well, don't worry.
If you get killed,
I wouldn't be able to face Momonosuke.
You wanna go back to the
house in the snow, right?
It does not matter
as long as I can hide myself.
I wanna get back to the
guy who stole my sword.
Of course, I will guide you to him.
Bandit's Bridge in Ringo, right?
I have to get it back
before the great battle.
I don't feel comfortable without it.
I guess I made Orochi really mad...
His hunting party's so pesky.
I wonder if Otoko is doing okay...
Yasuie!
Daddy!
After such a horrible thing
happened to her father...
I was not able to stay by her side,
so I am worried...
She's with my crew!
She should be fine, at least physically...
I won't forgive Orochi!
I'll avenge Tonoyasu at any cost!
I wish... I could...
...kill him myself!
What did you say?!
You let them get away?!
How about the ronin who attacked me?!
I am sorry...
I am disappointed in you guys!
But we captured a man named Trafalgar.
Tra... falgar?
Who the hell is that?!
Just like Straw Hat,
he is one of their masterminds!
So, now we have two heads of the intruder group
under control!
Where is he now?
In the world of pirates,
betrayal never goes out of style!
Even after torturing him,
we can use him in so many ways.
That sounds good.
What is the status of the capital?
Do not worry!
We put it on high alert
and stationed patrol-force samurai
and ninja all over the town!
Until those intruders are all caught,
I will see to it that you are well defended!
If you see any of these faces,
report it immediately!
These are all wanted posters?!
Keep in mind that letting them walk away
or hiding them will be considered conspiracy!
Gee...
SANGORO THE SOBA COOK
We should steer clear of
the capital from now on.
Not just the capital!
We're wanted across the country!
SHINOBU THE KUNOICHI
Wherever we go,
Orochi's assassins will be on the lookout.
To catch us!
Our wanted posters have been spread spread
throughout the Land of Wano!
So the capital isn't the only place
that's dangerous!
We're considered diabolical outlaws.
But in a way, our business
in the capital is done.
Our objective was to find
samurai with the moon tattoo.
But all those samurai are...
...Behind bars now.
Get us out of here already!
Shut up!
After Tonoyasu gave that speech risking his own life,
I thought they'd be considered innocent...
It might not be that easy.
The Prisoners' Quarters are vast.
I assume that about a thousand people got caught.
Hey, haven't they been freed yet?
You think Orochi-sama would say,
"I made a mistake"?
He won't admit that he was wrong.
You're right.
But now we know that they're our allies...
We definitely need their help!
We've got to do something!
Law's crew must be in there, too.
By the way, Shinobu-chan,
what are they doing?
Oh, they're making Sky Boats!
Sky Boats?
The Fire Festival is approaching,
so they're preparing for it.
They've lost two big figures.
I bet they don't feel like having a festival.
No! Actually, it's the opposite!
The Fire Festival in the Flower Capital
is an event to honor the dead.
The bigger the festival, the better the
chance that your thoughts will reach the dead.
Hmmm... So it's an important
festival for them.
W-What is going on?!
Straw hat man!
Luffy!
Don't worry. The medicine is working.
He'll get better soon!
The medicine has worked already?!
Luffy! Don't push yourself!
Big Bro! Are you okay?!
Some... thing... to... eat...
What?! What did you say?!
Bring me something to eat!
Go ahead and eat a lot!
--I want more!
--Too fast!
I'm glad that you got better!
Chopperemon-san!
All the others are safely neutralized, too.
What a relief.
I'm amazed by your skill!
Yes! Well done!
Your compliments don't
make me happy, you fools!
I feel a surge of power!
Thanks, everyone!
Big Bro!
Wait for me, Kaido!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah, sorry to make you worry...
I heard that you guys got caught!
--Luckily, we escaped.
--I see!
Oh, yeah!
Take a look at this...
Before he died, a Daimyo named Yasuie...
What?! Yasuie?!
He drew the symbol and showed it
to the people in the prison.
Wait a minute...
There are two lines added on the snake?!
Yeah, that's right!
I think the symbol's meaning
was altered by those lines.
The people from the Land of Wano
knew what it meant.
It's Yasuie's last message.
This is very important!
I'll make sure to hand it to Kin'emon!
--I'm counting on you!
--Okay!
If you need help, come to Amigasa Village!
Okay! Say hi to everyone else for us!
Captain...
It's our fault...
Dammit!
I'm sorry, Captain!
What did you do with our polar bear?
With your ability,
you can get them out in an instant.
What kind of fool would keep all the hostages
in one conspicuous place.
I'll put you in that jail, too.
You can't take me down.
Ouch!
Shachi!
I have four lives now.
You can only cut me up
after you've killed...
...the three from your own crew.
I have no choice...
A boss must take responsibility
for his henchmen's blunder...
I'll cut both you and them at once!
Damn you!
Captain!
The bargaining chip is your lives.
"Bargain"?
What do you mean by that?!
If I refuse, Trafalgar Law...
...will take my life along with yours.
A threat from a man
unwilling to bet on tomorrow...
...is something that raises concern
for my own life.
Captain, I'm sorry! We blew it!
These are the lives of you three!
It's a complete liberation...
You have no problem, do you, Trafalgar?
No, no!
Don't go! Captain!
Listen, guys.
Don't ever tell Straw Hat-ya and the others
that I got caught!
What? Why?!
Captain!
No, wait!
Don't go!
Captain!
I'm sorry...
Everyone... Because of our blunder...
...Captain is...!
We can't hang around and do nothing!
We're the Heart Pirates!
Let's take our captain back!
Our Captain's life is more important
than Kin'emon's plan!
Trafalgar Law!
Damn you!
That's enough.
What's the matter?
You're acting strange.
No, it's nothing.
Let's get it over with.
Yeah, it's an easy job.
It'll be over as soon as you spit it out.
His people and the Straw Hats are connected.
What are you up to in this Land of Wano?
Tell us everything.
To take down Kaido, the Straw Hats and
their allies from the Land of Wano
make their moves for the great battle
and deepen their bonds!
Meanwhile, at Onigashima, Big Mom and Kaido,
finally meet each other creating a tense atmosphere.
It's a volatile situation!
What will happen to the Land of Wano?!
On the next episode of One Piece! "Tension Rises
in Onigashima! Two Emperors of the Sea Meet?!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!