The Roger Pirates are disbanded!
After reaching the last island, Laugh Tale,
the Roger Pirates disbanded.
Oden, who returned to the Wano Country,
learned that Orochi is sitting as the Shogun.
I understand the way Orochi does things!
Guys! Protect my family!
Oden-san!
Protect Kuri!
Sad News
The Opening of the Great Pirate Era
Oden-san!
Are you going to attack Orochi?!
Toki, you don't have to be afraid anymore.
No! Don't go!
Orochi will stop at nothing!
I know how you feel,
but it is too dangerous to charge in with no plan!
I'll leave Kuri to you...
I don't understand complicated things,
but I think this is what happened.
A fool took over the Wano Country!
With the help of a strong pirate,...
a weak fool took advantage of the period of isolation
during which no one would intervene...
...and is trying to...
...turn this country into hell!
Drink!
Dance!
Sing!
Be merry!
It's a beautiful country...
I won't let him turn it into hell!
H-Hey!
Y-Yeah!
It's an emergency!
Kozuki Oden is heading toward the Flower Capital!
Report to Orochi-sama immediately!
Orochi-sama! Please respond! Orochi-sama!
Was that...?!
Oden-sama?!
Oden-sama has returned?!
He's the true heir!
Will he become the Shogun?!
Orochi's dominion will end!
Leave, Kozuki Oden!
This is Shogun Orochi-sama's castle!
You cannot enter without permission!
Shogun Orochi! Please evacuate!
What? What are you talking about?!
Kozuki Oden invaded the castle!
What?!
Orochi...
Orochi...!
Orochi!
Orochi!!
W-Wait a minute! Oden-sa... O-Oden!
Think twice!
If you cut me up, Kaido won't just take it lying down!
Think what'll happen to this country!
I will.
After I slice you up!
I forgot... he's...
He's crazy!
Orochi!
Don't do it!
What the?!
What's this?!
Is it glass?! No!
Come out, Orochi!
Orochi!
No need to be scared, Orochi-sama...
Trust my Bari Bari technique.
In theory,
my barriers won't allow anyone to come closer.
Your strength means nothing, Oden!
That's right.
If you were a pirate,
I'm sure you're really familiar with...
...the superhuman powers of the Devil Fruits!
So you're a power-user!
That's right.
People in this country call them magic-users...
Oden, if anger and violence were the answer,...
...the Daimyos from other regions
would already have done it!
No one can kill me!
Orochi!
I heard, for whatever reason,
my father named you as a proxy Shogun...
...until my return!
Then, yield the throne to me now!
I wasn't going to become such a big shot,...
...but I can make it a somewhat
better country than you!
Well, unfortunately,...
...that's not what your father, Sukiyaki, said.
What do you mean?
It's good to have you back, Oden!
What?! Father?!
How are you alive...
Who the Daimyos and all the
other fools believed was...
...me!
They believed a lie from this old hag
who transformed herself...
マネマネの実 Mane Mane no Mi,
Clone-Clone Fruit (Imitation)
...with the Mane Mane no Mi power!
The whole country believed it
and let me have the Shogun's post!
So I don't have to switch positions with you!
Now there's no way to know
what the real Sukiyaki was thinking...
What did you do to my father?!
Did he really die of an illness?!
That day, upon the crowd that was looking...
...up at the castle cheering for
the return of the Kozuki Family,...
...poisoned arrows rained down from nowhere.
Two people were wounded
and lost their sight after a bout of bloody vomit.
The other townspeople
who took shelter in the disarray...
...saw a big dragon
up in the darkened sky of the capital!
He grew up as a wild man, but he became the Daimyo of Kuri and went out to sea,...
...and matched up evenly with
the world's greatest pirates...
Then, he returned home
having become a lot stronger.
The invincible Kozuki Oden!
Don't worry.
Oden-sama will save this country.
Oden-sama!
Oden-sama! We were waiting for you!
He was expected to become a savior for the people
who suffered the power of evil...
Oden-sama?
A few hours later, Kozuki Oden...
...stripped himself down
in front of the Shogun Orochi's castle...
...and acted like a fool.
I knew you could do it!
Oh, radish, ganmo!
Chikuwa and eggs!
One, two, three, go ahead and eat!
If it didn't boil...
...it wouldn't be Oden!
Orochi and Kaido's subordinates
laughed at him.
One, two, three...
Having groveled in the dirt and earned
a small amount of money, the big man went home.
The Wano Country's true
heir, Kozuki Oden's return...
...was the nation's last hope, so to speak.
But people were completely let down
and deeply disappointed.
And eventually, they even became angry.
Kuri's silly lord, Kozuki Oden!
The snake's stare petrified him with terror!
If you laugh, you lose! Here we go!
Konbu, important!
Konbu is important!
The essential factor for
the taste is the stock!
If it didn't boil...
...it wouldn't be Oden!
Oden showed up in the capital once a week,...
...and clowned around in front of the castle
to earn a small amount of money.
Even on rainy days.
Or windy days.
Or snowy days.
We are begging you, Oden-sama!
Please tell us the truth!
What did you and Orochi talk about?!
Why are you doing this?!
Even the people of Kuri who believed in you all this time
finally gave up on you.
What do you mean why?
I dance naked and get paid every week.
That's my job!
Word of his strange behavior in the capital
traveled to Kuri, too.
Daikon, ganmo, chikuwa and eggs!
Konnyaku, chikuwabu, hanpen, potatoes!
Oh, don't forget shirataki noodles, too!
Don't be a man like him! Pathetic!
If you become Orochi's dog,
cut your belly like a samurai!
Konbu, important! Life, important!
The essential factor for
the taste is the stock!
A year later...
Father!
The Shogun's messenger brought this for you.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
Roger...
Inherited will...
People's dreams... The tide of the times...
As long as people seek the answer of freedom,...
...these things will never cease to be!
Did you say that you're gonna die soon,
Roger?
Yeah, it's only a matter of time.
Do you know what people of the World Government
call me these days?
"Gold Roger."
What? Is that your real name?
No, no!
My name is Gol D. Roger.
I meet people with "D"
in their names sometimes.
I have a crew member who has it.
His name is Teach.
What does "D" stand for?
Ah, do you wanna know that?
Alright, I tell you.
It's a story from way back...
After receiving a foreign newspaper
from the Shogun Orochi, Oden...
...ran along the seacoast,
cried out loud, then, laughed...
...and cried again...
Roger!
All right, let's get this over with quickly.
Hey, King of the Pirates!
Where did you hide all
the treasure you found?!
You got it, didn't you?!
That legendary treasure!
That great treasure!
The One Piece!
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
24 years before the present day,...
...the world went wild over the execution of
the King of the Pirates, Gold Roger,...
...and to get the enormous wealth...
...and the great treasure of
the One Piece he left behind,...
...all sorts of people took to the sea.
That was the beginning
of the Great Pirate Era.
Roger!
You're unbelievable!
You lived quite a life!
Orochi's nefarious plan is revealed!
He uses any means necessary...
...for his evildoing and Oden
finally erupts in anger.
To save the country,...
...Oden and the Akazaya members face
Kaido, their domination-plotting nemesis.
The legendary raid that will go down to
posterity is about to be launched!
Next time on One Piece!
Raid!
Oden and the Akazaya Nine!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Raid!
Oden and the Akazaya Nine