mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
"The Castle on Fire!
The Fate of the Kozuki Clan!"
Oden-sama!
We were mistaken...
Oden-sama... He did everything for us...
I cannot believe he sacrificed his own life
to win people's trust...
Damn Kozuki Oden!
He created a mess...
Now his son must bear
the burden of being in the spotlight.
Kozuki was this country's hope!
Oden-sama was
the true Shogun of the Land of Wano!
The true Shogun?!
I am the Shogun!
"If it wasn't boiled"?!
Just die when boiled!
Damn Oden! Damn Oden! Damn Oden!
Screw him!
Why are you just standing there?!
Chase the samurai!
Eliminate the Kozuki!
Eradicate them!
Thus, one legend has ended,
and the new legend will be passed down
to the stars of the next stage.
Toki-sama, we have just received
news of Oden-sama's death...
They said that he died a heroic death...
Toki...
When the time comes, read this.
Good luck in battle...
"Toki, I see the end coming.
If I fail,
someone who can take down Kaido
won't appear anytime soon.
20 years from now,
a massive war that could divide the ocean in two
will probably erupt.
That means, 20 years from now,
the leading figures of that massive war
will surge into the New World.
They will be the ones to bring down Kaido!
A long winter is coming to the Land of Wano.
Toki, I want you to use your power.
If I die."
I entrust you with Enma and Ame-no-Habakiri.
Give my swords to our children.
I think they're still too young
to handle a sword...
Aren't you sad?
I'm sentenced to death!
You're not going to die, are you?
That's my wife!
If I cry, you'll laugh at me.
We don't want to be your weakness.
Please, Oden-san.
Look ahead 20 years.
Where did they go?
Eliminate them as soon as you find them!
Is everyone okay?!
Kin-san, what should we do?
You know what to do!
We're gonna knock them all out!
Wait!
We can't just attack without any plan.
Do you wanna throw away your life?!
I can't neglect seeking vengeance
for Oden-sama anymore!
You must! It's pointless to fight them now.
Let go of me, you coward!
What?! Did you call me a coward?!
Yeah! Or you're a heartless jerk
who doesn't feel a thing about
Oden-sama's death at all!
All you-gara do is rant,
so don't give me attitude!
You can't just die for nothing!
Do you wanna betray Oden-sama's trust in us?!
Remember what he said!
How was the outside world?
To sum up the trip, I'd say...
...it was the best adventure ever!
Did you stop by Zou?
Yeah! Of course!
Zou and the Kozuki Clan historically
have a strong bond with each other.
The Minks are tough warriors.
Keep that in mind, guys.
When in a pinch, head for Zou!
I'm sure they'll be of tremendous help.
Oden-sama, what do you mean by a pinch?
What do I mean? A pinch is a pinch.
I'm counting on you two as well.
I'm kind of embarrassed-meow.
Let's work even harder, cat.
We're in a pinch now!
We must take everyone to Zou!
Shut up, stupid dog!
I'll fight! If it kills me, so be it!
You're stupid! You dumb cat!
Fine!
If you're eager to die,
I'll grant your wish!
Bring it on!
Enough!
We have a mission in Kuri!
Save Toki-sama, Momonosuke-sama,
and Hiyori-sama, and flee to Zou!
And eventually, fulfill Oden-sama's dream
to open up the country!
I will never allow you to waste your life!
An enemy?!
Everyone! Please relax!
Shinobu!
I collected all of these for you.
Boy...
For the future of this country,
you all must survive!
Thank you, Shinobu.
You are a great help.
No, it's nothing...
We are heading for Oden Castle in Kuri!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Say, Kin-sama...
Do you think I can be one
of Kozuki's retainers?!
We are all self-proclaimed retainers.
So it's up to you!
Okay!
I found them! They're here!
Kill all the descendants of the Kozuki!
--Kiku!
--Okay!
Go to hell!
--Thanks!
--No problem!
Shut up!
What?!
You care about the enemies,
you disloyal bastard!
Are you-gara the spy
that Kaido was talking about, dog?!
Screw you!
This all happened
because you teased Kaido and Orochi!
It's like you-gara killed Oden-sama!
What?!
I will take everyone to Zou!
If I let you,
we're all gonna be dead before reaching Zou!
Dogstorm! Cat Viper! That's enough!
Dog-chan! Cat-chan!
What idiots!
Let go of me!
What's that?!
Don't go help them! We don't have time!
Too many enemies...
Give me a hand, Ashura!
Okay!
Son of a...
Denjiro! Ashura!
Advance, Kin'emon!
Take over the future of the Kozuki
and Oden-sama's dream!
I'll go help them!
Run!
Don't look back!
Advance!
Dammit!
My apologies!
Forgive me!
To Oden Castle!
Shoot fire arrows!
Kaido-san?!
Mother...
Don't worry!
I'll make sure you two escape!
There is a way out of this!
Father!
Up you go!
Stop! That's too high, Oden!
Even from this high up in the sky,
you can't see the whole thing.
That's what the world is like,
Momonosuke, Hiyori.
Take a good look at the things
you can't see in the Land of Wano.
It's so shiny, just like treasure!
Treasure, huh?
It's funny you mention that.
That's my son.
Broaden your knowledge, Momonosuke.
I'll teach you all I know.
What type of girl do you like?
Too young!
When you cut people,
think of them as chikuwa.
Inappropriate!
You've gotten better, Hiyori.
I like that song!
Really?! It's called Moon Princess!
I'll try to get even better.
What a beautiful song.
Play it at my funeral.
Hey, Momo! Don't make your sister cry!
You made her cry!
What I said earlier?
I'm sorry. I was just kidding!
You were?!
I'm not gonna die!
Mother!
Mother! Mother!
Your name?
I'm gonna fall!
It's too high! I'm scared...
I'm gonna die!
Your father was a silly lord.
Your death will end the Kozuki Clan...
You're wrong!
Your father is a great man and you are...
My father was a great samurai...
...and I'm...
...the one
who will govern this country someday!
Shallow words
and a dream someone put into your mouth...
I didn't know you were so young...
What's your name?!
Say it!
Mo...
Father!
Somebody, help!
I've lost interest...
I can't believe that's Oden's son!
Roast to death along with the castle!
Come on! Hurry up!
I'm sorry!
Even though we were there...
we let Oden-sama be...
Lift your head up.
Toki-sama, it's dangerous here!
Let's get out!
I will stay.
You cannot!
Let's get out of here!
Toki-sama! We will protect you
as long as we breathe!
Toki-sama!
Leave... to the future!
The future?
People can never go back to the past...
But you can go forward into the future.
Mother?
No, I don't want that!
I will stay here with you!
Mother, please don't do that!
Mother! Mother!
Brother!
Brother...
Mother, where's Brother?
Mother?
Kawamatsu, look after Hiyori.
Yes, ma'am!
Where are you going?
I'll catch up to you later,
so listen to Kawamatsu and be a good girl.
Okay.
--Don't let her get away!
--Kill her!
Damn!
Toki, you came looking
for it, too, didn't you?
From 800 years ago,
seeking the day that the world turns upside down...
Then, jump 20 years into the future!
And what you seek is...
No dinner for you today, Oden-san.
What?! Well, I'm not making any money,
so it can't be helped.
That's not why!
What is it?! I don't get it...
You said a horrible thing to me!
A horrible thing?
You just told me to jump 20 years into the future
all by myself!
Well, considering the purpose of your trip,
I thought it was better...
It's changed!
What?!
It's changed...
...since I met you...
BAKURA TOWN, KURI
I'm scared, Grandma.
Something feels different tonight...
We're doomed...
We'll receive divine punishment because
we didn't fully trust the
Kozuki Clan and Oden-sama.
The endless night will begin...
Oden-san, I came running away from the past.
I always thought if I jumped to the future,
someone would...
...would do it...
Toki-sama.
You are the moon unaware of the dawn.
May your purpose be fulfilled...
But I can help!
...and cast nine shadows on
the night woven of 20 years
and you shall know the
brilliance of the dawn!
Oden-san...
Hope for the future was handed down by Oden!
The Akazaya members scramble
to avenge their lord and save the Land of Wano,
and their persistance pays off
as allies join the fight!
Fly the battle flag high, Straw Hats!
Advance to the battlefield, Onigashima!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Back to the Present Day! 20 Years Later!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!