Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
The Akazaya members who
lost Oden were scattered.
Leave... to the future!
Princess! This is the Kappa Dance!
Then 20 years later,
Orochi received a letter.
They came jumping from that day 20 years ago!
Anyway, your spy is quite competent.
Listen, he's a trustworthy man...
That's right.
I killed those who slayed your parents.
But our revenge is just started!
Live your life as a real Kozuki retainer,
and die as a Kozuki retainer
without letting anyone know!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR A PLACE TO DIE
IT'S AN HONOR
"The Sea Is For Pirates!
Raid! To Onigashima!"
Plenty of troops for the
raid are gathering...
...at twilight today, the day of the Fire Festival,
at Tokage Port.
Head for Onigashima!
Kaido...
...will be taken down by us!
Yeah!
That's how it was supposed to be...
Not a single ship is in sight!
Where are the four thousand soldiers?!
It seems like this port was attacked!
At twilight on the day of the Fire Festival,
at Tokage Port!
This is the rendezvous port!
Why hasn't anyone come?!
Where did they go?!
Luffy-dono, where are you?!
Hyogoro-dono, please respond!
Dogstorm Musketeers!
Law-dono!
Jibuemon of Kibi!
We are Kozuki Oden's retainers!
From 20 years ago...
We came from 20 years ago
to avenge our lord!
We should have died at that time!
So we came to die for a cause!
However,
it takes more than just our lives!
The enemy has 30 thousand soldiers!
We need help!
Somebody, respond!
--Please help!
--Enough, Kin'emon!
Look at the sky and sea!
We are already abandoned even by heaven!
No one will help us!
The view of the Land of Wano is magnificent!
Take this!
Strong Right!
Enma, huh?
Once I get used to it,
I'm gonna be even stronger, right?
We're here to win against Kaido!!
We don't need allies standing in our way!
I am counting on you guys!
Yeah, leave it to us!
See you at the port!
Yeah!
Stop, you all!
Taking that small boat is like suicide!
If we miss this opportunity...
we have to wait for a year.
But we cannot hide anymore.
They will find out that we took control of Udon soon.
Kaido's whole army will come to hunt rebels.
Do not go!
I forbid you to go!
Kin'emon! Ashura!
Kanjuro! Raizo! Kiku!
Kawamatsu!
Dogstorm!
None of the expected 4,200 troops arrived,
and there were signs of destruction
at the port...
The weather is raging!
There is no escaping!
Wait! Are you going to give it all up?!
Everyone!
We are not giving up, Momonosuke-sama!
Since we are a small team,
we will be able to sneak in,
and point a sword at Kaido's neck
before anyone realizes!
As long as we live, we will not give up!
Something is not right!
This means our plan has been leaked again!
Why are they so prepared?!
How did they know that we were coming?!
Maybe there is a spy in your castle.
I was... I mean I am sure
everyone was thinking the same thing!
I did not want to think so...
But there is probably a spy among us!
To be honest, I do not want to know now!
Kin-sama! That's not like you!
You must find the spy and cut them off
and move on!
Otherwise, we can't move forward!
There is no way they will confess!
Somewhere in my mind, I'd suspected there was a spy,
but I turned a blind eye to it.
This is the price we must pay!
How long has this person been betraying us?
And why?!
Wait! We must not suspect one another now!
If we become paranoid and start fighting each other,
we play right into the enemy's hands!
But if we keep the person alive,
we'll lose our already slim chance at winning!
Besides...
...this person betrayed Oden-sama...
I cannot let it go!
I agree with Kiku, Kin!
We have all eaten from the same pot
and shared the same hardships.
Even if there is a spy...
that person must have a compelling reason!
Perhaps blackmail by Kaido and Orochi?
That person must have been through a lot!
I am sorry that I did not notice...
Because of my incompetence,
one of my colleagues was coerced into spying!
How can you be so naive?!
If it were not for that person,
Oden-sama might still be here with us!
I...
...do not want a quarrel amongst ourselves.
But...
I understand how Kiku feels, too!
Kin! Let's clear it all up!
By acknowledging that it was me!
Kanjuro?!
Stop joking...
We were all almost boiled to death!
That's right.
I could've fulfilled my role
by dying with you guys!
One of the Akazaya Nine...
Evening Shower Kanjuro
who pledged his loyalty to Oden...
That man never existed!
I shared joys and concerns with you guys every day
and earned your complete trust...
I didn't hate anyone nor mean to hurt them.
I just kept sending information
to Orochi-sama...
So you are saying
it has all been a lie from the beginning?
Why would you do that?!
I've been persecuted since I was a child
and my parents were killed in front of me...
Since then, I've only been able to live
by playing someone other than myself.
Because I myself couldn't
feel or think anything.
Evening Shower Kanjuro...
That's just a role
that Orochi-sama has given me.
My real name is...
Kurozumi Kanjuro!
Isn't that enough reason?
The first plan was leaked...
...not because Law's
subordinates spilled it...
It was me who informed them.
Yasuie beautifully covered it up and
changed the rendezvous point in exchange for his life.
That was impressive...
I gave a new rendezvous point.
It is not much, but that is
all I can do with my life!
But once I got the message,
his death became meaningless.
When Jack appeared at Zou
where no one can reach without a Vivre Card,
you were wondering why,
weren't you, Dogstorm?
That's right! I gave it to him!
And I leaked everything about
the latest plan to Orochi-sama, too!
Do it!
Roger!
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KIBI AND UDON
I guess Orochi-sama blew up and blocked...
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KURI AND UDON
...all the roads that lead to Tokage Port.
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN RINGO AND HAKUMAI
As well as the Straw Hats' ship...
It's no wonder no one has come.
ITACHI PORT, KURI
Why didn't you suspect any of us?!
Why didn't you suspect your people
before all this happened?
You knew something wasn't right!
All this time! About everything!
Hey, it was true!
As Orochi-sama said, there are a group of people
who are heading to Onigashima in a boat!
That's too hilarious!
I can't believe it!
They're really the Akazaya members from that time!
And one of them is our spy!
Are you the one?!
Yes, indeed.
Kanjuro!
I would've felt great as an actor
to be swallowed by the sea
with you guys without revealing myself,
but Orochi-sama stopped me this time.
He said, "Good job. The play is over."
Kanjuro?!
Momonosuke-sama!
Orochi-sama also said this!
"Come to Onigashima with Momonosuke!"
Kin'emon!
Momonosuke-sama!
How did Kanjuro get there at the port?!
Then this is...
A drawing?!
The Kanjuro that we know can't draw this...
We got Momonosuke!
Kill all the rest!
Yeah!
Momonosuke-sama!
Kin-sama! Don't be reckless!
If I let him kidnap Momonosuke-sama,
I'll be too ashamed to see Oden-sama
in the afterlife!
Kin-sama...
Guys! We don't have time to talk!
Regain balance!
This is it!
Gee, you guys.
How can you sleep under such circumstances!
Honestly!
Is the ship repaired?
After I eat, sleep, and wake up,
I'll be the strongest I've ever been!
What?!
Fire!
Don't tell me...!
Sorry for being a little late!
Who is that?!
I thought we sank all the enemy ships!
Oh, no! The boat's gonna sink!
There's something in the water!
How foolish are you guys
to go out on the stormy sea in that small boat?!
What?! You are...
Don't underestimate the sea,
you damn samurai!
Hey!
This time from the opposite side!
I saw a ridiculous number of ships and samurai
gathering at the other port.
Who are they?!
H-He is...!
They were in my way,
so I wanted to sink them!
Luffy-dono! You're all okay?!
So you came after all, Jaggy!
Straw Hat! I won't let you have Kaido's head!
What in the world is going on?
I didn't hear about any of this!
Luffy!
This isn't what we were told!
All we were told to do is
sink the samurai on a boat!
They're pirates!
The pirates of the Worst Generation
who were supposed to be in prison!
You guys!
How could you mess with the samurai's boat?!
You're no sea experts,
don't be reckless!
You guys should stand back!
The sea is for pirates to fight on!
The three pirates aiming to become
the new conqueror of the sea, Luffy, Kid, and Law!
They hoist their fighting spirits and challenge
Kaido's giant fleet with their ultimate techniques!
A fierce sea battle erupts on the boundless ocean!
No one can stop them!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Worst Generation Charges in!
The Battle of the Stormy Sea!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!