Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
There is probably a spy among us!
Kin! Let's clear it all up!
By acknowledging that it was me!
My real name is...
Kurozumi Kanjuro!
Kanjuro!
Luffy!
Fire!
After I eat, sleep, and wake up,
I'll be the strongest I've ever been!
Sorry for being a little late!
Don't underestimate the sea,
you damn samurai!
Out of my way! Or I'll sink you all!
Why don't you retreat?!
The sea is for pirates to fight on!
"The Worst Generation Charges in!
The Battle of the Stormy Sea!"
Luffy-dono! I am glad!
I am glad that you came!
You came for us!
Law-dono!
That guy is...
...Luffy-dono's friend!
I cannot believe he came, too!
The Worst Generation!
Why are they here?!
I thought there were only remnants of the Akazaya!
Let's get them first! Aim!
Oh, no!
Our Sunny!
This is perfect for trying out my new sword!
Green Star, Skull Blast Grass!
I did it!
Way to go!
Yes!
Kin'emon! Everyone!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Don't give up hope!
We still have a chance to win
as long as there are people who fight with us!
They showed off as usual...
Enjoy crushing those small fry!
All I want is...
...Kaido's head!
What's this all about?!
Why's Luffy's clan here?!
Not only them, I heard Law was jailed!
Let go of me, Kanjuro!
I reported all about Kin'emon's plan
and the circumstances to Orochi-sama!
"Changed from Habu Port to Tokage Port.
Kozuki Hiyori is alive somewhere in the north," huh?!
Don't tell me Orochi-sama
didn't take any measures!
I can't believe it!
The lion ship appeared undamaged?!
We blew up that ship last night ourselves!
Yeah... We received an order from Orochi-sama
and went to the beach of Kuri.
Did you find the ship?
Yes. We found it.
But you sure about this?
Just do as I say!
Do it!
Roger!
I knew Orochi-sama took measures!
But then why?!
It would've been impossible for them
to repair it overnight...
So it was you guys who messed with our ship!
How could you?!
Last night, we were so pumped
and having a good time!
It's cool! This is perfect for me!
Oh, nice!
Should I wear this?
Wait a minute. I like this one, too!
Oh, I can't decide!
Hey, Franky!
You can use this, too!
Are you sure, Luffy?
Yeah, I am.
I'm a pirate...
So I'd rather wear this.
We're in Amigasa Village
which is here.
And the rendezvous point, Tokage Port,
is here.
4,000 troops will
gather around Kin'emon tomorrow.
It's gonna be spectacular.
Right, right! Enough to make our eyes pop out!
Despite the fact I'm a skeleton
and don't have eyes in the first place!
Where are you going?
I need to break this one in.
Don't get lost.
Tomorrow's a big day.
What happened?!
A blast?!
No way!
Don't tell me that's...
...where the Sunny is!
What's going on?!
Damn! The Sunny!
Who the hell did that?!
Dammit!
Sunny!
Just kidding.
Did you think you can destroy the Sunny
with an ordinary bomb? How naive!
This Thousand Sunny is...
...a ship that was built from Jewel Tree Adam
and it'll sail through a thousand seas!
There's no way this ship would be destroyed
by that stupid bomb!
You mean it didn't work?!
Of course not!
It didn't even make a scratch!
But the sails got burned!
Sorry, Kin'emon!
It took us a while to repair the sails!
I see! So that is what happened!
Hey, Kin!
Why are there only a few of you?!
It's not exactly as I heard, but it's okay
for me to destroy those battleships, right?!
He's right. There were supposed to be
a lot of allies here.
What happened to the 3,500 people
from the Excavation Labor Camp?!
Yeah, I don't see them.
Those bosses scattered to different regions
and gathered mobsters...
There must've been over 200 of them.
I don't see them...
At Itachi Port,
there were 200 of Dogstorm's Musketeers,
and 280 of Atamayama Thieves Brigade!
The ships that we repaired with them
were supposed to join us here!
A huge cache of weapons that'll be enough for everyone
was supposed to be delivered here from Ringo, too!
Hey, Kin'emon! Is there any problem?!
I... made a blunder...
Luffy-dono, I am sorry!
Our plan was all leaked...
It is all my fault! I deeply apologize!
I have no idea what happened to everyone!
That's why they're not here!
Should we fight without them?!
What?! No way!
I see... Well, we have no choice...
What is he doing?
Idiot! Bombs can't destroy our ship!
I don't think you understand the situation.
You guys are all alone!
None of your allies will come!
If the ship can't be destroyed,
I'll pull you out into the water.
Enjoy your watery grave,
fools from the Worst Generation!
What a shame! I fell into Orochi's trap!
You guys are all alone!
None of your allies will come!
Enjoy your watery grave,
fools from the Worst Generation!
What do you mean by
none of our allies will come?!
Knowing that doesn't do you any good!
You guys have no chance to win now!
Zeus!
Ninpo: Lightning Blast!
How about this?!
Cien Fleurs!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Both of you are amazing!
Screw you!
Is that it?
Hey, you guys! Answer my question!
All right. I'll tell you before you die!
However, we actually don't know
much about it either!
We couldn't destroy the lion ship...
But we sank all the ships
docked at the port last night!
What?!
Damn! We took the trouble to repair those ships...
That's not all!
Orochi-sama is a meticulous man.
We were ordered to destroy all major bridges
connecting the regions!
Now you get it?
No one's able to come here anymore!
Even if they could get here,
they won't be able to reach Onigashima without ships!
And if you miss today,
you'll never get another chance for your raid!
And we'll kill all the rebels that we found
one by one from tomorrow!
That's right! The Akazaya's allies won't come!
If we sink their boat, it's over!
That's how easy it is!
You idiots!
Now that Luffy's here...
But it is a shame!
I am sorry, everyone!
These voices that jeer the Akazaya members...
That's praise for the greatest act of my life!
Now the curtain will fall for the Akazaya members!
Aim at the Akazaya's boat!
Kin-sama, look out!
Yeah...
Kin-sama!
Shoot!
I-I cannot cut them all!
Thank you! Law-dono's crew!
We're not gonna slow anyone down anymore!
Yeah, we don't ever wanna
go through that again!
That's right.
This time, we'll protect our captain!
You guys...
The second round! Shoot!
Protect the Akazaya members!
Shishilian-dono, thank you!
There is one more thing that we haven't told you!
I'm sorry.
We didn't want to plunge you into further despair...
What?!
Today's banquet isn't just another banquet
on the night of the Fire Festival...
It's also a banquet to celebrate...
...the alliance between us, the Animal Kingdom Pirates,
and the infamous Big Mom Pirates!
Kaido and Big Mom?!
An alliance of the two Emperors of the Sea?!
Seriously?! That's too dangerous!
We ran for our lives from her!
Olin, I don't ever wanna see her again!
It looks like we're in the worst situation ever.
See?
It's easier for you to just give up!
We have both Kaido-sama
and Big Mom on our side!
What can they do about
the difference in strength?!
The Worst Generation?!
They're nothing!
Sink all of them into the sea
and it's over!
Get ready to fire!
You're in no position to be arrogant!
Don't mess with us!
Everyone, back off!
Idiot... You back off!
What are you doing, Tra-guy?!
I said I'll do it!
I can't count on you!
Both of you, back off!
I'll do it!
Jaggy, damn you!
Shut your mouth!
Listen to me, you morons!
Gee! First come, first served!
You bastard!
I'll be the first!
No, you won't!
Tra-guy!
Damn you!
You can't compete against my Room ability
in the rain!
That ability isn't fair!
So what?
You're just showing off!
Look who's talking.
Go away!
It only takes a single blow for me!
Do you mean I can't bring them down
with a single blow?!
I'll do it.
You two are losers. Any complaints?
Losers?!
--Who are you calling that?!
--I won't lose to anyone!
Don't be pushy!
D-Don't think
you're gonna make it out of here alive!
Stop barking, you small fry!
I'll take care of them.
Shut up! The competition is on!
Room!
Bounce-Man!
Punk Vise!
Injection Shot!
Hey, did you see that?
Who's a loser now?!
That's next.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
I'll sink that ship, too!
Too?!
Let me make one thing clear.
I'm the one who just sank the ship.
Are you blind?!
I'm the one who sank it!
Don't be ridiculous!
I sank it!
Why don't you two just kid around like that?
What did you say?!
I thought they were allied...
Use this chance to draw away from them!
Is that...?!
KYO
The Kyoshiro Family's ship!
Kyoshiro's here!
I'm safe now!
He's the one from that time!
He's strong...
Seems like you're in trouble.
What can I do to help?
You came for us!
Orochi-sama ordered us to sink the Akazaya members
and that's all we have to do,
but it's not as easy as we thought.
All right. Sink the enemy, right?
Count on me!
Quiet, you two.
Here he comes!
Oh, no!
What?!
That man...
What is he thinking?
Help has arrived!
Kyoshiro A.K.A. Denjiro!
The surprised Akazaya members are approached
by a fleet of ships and Kanjuro shows his teeth!
A samurai watching over the fierce battle
puts his life on the line for the late Oden's wishes.
What destiny awaits them?!
Now they advance!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Good Luck?! Leader Kin'emon's Plot!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!