Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Luffy-dono! I am glad!
I am glad that you came!
On the night of the Fire Festival,
after finding out their crewmate,
Kanjuro, was an enemy informant,
it seemed like all hope
for the Akazaya samurai was lost,
but Luffy and the other pirates
came through for them!
Why's Luffy's clan here?!
Not only them, I heard Law was jailed!
Luffy-dono, I am sorry!
Our plan was all leaked...
Should we fight without them?!
What?! No way!
There is one more thing that we haven't told you!
I'm sorry.
We didn't want to plunge you into further despair...
What?!
Today's banquet isn't just another banquet
on the night of the Fire Festival...
It's also a banquet to celebrate...
...the alliance between us, the Animal Kingdom Pirates,
and the infamous Big Mom Pirates!
Shut up! The competition is on!
Bounce-Man!
Injection Shot!
The Kyoshiro Family's ship!
Kyoshiro's here!
I'm safe now!
Seems like you're in trouble.
What can I do to help?
Oh, no!
That man...
What is he thinking?
"Good Luck?!
Leader Kin'emon's Plot!"
What are you doing, Boss-san?!
What's going on?!
I didn't want to sink the ship.
So I've only disabled the cannon
pointed at us.
W-What's going on?!
Be careful! He's quite skillful!
He's the Shogun's dog!
He's a yakuza
who's taking the place of Boss Hyogoro!
Akazaya samurai!
I am a yakuza from the Flower Capital,
people call me Napping Kyoshiro!
My Kyoshiro Family is 200 strong
and we would like to help you with your raid!
--What?!
--You've got to be kidding, Boss!
Does he want to join our side?
I thought he was an enemy.
He was supposed to be...
What does he want?
What do you mean?! You're Orochi's subordinate!
What favor do you owe us?
I owe the Kozuki Clan
an immeasurable number of favors and debts...
I often remember you, Kin-san!
Kin-san?!
The Mountain God incident
that occurred in the capital 40 years ago!
People thought that was
just Oden-sama going crazy...
But it wasn't.
That happened because the younger you
who was so greedy tried to sell a little boar!
Paradise Waterfall!
What?
There's only one person left
who knows that!
That's why they call it the Mountain God!
What?!
Oh, no! It's my fault that the capital is...!
Don't tell me...
Are you Denjiro?!
--What?!
--Denjiro-san?!
Denjiro!
Too many enemies...
Give me a hand, Ashura!
Okay!
Denjiro! Ashura!
Advance, Kin'emon!
Take over the future of the Kozuki
and Oden-sama's dream!
You're alive...
That is right! I am the Kozuki Clan's retainer
and one of the Akazaya Nine!
Denjiro!
W-What?!
I guess I am unrecognizable...
When I learned of Kin-san and the others' return,
I wanted to come forward right away,
I remained an enemy, just in case.
Sure enough, if I had revealed my identity,
the spy would've blown my cover
and I would've been wiped out by Orochi!
Denjiro!
Shut up!
However, since I continued to earn
Orochi's trust until the end,
I was able to free the 1,000 samurai
in Rasetsu Town Prisoners' Quarters!
--Look over there!
--Reinforcements for the enemy?!
No, they're not.
Those symbols are...
Don't tell me...
Samurai clan crests!
1,200 soldiers in total! Count us in!
This day's finally come! We get to fight!
B-Boss Kyoshiro is one of the Akazaya Nine?!
Call Onigashima now!
Y-Yeah!
Denjiro...
Now, Kin-san!
You're a hell of a smart man!
This symbol implying the date
and the rendezvous point for the great battle!
Two birds on fire and...
...a Habu (pit viper) and...
...a Reversed Crescent Moon
which signifies rebellion!
"On the day of the Fire Festival.
Twilight - the second hour of the bird.
At Habu Port."
The original symbol didn't have those two lines.
This flyer was leaked to Orochi and the others...
but Yasuie-sama altered it
before he died.
These two newly-added lines mean...
...crossing out the middle letters!
That means the new rendezvous point is
HABUMINATO (HABU PORT)
Habuminato (Habu Port) without the middle part...
...which is hato!
HATO
HATO (WHARF)
So it's the wharf at Habu Port which has a great view of the
maple tree forest that Yasuie-sama loved.
What?
What?!
Hearing two lines on a habu (pit viper),
anyone would easily get the message.
But you, sensing that Orochi's spy was with you,
purposefully told your people
that it was "Tokage Port"!
Every port in the Land of Wano
has a name that sounds the same as an animal.
The body is a bit too long,
but adding limbs to a habu snake makes it a lizard.
Tokage (Lizard) Port is in Udon.
It's true, that picture didn't look like a lizard.
I believed it
because Kin-sama was so confident...
The spy fell right into your trap,
and told Orochi
that Tokage Port was the new rendezvous point!
It was the foolishness of the one
who acted as he liked in the capital for so long!
Orochi misjudged the distance between each place
and didn't do anything until last night!
I am going to show you hell!
--Did you find the ship?
--Yes.
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KIBI AND UDON
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KURI AND UDON
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN RINGO AND HAKUMAI
ITACHI PORT, KURI
But by that time,
everyone had crossed those great bridges,
and the ships they needed had left the port!
All that was destroyed were leftover ships!
Just as you planned,
the 4,200 troops that you recruited...
...were lying low at the Habu Port wharf
until the time came!
Then, are they all safe?!
Even after 20 years,
I still remember Oden-sama's legendary death!
We have lived our lives
believing in the Kozuki Clan's comeback!
We are coming with you, Akazaya samurai!
We are fully ready!
The plan to raid Onigashima
hasn't gone wrong at all!
Adding the 1,200 of us,
it's 5,400 in total!
Now let's go, everyone!
To Onigashima!
There are tons of them!
This is bad!
Anything from Onigashima?!
I've been calling them, but they haven't noticed
since they're busy with the banquet!
Whoa-whoa, that's amazing!
After all that trouble,
we ended up with more allies!
We were gonna do it anyway though.
--The greater the force the better.
--It's good to have them.
We can easily beat the Animal Kingdom Pirates now!
It's spectacular!
I don't really know what happened,
but everything's alright now!
Don't lower your guard.
Big Mom is at Onigashima, too.
Oh, no! Nothing has changed!
Damn you, Kin'emon!
Kin-san! That's our leader!
You're worthy of respect as I thought!
That's our Kin'emon-san!
You're the only one who can lead us!
We'll follow you to the end!
So it wasn't " tokage (lizard)"...
It was " hato (wharf)"...
Be honest, Kin'emon.
We know you're not capable of
telling such a clever lie.
It turned out to be all right.
We won't get mad so say it.
Stop.
You really thought it was "tokage," right?
Stop it!
Well, it turned out fine after all!
It was a lucky mistake.
Maybe I'll die in this battle!
I feel like I've used up a lifetime's worth of luck!
Yes, you're stunningly lucky!
--Kin'emon-dono!
--Our beloved leader!
But since we share the same goal,
it was our luck, too!
He's right, Kin-sama!
We won't let you die alone!
We served Oden-sama together!
We were born and raised differently,
but we'll die together! Don't forget that!
I am not happy to hear it
from annoying men like you guys.
Raise your sword, Kin-san!
We know we'll win this preliminary skirmish!
I accept my fate!
It has been 20 years
since Oden-sama's tragic death!
The Land of Wano has been in a darkness
darker than this cloudy sky!
But the time has come!
Now, to Onigashima!
Let's avenge Oden-sama's death together!
Kin'emon-dono!
We're gonna change the Land of Wano
at any cost!
--Let's retreat for now!
--O-Okay!
--What's this?!
--What's going on?!
--What are we gonna do?!
--We've got to get away!
Don't think you can go home safely
after you mock me!
Hey! We don't need to go after them...
Gee...
Damn Kin'emon...
I have to report to Onigashima.
I fulfilled my role that Orochi-sama gave me!
There's just one thing left to do!
Kawamatsu?!
I did not know
you were this good at drawing!
I won't let you go!
I won't let you kidnap Momonosuke-sama!
Kawamatsu! I am coming, too!
You can't! You'll drown!
We all have shared
many years of pain and suffering!
We served under Oden-sama together
and we lost him together!
Do you enjoy deceiving
and betraying such friends?
Do you enjoy trampling on our wishes
and disappointing us?
Kanjuro!
Yeah! I'm having so much fun!
Deception, subterfuge, and then a surprise ending!
There's no role in the world
that's more worthwhile than this!
I like how you guys played the fool, too!
Kanjuro!
We'll end the play by staining the stage
with the Kozuki's blood!
Kawamatsu!
Momonosuke-sama!
Don't worry, Momonosuke.
I'll let your sister follow you into death.
Kawamatsu!
I swear I'll find Hiyori and kill her, too!
I know she's alive now!
Kanjuro!
I cannot believe you drew a bird
that flies so beautifully!
All we saw were ugly and useless drawings
that dissolved in water!
That was part of my acting!
It's so high!
Let me down! I am scared! Somebody!
We sank them at the same time again!
I'll sink the last ship!
--Let me do it!
--I said I'll do it!
Momonosuke-sama!
Kanjuro? Momo?
Hey! Where are you going?!
Goodbye, fools!
In any case, you're no match for Kaido-sama's army!
You can't even enter the island!
Help!
As he is taken away,
the young general Momonosuke endures his trembling fear,
shouts his heart out and encourages his friends.
Enraged at Kanjuro's betrayal, the Straw Hats blow away
the enemy's attack along with the rough waves!
They'll save their friend at any cost!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Tearful Promise! The Kidnapped Momonosuke!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!