Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
You're finally here!
A former Warlord of the Sea,
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei,
finally returned to the Straw Hats.
To celebrate Jimbei's coming aboard,
let's make a toast!
Yeah!
While Kin'emon and the others were
strategizing on how to enter Onigashima,
the Straw Hats were ahead of them
attacking the enemy's fortress.
"Kaido's Trump Card!
The Tobi Roppo Appear!"
This torii gate...
This is the first obstacle in our path
to raid Onigashima.
An obstacle? Are there guards?
Not only guards.
Tons of cannons and other weapons
are set up there.
It's like a small fortress.
And it's the Fire Festival today.
I suspect a bunch of soldiers
are holding a banquet.
Then, what if they've been notified about the raid?
If we go any farther,
we'll be easy prey for them.
That's not good!
In any case...
We must let everyone know about this quickly!
Fortunately, it seems like the guards at the gate
have not noticed us yet!
Um...
Wasn't there a ship heading that way earlier?
What?
Hey...
The Straw Hats' ship is missing.
What?!
No way! Luffy-dono!
Is Luffy-dono in there?!
Law-dono! Head the ship that way!
We must save them now!
No, I can get there sooner if I swim!
Kawamatsu-san!
It's dangerous to go alone. I'll go...
Law-dono! Hurry, the ship!
You're in my way!
Gum-Gum...
Is that...
Gee, those fools...
They always do whatever suits them!
Hey, what are you doing?! Shoot him down...
Red...
...Hawk!
The guards at the torii gate...
...have been wiped out!
Look how many weapons there are!
If we'd been attacked by them...
Yeah, I wonder how much manpower
would've been lost...
We can all go, right?
To Onigashima!
All right, guys! Well done!
It was okay.
Not bad!
Guys, good job!
--You guys should've helped a little!
--Heh!
Gee, those rascals...
Let's have a toast!
But there's no booze to be found...
I'll look for some.
You don't have a good nose
even though you're a cook.
I wasn't aware moss balls had noses.
--Worthless cook.
--Dumb moss ball.
--Shitty cook.
--Moss head.
I don't have a nose because I'm a skeleton!
We know.
I can't believe hundreds of soldiers
were overwhelmed by just a few of them...
They're extremely strong!
But other times,
they can be so carefree...
They're hard to understand.
It's so reassuring to have them!
Bonding with those incredible people...
That's my Kin-san!
What a man!
Luffy-dono!
It's cold!
Hey! Can't you even hold a barrel?!
This is why I hate to drink with you guys!
Shogun-sama!
Come to the sound of the clapping hands.
You're there! Here I come!
Hey, Shogun-sama,
you're in a particularly good mood today.
I know!
Something good happened to you, didn't it?!
How did you know?
What? What is it?!
There was a piece of junk
that was always in my way...
But it's finally been disposed of...
You're happy
because some garbage was taken away?
Shogun-sama is so odd!
Right?!
Am I that odd?!
Yes, you are!
But that's kind of cute!
Right?!
Why don't you come closer?!
I'm the Shogun of the Land of Wano,
Kurozumi Orochi!
Hey!
I want more red-bean soup!
Please wait a moment!
Big Mom wants it, too, now...
Big Mom?
What does it matter?
We have the annual Golden Festival tonight.
It's a major event where you can dance
or just have fun.
Who is at its center?
Queen!
Yes! It's me!
Who is the singer-and-dancer-type
Lead Performer?
Queen!
Yes! It's me!
On top of that, if I get thinner, I'll be...
...too popular.
If you understand, just give me red-bean soup,
you fool!
There's excitement everywhere...
That's good.
This is how a banquet should be...
Yes! I can't wait to see the show tonight!
But what is he doing?
Who?
Who do you think?!
I'm talking about my son!
He has to show his face! It's a banquet!
I-I'll look for him!
Kaido-sama!
All six members of the Tobi Roppo are here,
so please grant them an audience!
The Tobi Roppo?
I don't remember calling them,
but, all right, let's introduce them to Linlin.
Where did she go?
But... Big Mom is changing into her kimono now.
Kaido-sama! The Tobi Roppo has arrived!
Let them in!
GOLDEN FESTIVAL
Today's a long-awaited casual day
Here comes the champ Brachio
The Plague...
Queen!
Thank you for waiting, you all!
It's the annual Golden Festival!
Let's have fun!
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
If I get thinner, I'll be too popular
So I don't get thinner, that's my kind of...
...funk!
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
I may look chubby, but it's all muscle
I can sing and dance, that's my kind of...
...funk!
Okay! Onigashima!
Are you having fun?!
Here we go, you guys!
I'll take the usual roll call!
Shout from your gut!
Waiting for the moment of your turn
Are you sick of waiting, Waiters?!
Lost a bet
But you just laughed at it
Just laugh, Pleasures!
A hot present, the Smile's gift
Go ahead and roar, Gifters!
The quintessence of strength
called the Headliners!
You guys are the best!
HEADLINERS
The top six
Here come those badasses
Dangerousness indefinite
Strength infinite
The Tobi Roppo!
Just kidding!
I've never heard them respond,
have you?!
Forget about those impertinent fools!
Next, the monsters!
The Numbers!
They're all over the place!
Who cares?
Next, Orochi's people! Here we go!
First, the samurai squad, the Mimawari-gumi!
Oniwabanshu!
He's calling you, Fukurokuju!
Don't you have to go?
Oh, please.
It is my duty to protect you at all times...
Don't be so formal!
Due to my perfect strategy,
the Akazaya members are dead!
There is nothing to be afraid of anymore!
Today's the Fire Festival! Loosen up!
Enjoy it even if it kills you, you guys!
Enjoy or die!
In addition,
we have some very special guests this year!
I heard they're already near!
What?!
They're Big Mom's children!
Queen won't shut up-arinsu.
Did you hear him saying
the Tobi Roppo is impertinent-arinsu?!
Stop ending your sentences like that...
Is that your thing now?!
How embarrassing...
Come on, Pay-Pay, you're so shy-arinsu.
Don't call me Pay-Pay!
If Queen drops dead,
who do you think will become the next Lead Performer?
You think it'll be you, don't you?
I'm not interested in becoming a Lead Performer.
X. DRAKE
I'd appreciate if you drop out of this competition.
SASAKI
Pay-Pay, you can't compete, either, right?
You'll drop out?
PAGE ONE
You let that fool named Soba Mask get away.
Hey, you!
If you mess with my Pay-Pay,
I'll kick your ass, Sasaki!
ULTI
Hey, stop, Big Sis!
--Did you say "Stop"?!
--Don't get mad at me!
Did you say, "Don't get mad"?! You...
WHO'S-WHO
You're annoying me, you shitty brats.
Yeah? They're kind of cute.
Ul-chan who snaps at everyone is my favorite.
BLACK MARIA
No matter how many times I tell her
to choose who she snaps at, she doesn't get it.
She's not cute at all.
I am cute!
That's enough...
Now...
why are we being called in and kept waiting?
Urgent business came up!
When Kaido-san says, "Something important,"
it's always about the same thing...
Is it a family matter again-arinsu?
TOBI ROPPO, ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Is Kaido stupid?
Don't snap at him!
Hey! Kin'emon! We found the enemies!
Everyone's catching up to us?
Hey, Mosshead!
Where did you get that?
Oh, you found booze, Zoro!
I told you I can tell where it is by the smell.
That's his instinct...
All he thinks about is booze and swords.
Hey! It's all ready!
Okay! Let's make a toast!
Luffy! If you don't come here now,
we're gonna drink it all!
--I mean, Zoro will.
--I won't!
Okay!
Here you go, Boss-san.
Thank you.
Let's make a toast to the super helmsman
that we've always wanted!
I wish we had time for me to sing a song.
I've never exchanged a cup of sake
in such a pleasant mood.
Jimbei.
We've been waiting for you!
Mm-hm!
I couldn't wait to travel across the sea
with you all, too!
All right! Are you ready?!
Guys!
Yeah!
In celebration of...
...Jimbei's coming aboard our ship...
Thank you, Luffy-dono!
--What's that?
--You quickly got past the first barrier...
I appreciate it!
What?! Everyone's so full of spirit!
Conquering this fortress must've boosted
everyone's morale!
They'll get to Onigashima at breakneck speed.
Th-Th-Then, let's make a toast fast
and join them!
We won't waste this opportunity
that Luffytaro and the others gave us!
Yeah! We won't let our enemies prepare!
The Straw Hats are so dependable!
Yeah!
Since I first met him,
he kept changing despair into hope!
Kozuki's samurai!
You loyal warriors!
Follow us!
All ships, to Onigashima!
Charge!
What are you doing?
Luffy.
Hey, Luffy!
--Let's stop.
--What?
Let's do it with them!
A banquet and a toast!
After taking down Kaido!
And bringing down Orochi and Big Mom!
After we win this battle,
we'll have the biggest...
...banquet ever!
Gee. You're the one who said
we should make a toast!
You're always so impulsive!
Nami-san's right.
Am I?
Well, it's always been like this.
It's a waste of time to complain now.
Mm-hm!
You have no right to nod!
We're okay,
but how about you, Boss-san?
You know my answer!
I'm in!
Let's go, guys!
Follow the samurai!
Yes! Captain!
Onigashima is home to a giant skull that
looks extremely ominous!
With Oden's wishes in mind,
the Akazaya members now set out for the battlefield!
After overcoming many hardships,
the samurai warriors cut off their retreat and begin to infiltrate!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Samurai Warriors' Earnestness!
The Straw Hats Land at Onigashima!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!