mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
You fools!
Stop drinking!
Pick up your weapons!
We're getting raided!
Open up the Land of Wano!
"Onigashima in Tumult!
Luffy's All-Out War Begins!"
Oden!
Sunacchi!!
Oden Two-Sword Style!
Paradise Totsuka!
The scar that Oden left on me...
Why does it hurt?
How did the blade pierce my body?
Don't underestimate my samurai retainers!
I don't mind...
...being forgotten!
But...
...my spirit will live on!
Are they using Oden's Ryuo?!
Let it pierce through to the other side!
Kaido!
Kaido-sama!
Y-You guys!
They're the Akazaya Nine!
Oden's real retainers!
They're so strong!
This is a dangerous banquet!
Is Kaido dead?!
No way!
The invincible Kaido-sama can't be dead!
Fight them! Kill the Akazaya rats!
Straw Hat, Kid, and the others earlier
were just decoys for this surprise attack?!
Stay alert, you guys!
There might still be intruders somewhere!
That's right!
Listen, you weaklings!
We won't let you harm
Kin'emon and the others!
Okay! We're gonna join them!
Let's give Kaido another thrashing!
There you are!
Yamato!
Headbutt!
Ulti!
You came in droves again!
How dare you hit me!
It hurt so bad!
I'm your ally but you attacked me,
and you're running around
alongside Straw Hat...
What are you doing-arinsu?!
There's nothing wrong...
The day I become Kozuki
Oden has finally come!
Kozuki Oden?!
What are you talking about?!
Are you crazy?!
I'm serious!
Are you okay?!
Let's kick their asses and move on!
Yeah!
Young Master Yamato, we have a problem!
Your father was just attacked
and there are a bunch of enemies on the floor!
Stop fooling around!
I know!
What?
I'm not your ally anymore,
and I don't care if my father dies!
What?!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
What is it this time?
There is really too much going on at this banquet...
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
That must be...
--Oh, no!
--She sees Luffy!
Ugh! Big Mom!
Not when I'm so busy!
I finally found you.
Straw Hat!
Room!
Wait!
Yamato's this way!
You wanna catch him and win the right
to challenge a Lead Performer, right?
I have some other business.
Get out of my way, Ulti!
I'm Kozuki Oden! And I'll take down Kaido!
Who's Oden, you ultra-idiot?!
You have to cherish your family!
Look who's talking!
In that case, be nice to Page One!
What?! Don't tell me what to do!
I'm...
...nicer to Pay-Pay than
anyone else in the world!
Ulti...
...Mortar!
Let's go! We can save him now!
Wait!
Look at that!
What?! Is that...
Shinobu-chan!
Don't worry, Nico Robin!
We have dependable friends!
Boss-san!
Just like Shinobu...
Keeping a low profile here
will help at some point!
So be patient for now!
Yes, I got it!
When the time is ripe, we'll go all out!
I'll be counting on you, Boss-san!
Carrot! Let's make a break for it!
Uh-huh!
That's impossible-wall!
Mama's orders are absolute!
That's right!
Prepare yourself!
Black Ball!
Hey, are you okay?!
Here I go!
Me, too!
Storm Cloud!
Eleclaw!
Ninpo: Ectoplasm Thunder!
We did it!
Let's go, Carrot!
Uh-huh!
To the place where Big Mom is!
Yeah!
Wait... What?! Why?!
We just took the trouble to get away!
I...
...make it a principle never to let go of
any treasure I've seized!
Are you talking about Zeus?
Wait for me! I'll get him back at any cost!
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
You kicked sand in the eyes of my pirate group
so to kill you...
I came all the way from the Totto Land!
Straw Hat!
Oh, no... This is not good.
I must fight too or Mama will kill me!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yummy!
Zeus-chan!
Na...mi!
I'm glad that you're okay.
I was worried about you.
I was worried about you, too. Really.
I'm happy!
Our bond runs deep as I thought!
You're hurting me, Nami! Let go of me!
I'll never let you go!
Nami...
Yes, I can see it!
The bond between you two
which glitters like treasure!
She's right, Zeus!
You're my very own precious treasure...
You are the moon unaware of the dawn.
May your purpose be fulfilled...
...and cast nine shadows on
the night woven of 20 years
and you shall know the
brilliance of the dawn!
Our time has come.
By taking Kaido's head,
we will avenge our lord Kozuki Oden!
Run! To Kuri!
Don't look back!
Oden-sama!
Straw Hat! Why are you here?!
Don't tell me you came to take down Kaido,
that's too funny.
That's not what I'm here for!
What?
Luffy?!
Straw hat man... What did you say?!
That's not, Luffy?!
No! I'm...
After 20 years,
the Akazaya samurai will come to get their revenge...
Orochi's prediction that no one believed
was connected with all the other dots!
I can't believe you joined
hands with pirates.
The rumor about the shadows
at the ruins of Oden Castle...
Punk Hazard.
Dressrosa.
Zou the Phantom Island.
Behind it all was the Straw Hats!
By a curious coincidence,
you guys were hiding behind the Straw Hats
who I see as my enemies.
Some of you held out for 20 years
while others jumped forward and ran around,
and you ended up gathering all your troops.
But pirates will stab you in the back!
The moment they know you'll lose,
they'll abandon you and run.
Besides,
I've already taken Straw Hat down a peg once!
You are insulting him!
Luffy-dono is nothing like you guys!
You, Kaido, the officers, Orochi,
and all your subordinates!
I'm here to kick all your asses!
Luffy...
He is the man
who will stand at the pinnacle of the sea someday!
Even if we die, he will still be here!
The Daybreak will come to
the Land of Wano again!
Because...
...that is what we promised our lord!
It's gonna be an all-out war!
The tide has turned!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates struggle
against the surging samurai warriors!
Kaido looks down on Luffy
who started the fight!
It's the night of the full moon!
As they fight while thinking of their battered home,
the Minks show their true form!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battle Under the Moon!
The Berserker, Sulong the Moon Lion!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!